<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3338531-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/a-game-for-harry-celebrity-football-match-at-the-daggers-3338531.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>A Game For Harry: Celebrity Football Match at the Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>A Game For Harry: Celebrity Football Match at the Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>A Game For Harry: Celebrity Football Match at the Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>At the Daggers On Sunday 9th October Charity Celebrity Football Match</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Come down to the Chigwell Construction Stadium on Sunday 9th October to raise money for Harry Parker who is a football mad 6-year-old who suffers from Spastic Diplegia Cerebral Palsy as a result of being starved of oxygen at birth. Please join us on the journey to get Harry walking after life changing surgery. This  surgery is not available on the NHS, so Harry’s family are hoping to raise £75,000 so they can get Harry to go to Great Ormond Street Hospital in London for an operation called Selective Dorsal Rhizotomy. This operation will permanently reduce the spasticity in Harry’s lower body and allow the development of his muscles that were previously hindered. It will allow Harry to experience greater opportunities in life. With this operation he will be able to play football and ride a bike, two things that his disability has restricted him from doing.
<br  /><br  />
Here at the Daggers we are hosting a Charity fund-raiser celebrity football match to raise money for Harry’s operation. Starting at 1pm there will be a celebrity gents and ladies match and live entertainment. With stars such as Dapper Laughs, Stephen Bear, Lydia Lucy and James ‘Arg’ Argent all to make appearances it’s set to be a great day here at the Chigwell Construction Stadium. To buy tickets please go to: <a href="http://www.bluemoonfootie.co.uk/" >www.bluemoonfootie.co.uk/</a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/gameforharry2-86292-3338522_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/gameforharry2-169292-3338523_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-05 10:10:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Home</Tags>
</News>