<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3341168-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-redbridge-0-0-tranmere-rovers-3341168.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge were held to a goalless draw at home to promotion rivals Tranmere Rovers.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Manager John Still elected to name the same squad for the fifth game in a row, with the starting XI having won the previous four matches in the National League.
<br  /><br  />
Fejiri Okenabirhie went close to opening the scoring for the hosts in the 17th minute, but his effort from just inside the box was off target.
<br  /><br  />
Three minutes later, the hosts were indebted to a brilliant save from Elliot Justham, who rushed out quickly to close down Rovers striker James Norwood.
<br  /><br  />
With 16 minutes left in the half, Jordan Maguire-Drew forced Tranmere stopper Steve Davies into a super save with a half-volley from 12 yards.
<br  /><br  />
At the other end, Justham and Scott Doe combined to deny Andy Cook an opener for the hosts as the half ended level.
<br  /><br  />
In the 54th minute, Tranmere were reduced to 10 men when Michael Ihiekwe was shown a second yellow card for hauling down Corey Whitely.
<br  /><br  />
With five minutes to go, substitute Chris Assombalonga headed a corner against the post for Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
Oliver Hawkins forced Davies into action soon after, while Andy Cook fired wide for the visitors late on, but it ended goalless.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3316007_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-01 20:30:51 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>