<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3343323-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-dagenham-redbridge-1-cambridge-united-4-3343323.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 Cambridge United 4</headline>
  <page_title>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 Cambridge United 4</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 Cambridge United 4</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Crumble At Cambridge</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A bleak morning in Cambridgeshire saw the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s beaten 4-1 in a bitter encounter with the Cambridge United academy.
<br  /><br  />
Defensive errors were the prime cause of a heavy defeat for the visitors, who were a goal down just forty seconds in after Scott Mitchell surrendered possession in the box, before the U’s netted from a set-piece following a Kieran Walker-Brown foul.
<br  /><br  />
Joe White gave the away side a glimmer of hope with a tidy finish from a sensational ball midway the second-half.
<br  /><br  />
But all hopes of levelling were extinguished nine minutes from time by a powerful finish that Chapman could only help on its way, and the U’s number fourteen applied the gloss to the victory with an 18-yard free-kick after the Daggers stopper handled outside the area.
<br  /><br  />
It was a relatively underwhelming performance from an off colour-looking Daggers, who have enjoyed a recent spell of red hot form that has seen them claim ten points from five league games, as well as extend their run in the cup.
<br  /><br  />
The London side’s unbeaten streak has contributed vastly to their recent progress, but came to halt at the hands of the MK Dons last week as the Buckinghamshire outfit injected a harsh dose of reality that coach Micah Hyde will have looked to his players to bounce back from.
<br  /><br  />
Their last visit to East Anglia was definitely something the Daggers could have taken inspiration from, shining in a 4-1 victory against Peterborough United a fortnight ago as part of their positive run of results.
<br  /><br  />
But on this occasion, the sharp and clinical nature of an in-form Daggers side failed to present itself, much to the joy of Cambridge United, who took full advantage as the visitors struggled against their opposition’s early onslaught.
<br  /><br  />
Cambridge themselves did not appear particularly skilful or tactical with their approach – primarily, their game plan appeared more to revolve around regular overloads in the opposition box and exploiting any defensive errors they could force – unfortunately for Micah Hyde and his team, the Daggers caved in on a few too many occasions.
<br  /><br  />
The relentless pressure instantaneously imposed on the Daggers forced the visiting backline into a number of rash moves that could have seen the hosts escape with the game by the half hour mark.
<br  /><br  />
Centre-back Scott Mitchell was forced into a scuffed back-pass that trickled directly to a home player, who teed up the number eleven for a drilled finish, before Keiran Walker-Browne’s foul on the away number nine allowed the number ten to guide a stooping header in from the resulting free-kick.
<br  /><br  />
The east London outfit’s best chance of the half arrived before ten minutes, and utility wingback Blue Gallagher’s persistence and tenacity amongst the presence of two United defenders came agonisingly close to reaping its rewards.
<br  /><br  />
The outnumbered wingback managed to force his way deep into the U’s penalty area, but Dylan Florence’s finish from the midfielder’s low cross was cleared off the line before the forward skewed his second attempt across the face of goal as Daggers players were left holding their heads in disbelief.
<br  /><br  />
At the other end, Joe Carter, who had produced an early save to deny the away number five’s low drive, preserved scoreline with yet another good save, pushing a looping header over the bar shortly after the Daggers were let off for a handball in the box as a Cambridge United man skied a penalty half an hour in.
<br  /><br  />
The second half looked a lot more promising for the visiting side who, by no means, had surrendered hope.
<br  /><br  />
In-form striker Dylan Florence had a goal-bound effort saved ten minutes after the restart, before Scott Mitchell made amends for his earlier error with a superlative cross-field pass that released Joe White, who slid a diagonally between the legs of the home stopper with half an hour still to play.
<br  /><br  />
However, the hosts appeared keen to wrap up the victory, and substitute goalkeeper Louie Chapman did well to initially deny the hosts a chance after the Daggers were left exposed on the counter, but was helpless to a powerful close-range strike that he could only palm into the bottom left corner of his goal after the away side failed to clear.
<br  /><br  />
In a desperate bid to deny the U’s a fourth, Louie Chapman promptly vacated his goalline as the hosts attempted to break into the Daggers penalty area, but ended up conceding an eighteen-yard free-kick that was powerfully curled in by the away number fourteen after the stopper handled outside the area as the Daggers were forced to succumb to a bitter defeat.
<br  /><br  />
Academy Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the tie:
<br  />
“Poor defensively poor in the first half especially, not correct attitude, intensity, resilience, but we did improve in the second, there were a few individual positive performances which is the most important thing, but not enough to win the game”, said Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“On our second-half performance, I think we may have done enough to draw, as our front unit was functioning well, but we conceded soft goals again which made things difficult, individuals have to learn from their mistakes”, the coach continued.
<br  /><br  />
Line-up
<br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1. Joe Carter, 17. Blue Gallagher, 3. Hani Berchiche, 5. Kieran Walker-Brown, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. Liam Gordon, 8. Tyrique Hyde, 9. Joe White, 10. Jordy Mongoy, 11. Mustaphe Ali, 14. Dylan Florence, 2. Kwasi Opoko, 4. Elliot Bonds, 15. David Agboola, 16. Louie Chapman
<br  /><br  />
Goalscorers
<br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Joe White 64’
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-03 10:05:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Home</Tags>
</News>