<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3344022-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reactionjohn-still-on-the-tranmere-rovers-game-3344022.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Tranmere Rovers game</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Tranmere Rovers game</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Tranmere Rovers game</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Still was frustated with Saturday's result but happy with the team performance. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["I thought that the first half was even with not much in it and after the first five-six minutes we really got into our stride."
<br  /><br  />
"They had a man sent off which gives us the advantage, which I thought we used and we moved the ball really, really well, it was just the final shot, pass or cross that was not really there or us on Saturday, Assombalonga came on and hit the bar as well, but I am pleased with how we played."
<br  /><br  />
"People maybe would look at how many games we have played this year against top teams, I think we have played more big teams that people think, we beat Dover and Lincoln here at home and we played very well here against Tranmere, we just couldn't get the goal we needed."
<br  /><br  />
"When teams come here, it is almost a privilege that teams come here and feel like they have to up their game, and when I look at our team and out attacking players we are still learning and they will learn from the game against Tranmere."
<br  /><br  />
"I think we created enough chances to get the win but their goalkeeper played well and that’s football but I am satisfied with our overall performance, I am really happy with what we are doing."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/Buy">here</a>.</strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johnstilltranmere-86292-3343986_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johnstilltranmere-169292-3343987_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-03 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>