<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3346436-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-eastleigh-3346436.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: Eastleigh</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: Eastleigh</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: Eastleigh</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of Travelling to the Silverlake Stadium for the Daggers’ fixture against Eastleigh, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<strong >DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong><br  />
Leave the M27 at Junction 5 and taken the Stoneham Lane exit towards Eastleigh. From here, you will pass the back of the stadium on your left hand side. Continue to the end of the road and at the roundabout, go back on yourself to head back towards the motorway. Just as you pass the Concorde Club on your left, turn right into Stoneham Lane. The entrance to Silverlake Stadium is around the bend on the left. There is a reasonable sized carpark at the ground with a capacity to hold 500 vehicles which is free to use.
<br  /><br  /><strong >BY TRAIN:</strong><br  />
Eastleigh is served by trains from Southampton Airport Parkway which is accessible directly from London Waterloo. The journey takes just over an hour and is priced at £16 for an adult return ticket without a railcard. Services run four to five times every hour. From Airport Parkway, turn right out of the station and cross to the other side of the road. Turn left at the sign advertising the Lakeside Miniature Railway and follow the footpath through the Lakeside Country Park. When you come out of the park, cross over and proceed down Stoneham Lane where you will eventually reach the ground entrance on your left.
<br  /><br  /><strong >SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong><br  />
The supporters club will be running a coach to this fixture at a cost of £18 for members and £23 for non-members. It will depart Victoria Road at 11am and will not be making a service stop en-route. To book please call the Supporters Club Travel Hotline on: 07989901686.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-eastleigh-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3345594.aspx" >here</a><br  /><br  />
Away guide for Saturday's game <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-eastleigh-v-dagenham-redbridge-3350004.aspx" >here</a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-04 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home</Tags>
</News>