<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3346784-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-torquay-1-0-daggers-3346784.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>MATCH REPORT: Torquay United 1-0 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>MATCH REPORT: Torquay United 1-0 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>MATCH REPORT: Torquay United 1-0 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge saw their five-game unbeaten run come to an end with a 1-0 loss away to Torquay United in the National League.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1" >Daggers made two changes for the trip to Plainmoor, with Luke Howell replacing Andre Boucaud and Craig Robson coming in for Josh Staunton.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >After early chances for Oliver Hawkins and Fejiri Okenabirhie, the Essex club had skipper Scott Doe sent off for a foul in the 15<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >The centre-back was judged to have pulled down Torquay’s Dan Sparkes as the last man, leaving referee Antony Coggins with little option but to send Doe off.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Eight minutes later, the Gulls took the lead when Jamie Reid fired in for the hosts to make the Victoria Road side’s task a lot harder.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Daggers almost equalised in the 35<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute from a corner, but were thwarted by a combination of Torquay midfield Damon Lathrope and keeper Brendan Moore.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >However, the visitors could not find a goal and headed into the break behind with the score 1-0.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Neither side could fashion a clear cut chance in the opening exchanges of the second half, though Hawkins narrowly headed over in the 57<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Substitute Chris Assombalonga almost levelled for Daggers in the final minute of stoppage time, but headed a Matt Robinson cross over the bar.</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Daggers will hope to rebound swiftly when they make the trip to the Silverlake Stadium to face Eastleigh on Saturday.</p><p class="p1" ><br />
Torquay: Moore; Ward, Galifuoco, McGinty, Rower-Turner; Richards, Lathrope, Young, Sparkes (Chaney 54); Blissett, Reid (Williams 73)</p><p class="p1" >Subs: Chamberlain, Nicholson</p><p class="p1" >Daggers: Justham; Widdowson, Doe, Robson, Raymond; Robinson, Howell (Ling 75); Maguire-Drew (Staunton 19), Whitely, Okenabirhie (Assombalonga 69); Hawkins</p><p class="p1" >Subs: Cousins, Donnellan</p><p class="p1" >Attendance: 1,638 (including 70 Daggers fans)</p><p class="p2" ><br /></p><p class="p1" >Referee: Antony Coggins</p>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-04 21:55:51 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>