<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3350004-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-eastleigh-v-dagenham-redbridge-3350004.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Eastleigh v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Eastleigh v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Eastleigh v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Dagger's National League away tie at Eastleigh this Saturday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The home of Eastleigh since 1957, Silverlake Stadium has a capacity of 5,250 making it the fourteenth largest stadium in the National League.
<br  /><br  />
The ground has undergone significant redevelopment in recent years to bring Silverlake up to National League standard; the most recent addition being the Mackoy Community Stand which was opened in 2015. Prior to that, the 2,290 capacity all seater South Stand was opened in 2014, while the East Terrace was purchased from Exeter Chiefs Rugby Club, and has an allowance of 1,250 spectators. The ground is completed by the 370 seater main stand which resembles the archetypal non-league stand dating back from the 1980s.
<br  /><br  /><strong >DAGGERS FANS:</strong><br  />
Daggers fans will be accommodated in the new South Stand behind one of the goals at Silverlake. The stand is completely covered and is all seater, making it feel somewhat like the away stand at Bristol Rovers that Daggers fans will be no doubt familiar with.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
Despite there not being many food outlets close to Eastleigh’s stadium, if you head into Eastleigh Town Centre or alight at Eastleigh Station, you have plenty of fast food and restaurant options along Blenheim Road and Southampton Road. The nearby country park also has a café facility and serves a recommended brunch meal. Pubs near Eastleigh Station include the JD Wetherspoon ‘Wagon Wheel’ and ‘The Station’, which serves food and shows live sports. Closer to the ground, ‘The Globe Bar and Kitchen’ is seconds from Southampton Parkway, while the Cricketers on Chestnut Avenue serves food and ale. Eastleigh’s clubhouse, the Spitfire, also admits away supporters, as does the Concorde Club on Stoneham Lane. Alcohol is not available inside the stadium.
<br  /><br  />
Click <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-eastleigh-3346436.aspx" >here</a> to view our away travel guide
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-06 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>