<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3351098-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/fejiri-okenabirhie-eastleigh-preview-3351098.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Fejiri Okenabirhie Eastleigh Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Fejiri Okenabirhie Eastleigh Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Fejiri Okenabirhie Eastleigh Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Okenabirhie is disapointed with Tuesday's results but is determined to get back to winning ways</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["We are obviously disappointed with the loss, even though we did have 10 men for a lot of the game, I thought we were the better team and we dominated, we had them playing on the counter attack even though they had 11 men. Now we have just got to look to Saturday and put it right."
<br  /><br  />
"Boucaud is a big part of what we do as a team, he’s an experienced player and has seen a lot more so he can guide us younger players through the game."
<br  />
 
<br  />
"Although I don’t think can pin our defeats just on the absence of Boucaud, it’s a different circumstance with each game Tuesday I think if it stayed 11 men we definitely would of got something from the game. There’s going to the times when people are missing from the team due to injury or suspension so we have to be able to adapt to those things."
<br  />
 
<br  />
"We don’t fear any team we play against, we are a match for anyone in this league, we will just go there do what we do and try and get the win."
<br  /><br  />
"We have to play all the teams, home and away so obviously we are playing a lot of teams that are near the top this month but we are up there too and we need to go out and show them why we are up there."
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/fejiri-86292-3351085_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/fejiri-169292-3351086_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-06 17:31:12 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>