<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3355696-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-john-still-on-the-eastleigh-win-3355696.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Eastleigh win</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Eastleigh win</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Eastleigh win</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Still was happy with the teams performance away to Eastleigh</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >We worked our absolute socks off, we played some great football it was a proper team performance you know what it was a Dagenham performance.</div><div ><br /></div><div >So that was extra pleasing we didn’t sit back and soak up pressure for 90 minutes we tried to attack, move the ball and we played with some great energy and enthusiasm. Everyone worked for the team, when we needed a bit of quality from defending we narrowed the pitch up, it was a first class performance.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Okenabirhie played on Tuesday, we were down to 10 men and he’s been playing a lot games, so I thought he needed a rest today and that’ll freshen him up, its nothing against what he’s done he’s been brilliant.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With Scott Doe being missing we’ve had to change the back four around a bit with the full backs, Sam Ling was brought in although he’s not 100% ready yet but I couldn’t asked for any more today.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In training Whitely scores from some unbelievable angles, he’s a very talented kid so I don’t blame him for taking shots.</div><div ><br /></div><div >I had Matt Robinson with me at Luton and he was part of a conference winning side so he knows what it takes, I gave Matt a three year contract he was only young and I said to him at the time you might not be ready quite yet but in 3 years' time you’re going to be a player, I couldn’t believe we got him I think he is just going to get better and better I really do.</div><div ><br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jstill-86292-3348705_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jstill-169292-3348706_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-10 12:33:30 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>