<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3355128-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Academy: Dagenham and Redridge 3 - 2 Northampton Town</headline>
  <page_title>Academy: Dagenham and Redridge 3 - 2 Northampton Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy: Dagenham and Redridge 3 - 2 Northampton Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Strikes from Joe White and Dylan Florence guided the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s to a deserved 3-2 victory as the Londoners hosted  Northampton Town. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The away number nine headed the Cobblers in front twenty minutes in, but the Daggers equalised from Joe White’s close-range finish, before the in-form striker gave the hosts the lead with a fierce free-kick.
<br  /><br  />
The sides were back on level terms when the Cobblers number ten bundled in from the number nine’s driven cross, but excellent work from Blue Gallagher allowed Dylan Florence to roll in the winner.
<br  /><br  />
Although it was not their usual stylish victories, the Daggers showed tremendous spirit to bounce back from their last two league results, working tirelessly to overcome their stubborn opposition in an intense ninety minutes of football.
<br  /><br  />
Their midweek cup result will undoubtedly have restored their confidence having shone in a 4-1 thrashing of Cheshunt at the Chigwell Construction Stadium as the east London side prolonged their cup run on Thursday, one of four fixtures in the space of a week.
<br  /><br  />
Having featured so many times within the past seven days, the Daggers may easily have succumbed to fatigue, but their energy and commitment prevailed over any signs of burnout, and were the vital ingredients for such a commendable display.
<br  /><br  />
With two in-form strikers leading the line as part of a front three, the hosts sought to regularly thread balls through from midfield, knowing that any half-chances created would be gleefully dispatched by either Dylan Florence or Joe White.
<br  /><br  />
And it nearly paid off just six minutes in, as a pass from midfield deflected off an away defender into the path of White, whose effort from close range was blocked by the away stopper.
<br  /><br  />
At the other end, the Daggers could just as easily have been behind after switching off during a worked Cobblers corner, but much to the hosts relief, an away man clipped over from six yards.
<br  /><br  />
It was a warning sign that unfortunately bypassed the Daggers, resulting in the visitors taking the lead moments later, with the Cobblers number nine heading in after the number eleven ran down the line and crossed for the striker.
<br  /><br  />
However, the hosts were almost level less than a minute later, as Scott Mitchell’s headed pass from a free-kick landed at the feet of Mustaphe Ali, whose shot deflected out for a corner that nearly resulted in Florence equalising, but the forward struggled to control the travelling ball.
<br  /><br  />
Goalkeeper Louie Chapman then produced a splendid save from point-blank range to keep the scoreline even - the stopper spread himself well to block the away number ten’s close-range effort from a left-wing cross as the Daggers occasionally treaded the line.
<br  /><br  />
But Joe White ensured the next goal fell the way of the hosts as the forward precisely slotted a five-yard equaliser in from a right-wing cross as the hosts levelled on the stroke of half-time.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers could well have been ahead by the interval after Dylan Florence collected from Jordy Mongoy ahead of turning and thumping a low shot just wide with the Londoners ending the half positively.
<br  /><br  />
The second period saw the Daggers take more control of the encounter, looking a revitalised and refreshed side as they fought with more intensity and determination in their quest for another victory.
<br  /><br  />
Again, Dylan Florence was agonisingly close with a fizzing effort that was palmed to safety by the away stopper, and Joe White was narrowly beaten to the rebound by a Cobblers defender.
<br  /><br  />
Having just escaped following a sudden infliction of Cobblers pressure that saw both Louie Chapman and the left upright come to their aid, the Daggers were ahead when Joe White powered a ferocious free-kick into the roof of the Northampton Town net after a Jordy Mongoy shot had been handled on the edge of the area.
<br  /><br  />
But celebrations were cut short as the Cobblers drew level within minutes, with the away number ten diverting the number nine’s driven cross into the far corner of Louie Chapman’s goal.
<br  /><br  />
With over twenty minutes left to play, there was more than enough time for the Daggers to unearth a much-deserved winner, and it was the persistence and tenacity of substitute Blue Gallagher that unlocked the opportunity.
<br  /><br  />
The midfielder superbly forced his way down the right and picked out Dylan Florence in the middle, who had the simple task of rolling underneath the away stopper from twelve yards as the Daggers emerged from the tie victorious.
<br  /><br  />
Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the performance:
<br  /><br  />
“We did the fundamentals well, we showed a winning mentality, although we were not at our best technically, they still had enough quality to win today, and to feel that way is a good feeling”, said Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“In the first half we could have retained the ball better and kept it in the attacking third more, but we improved on that in the second half and I thought we were largely dominant throughout”, the Headcoach insisted.
<br  /><br  />
Line-up:
<br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 13. Louie Chapman, 2. Abubakkarr Soloku, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Hani Berchiche, 5. Kieran Walker-Browne, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. Ali Mustaphe, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Joe White, 10. Jordy Mongoy, 11. Dylan Florence, 1. Joe Carter, 14. Blue Gallagher, 15. David Agboola
<br  /><br  />
Goalscorers:
<br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Joe White 41’ + 65’, Dylan Florence 71’
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-10 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Home</Tags>
</News>