<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3357604-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-craig-robson-on-the-win-away-at-eastleigh-3357604.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: Craig Robson on the win away at Eastleigh</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: Craig Robson on the win away at Eastleigh</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: Craig Robson on the win away at Eastleigh</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Craig Robson was happy with how him and his team played today and is looking forward to the Emirates FA Cup fixture</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[It was a team performance today, everyone was to a man absolutely fantastic. Personally I think I had a good game made some good blocks, really I’m just happy to get three points that’s the main thing and all I care about.
<br  /><br  />
I’ve took on advice from John Still as at my last club I used to be very open and take a lot more risks but at this level you can’t take those risks so you have to know at all time when to play it long and analyse the game.
<br  /><br  />
Hawkins is a massive asset for us, if he stays fit we’ve got a great chance of gaining promotion. With him being 6ft 6 and the way he is in the box he’s such a massive threat for us.
<br  /><br  />
My expectations at the start of the season was to get promoted and they haven’t changed, we’re not here to float around mid-table we’re here to win it. Whether we do that’s a different story but I believe we can especially with how we have been playing, in both parts of the game we’re good going forward and we’ve been good defensively.
<br  /><br  />
Missing Scott Doe is a massive blow, he’s a captain, and he’s a leader and is very good vocally for us. Although it gave me and Josh Staunton an opportunity to show our skill and quality, we had no choice today everyone had to talk to each other as it was a very tough game.
<br  /><br  />
I’m looking forward to the FA cup, getting through the rounds and reaching them big stages is what everyone wants, but we can’t get ahead of ourselves we need to take every game as they come and hopefully we can do really well.     
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/robson-86292-3357597_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/robson-169292-3357599_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-11 14:35:44 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>