<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3358590-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/now-available-in-the-club-shop-rejected-by-peter-richardson-3358590.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Now Available in the Club Shop: Rejected by Peter Richardson</headline>
  <page_title>Now Available in the Club Shop: Rejected by Peter Richardson</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Now Available in the Club Shop: Rejected by Peter Richardson</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Rejected by Peter Richardson is now available to buy in the club shop</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Rejected by Peter Richardson
<br  /><br  />
You may recall that a year or so ago I published a letter from Peter where he was applying for the managers job, I also revealed my reply and then eventually the fact that Peter was in the process of writing to every football league club with the same request.
<br  /><br  />
He has now published a book containing all these letters, which apart from the first few are all different,  along with replies, where he got one. I have now read most of the book, and I must say that I find it very funny, several times I have actually laughed out loud, in fact so much so that my wife is urging me to finish the book so that she can read it.
<br  /><br  />
I have bought and paid for 50 copies of this book and donated 48 of them to the club shop to sell ( the other 2 are my sons Christmas presents, I hope they don't read this and spoil the surprise) The retail price shown on the book is £7.99 each, we are offering them at a discounted price of £6.99 each, anyone wishing to buy 2 copies or more as presents can have them for £6.00 each. The total proceeds from the sale of these books will stay in the club.
<br  /><br  />
Peter has informed me that he is being interviewed on Talk Sport on 27th October, between 1.30 - 2.00pm and he has promised to mention Dagenham and Redbridge, I think that's because I was the only one to offer him a job, whoops that's a spoiler.
<br  /><br  />
If you have a good sense of humour, I believe you will enjoy reading this book.
<br  /><br  />
Regards Dave Bennett
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/book-86292-3358578_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/book-169292-3358577_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-12 12:40:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>