<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3358229-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-essex-senior-cup-dagenham-redbridge-3-0-southend-3358229.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report Essex Senior Cup: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-0 Southend</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report Essex Senior Cup: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-0 Southend</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report Essex Senior Cup: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-0 Southend</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are through to round four of the Essex Senior Cup after beating Southend 3-0 at home. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Darren Currie took charge of the Essex Senior Cup tie and the Daggers had early control of the game. 
<div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers took the lead in the 35 minute through a header across the goalkeeper from young striker Joe White. </div><div ><br /></div><div >A brilliant ball in midfield was played by Tyrique Hyde to Chris Assombalonga on the right hand side, and the cross from Assombalonga was the perfect delivery for White to get the opening goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers went into half time 1-0 up and in control of the game, and the Daggers got their second goal of the game 12 minutes from time after a finish from Assombalonga. </div><div ><br /></div><div >More good play by Tyrique Hyde in winning the ball back in midfield and driving passed a defender in the box to set up Chris Assombalonga to finish into the corner of the net to give the Daggers a two goal lead. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Dagenham got their third of the game just before full time after another goal from striker Joe White to complete the win and the Daggers move into the next round of the Essex Senior Cup. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers Line Up: Cousins, Ling, Gordon, Mitchell, Shepherd, Mongoy, Hyde, Assombalonga, Howell, Donnellan, White. </div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-12 10:10:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>