<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3360780-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/john-gowens-injury-update-interview-3360780.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>John Gowens: Injury Update Interview</headline>
  <page_title>John Gowens: Injury Update Interview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>John Gowens: Injury Update Interview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Gowens discusses how the players are coping with injuries and our up and coming Emirates FA Cup Fixture</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Howell’s fitness is going well he played in the Essex Senior cup on Tuesday, obviously the more games he plays the better. The reason for this is because Luke missed pre-season and pre-season is a massive thing for footballers and what you normally find is people who miss that always struggle fitness wise. So what we are trying to do now is get as many 90 minutes under his belt as possible but obviously sensibly we don’t want him to breakdown.
<br  /><br  />
Curtley Williams is doing okay, he is now moved on to his rehab resistance work. Next week he is going to St. Georges because they are in conjunction with the PFA to run a scheme to help injured players and it’s good sometimes to have a break away from our environment and go to a different environment, he’ll be there a week to try push on with his fitness work again. When he comes back we’ll see where he is at, but at the moment he making very good progress, his knee is holding up with the work we are asking to do.
<br  /><br  />
The injury with Paul Benson is a strange one, when he played in the game against the Southend Reserves he came off the centre half and all of a sudden grabbed his side. We’ve looked at him it does seem to be an intercostal muscle which is down the bottom of your stomach he is getting better. We have had it scanned and we are waiting on results from that just to see if there is anything more than that; hopefully there is not. He may be away from training a week or so depending on what these scans say, he’s improving all the time and able to do more and more.
<br  />
 
<br  />
We do bring in a lot of players from the non-league clubs so we do have to monitor their fitness and try and integrate them into full time training, while not pushing them to hard as their bodies are not used to full time training. In lots of cases we have had it in the past where players have had strain and injuries because of that.
<br  /><br  />
Obviously we are heavy favourites to beat Wealdstone but that doesn’t mean anything, with all the usual clichés coming out like it’s the FA Cup the underdogs beating the big teams and whatever. I try not to make predictions I’ve been in the game to long and when you do make predictions they end up coming back to bite you. Wealdstone will turn up and try as hard as they can to beat us so we’ve just got to match that work rate if we do I can’t see there being any problems but this is football anything is possible.
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div><br  /><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johngowens86292-3360777_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johngowens169292-3360779_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-13 16:50:33 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,First Team,Home,Injury,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>