<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3362193-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/corey-whitley-on-his-recent-form-3362193.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Corey Whitley on His Recent Form</headline>
  <page_title>Corey Whitley on his recent form</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Corey Whitley on his recent form</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Ahead of the Emirates FA Cup Fixture against Wealdstone Corey Whitley discusses his recent form and how his teammates have helped him</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Eastleigh was a tough game, they had a very good team and I would say physically they were much stronger than us. I think that is the most I have defended from any game it really tested my work rate. I always thought we was going to get a good chance to score and that opportunity fell to me, I hit it low and it went in.
<br  /><br  />
It’s a big relief I’m scoring now, as I am used to scoring and obviously at the start when I joined I hadn’t scored for four games in a row but now the goals are starting to come in so I’m happy with that.
<br  /><br  />
Our strike force is unbelievable, I haven’t seen anything like it before, with Jordan Maguire-Drew coming in from the right and Fejiri Okenabirhie coming in from the left and Hawkins as a target man there is just so much variation to our attack. We all work together very well, we know what each other are going to do; we are a very good attacking team.
<br  /><br  />
Two weeks ago I was just getting used to full time training, before that my legs would be in bits after training. But now my recovery is much better and I’m used to training every day and I’m getting stronger every day.
<br  />
     
<br  />
I'm excited for our FA Cup fixture this Saturday, There’s nothing better than the FA Cup, hopefully we can go far. 
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/corey-86292-3362188_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/corey-169292-3362189_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-14 15:30:30 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>