<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3363062-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-daggers-0-0-wealdstone-3363062.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-1 Wealdstone FC</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-1 Wealdstone FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 3-1 Wealdstone FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers progress into the first round proper of the Emirates FA Cup after defeating Wealdstone FC 3-1</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1" >Goals from Fejiri Okenabirhie, Oliver Hawkins and Jordan Maguire-Drew took the Daggers through to the first round proper of the FA Cup.</p><p class="p1" >They achieved it without getting anywhere near top form. So to pull off a win even though they were below their best is encouraging.</p><p class="p1" >The Daggers made hard work of seeing off opponents who play at lower level.</p><p class="p1" >They were in second gear for the first half, allowing Wealdstone to stay in the game.</p><p class="p1" >In fact the visitors had enough chances to have caused an  upset with former Dagger Danny  Green passing up a couple of fine chances.</p><p class="p1" >The Daggers were not as sharp as usual and their use of the ball was not quick enough.</p><p class="p1" >But they went ahead in the 31st minute when man of the match Hawkins did well to win the ball and sent Okenabirhie racing through to finish with a shot across the keeper and inside the far post.</p><p class="p1" >The Stones drew level as the first half went into injury time when a shot from Matthew Whichelow took wicked deflection and looped over the stranded Mark Cousins.</p><p class="p1" >There was more about the Daggers in the second half and they regained the lead in the 50th minute - Hawkins heading through from close range  after the Stones failed to clear a free kick from Maguire-Drew.</p><p class="p1" >And the kid on loan from Brighton finished the scoring 15 minutes from time when he cut in from the right and chipped the ball in.</p><p class="p1" >The win was a  financial boost for the club, who hope for a decent draw to keep the momentum going.</p>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-15 22:50:04 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>