<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3364939-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-3364939.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy: Leyton Orient 2 - 1 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy: Leyton Orient 2 - 1 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy: Leyton Orient 2 - 1 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18's fell to a defeat against Leyton Orient on Saturday.  </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >A sweet strike by Dylan Florence was rendered insufficient as the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s succumbed to 2-1 defeat at the hands of the Leyton Orient Academy in an enthralling London derby.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Florence added to his impressive tally of goals this season with a spectacular effort from range to reduce to deposit after efforts from the home number ten and six saw the O’s take a 2-0 lead before the hour mark.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The striker, who also saw a powerful first-half drive from eighteen yards tipped over by the home stopper, was then presented with the best opportunity to equalise fifteen minutes from time but miskicked from Abubakkarr Soloku’s mid-height cross with the goal gaping, leaving the O’s breathing a sigh of relief following some poor defending.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It was an encounter that featured both exciting and stale moments as the Daggers sought to re-establish another winning run by destabilising Leyton Orient’s quest to remain top of the league table.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Throughout the contest, the Daggers were the more ambitious of the sides as both fought for control of the tie, but struggled to penetrate defences often enough, and a lack of clear-cut chances proved a direct result.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The physical and aerial presence of a tall and strong O’s side may have given the hosts a slight advantage, but the Daggers were determined to counteract their rivals’ physicality with skill and panache.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Liam Gordon and trialist Jimmy Burston both contributed to a fair few skilful displays from the away side with exhibitions of good footwork that, on two occasions, could have resulted in the visitors returning to Dagenham with something in the bag.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Forty minutes in, the former worked his way into a good crossing position following a mazy run that the O’s struggled to bring to a halt, but nothing could be made of the wingback’s square ball, allowing  the hosts escaping unharmed.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Subsequently, midfielder Burston turned defence into attack for the Daggers with a superb piece of skill before releasing Soloku with a sensational ball, but the right-back’s pass across the face of goal could not be kept alive as the Daggers made a positive start to the second half.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Amidst their pursuits forward, Micah Hyde’s youngsters were given regular reminders throughout the contest not to abandon their defensive duties having been punished for an early lapse in concentration when the home number ten stroked into the far corner after controlling an airborne ball, and a superb save from Louie Chapman ensured a far-post header didn’t double the hosts’ lead.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The O’s number ten was then denied a brace courtesy of a heroic sliding challenge from Scott Mitchell that prevented the goalscorer getting his shot away from an inviting position, and Kieran Walker-Browne did well to block a powerfully-struck follow-up, keeping the score at 1-0 until the O’s number six rolled a twenty-yard free-kick under the wall, beating Joe Carter at his near post 53 minutes in. </div><div ><br /></div><div >To their credit, the Daggers emitted no signs of surrender following the Os’ second, and Dylan Florence helped set up a tense finale for the hosts when the frontman collected in midfield before turning and finding the bottom corner with an impeccable 25-yard strike as hopes of a comeback were on for the Daggers.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Unfortunately for the visiting side, who applied great pressure to a more compact O’s backline in search of a much-craved equaliser, the Daggers were left frustrated in their efforts to draw level as Leyton Orient saw off the encounter. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the tie:</div><div ><br /></div><div >“I don’t think they deserved to lose the game, I saw a lot of independent learning and development in our players as a team and I think if there was better decision making at certain times we would have done better, but they did well today again”, said Hyde.</div><div ><br /></div><div >“I’m happy that we showed resilience and quality, but obviously they are not happy we didn’t win the game because I thought we did enough to do so, we were the more creative, especially in the second half, this performance won't hamper their confidence , but enhance it and also their game understanding as we look forward to our next outing”, the U18s coach revealed.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Line-up:</div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 13. Louie Chapman, 2. David Agboola, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Jimmy Burston, 5. Kieran Walker-Browne, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. Mustaphe Ali, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Joe White, 10. Jordy Mongoy, 11. Dylan Florence, 1. Joe Carter, 14. Blue Gallagher, 15. Abubakkarr Soloku, 16. Jack Lee</div><div ><br /></div><div >Goalscorers:</div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Dylan Florence 66’</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-17 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Home</Tags>
</News>