<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3364942-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/darren-currie-post-wealdstone-fc-3364942.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Darren Currie Post Wealdstone FC</headline>
  <page_title>Darren Currie Post Wealdstone FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Darren Currie Post Wealdstone FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Darren Currie gives credit to Wealdstone and comments on the teams performance. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1" >"In the first half I think we were below the standards of what we set, but you have got to give credit to Wealdstone, they’ve come here and they have had a go."</p><p class="p1" >"There’s a time when you’re a favourite and there is a time when you are an underdog. Wealdstone definitely caused us some problems in the first half there is no doubt about that. We just reminded the boys at half time of the quality they have been showing of late and pretty much most of the season, bar one or two blips and they responded to what is being asked of them again and in the second half our quality shone through and we were much better in the second half which was pleasing."</p><p class="p1" >"Corey Whitley is contributing to what we are doing, granted he may not be getting as many goals as he may like to, but it’s not for the lack of effort he’s always trying and as we saw he got the all-important goal away at Eastleigh."</p><p class="p1" >"The front four are a real handful, but not just the forwards all over the pitch we are solid and strong. It’s all about consistency and we didn’t quite have that in the first half but we certainly brought it back into our game in the second half."
<br /></p><p class="p1" >"Consistency is all part of the game, we need to keep winning to get in the hat for the next round, although consistency is what we are going to need over the full season to reach our targets and we have displayed that in the first quarter of the season."</p><p class="p1" >"We’ve got a week leading into the Macclesfield game so we can structure the week and get them prepared, with no mid-week game it allows us to get prepared and give the boys a little rest as well. We are confident as we have been all season and we’ll be fully prepared for Macclesfield next Saturday."</p><p class="p1" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/darrencurrie-86292-3323404_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/darrencurrie-169292-3323405_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-17 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>