<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3369871-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/tickets-forest-green-rovers-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3369871.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Tickets: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Tickets: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Tickets: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Ticket information for the Daggers' trip to the New Lawn Stadium on Saturday 29th September, 3:00pm KO.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >For this game Forest Green Rovers will be opening the North Stand (standing) for away supporters, which can hold up to 744 supporters. For those supporters that prefer to sit or could struggle to stand for the whole game, there are ONLY 40 seats available to purchase – please note that you will be located in a segregated Block of our Main Stand, which is adjacent to the North Stand.</div><div > </div><div ><strong>Please note that seating tickets are strictly limited and are expected to sell out: as such if you would like or need a seat for this game, please buy your ticket in advance. Once these tickets are sold out, there will be no more available.</strong></div><div ><br /></div><div >All away supporters (standing and seating) will gain access to the stadium via the North Stand turnstiles (7&amp;8) and will be using the North Stand facilities (catering, toilets). This means that any away supporters with a seating ticket, will need to walk back into the North stand to use the facilities.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>How to Buy Your Tickets:</strong></div><div >We recommend supporters purchase their tickets in advance, for convenience and to save money too. Tickets can be downloaded to your smart phone, be posted out to you or simply collected on the day from our Ticket Office (right in front of the stadium as you arrive). Tickets will be available to purchase on the day but to save time, to avoid the queues and to save money, we recommend that all supporters purchase their tickets in advance by: </div><div >- Via our website online (link) </div><div >- Over the Phone: via Reception (01453 834 860), from 9am to 3pm, Monday to Friday.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Ticket Prices:</strong></div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Standing:</strong></div><div >Adults - £15.00 (£16.00 on the day)</div><div >Senior (65+) - £11.00 (£12.00 on the day)</div><div >Young Adult (16-21) - £7.00 (£7.50 on the day)</div><div >Junior (Under 16) - £4.00 (£4.50 on the day)</div><div >Kids (Under 11) - FREE (with an adult ticket)</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Seating:</strong></div><div >Adults - £17.00 (£18.00 on the day)</div><div >Senior (65+) - £13.00 (£14.00 on the day)</div><div >Young Adult (16-21) - £9.00 (£9.50 on the day)</div><div >Junior (Under 16) - £6.00 (£6.50 on the day)</div><div >Kids (Under 11) - FREE (with an adult ticket)</div><div ><br /></div><div ><div><strong>Wheelchair/Disabled Information:</strong></div><div>We have a limited number of wheelchair accessible seating in our main East stand and limited numbers of disabled parking for both home and away supporters. These are only booked over the phone via the FGR Reception (01453 834 860). Please note that these are sold out for most games, so we recommend all supporters book in advance to avoid disappointment.</div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/forestgreenroversticketnews-86292-3369860_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/forestgreenroversticketnews-169292-3369864_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-18 15:10:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Tickets</Tags>
</News>