<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3372800-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/club-news-statement-from-safety-officer-3372800.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Club News: Statement From Safety Officer</headline>
  <page_title>Club News: Statement From Safety Officer</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Club News: Statement From Safety Officer</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Statement from our safety officer regarding behaviour from fans at recent games. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks I have been approached by many people connected with the club, from the Manager, directors, supporters club and others, about the behaviour of a small number of our own fans at both home and away matches. There is concern that some may be overstepping the mark with their comments and actions, and thus doing harm to our reputation as one of the most friendly and well-behaved clubs in the country. It is clear from the conversations, comments on various forums and reports from the police that I am not alone in my concerns.
<br  /><br  />
This is not to say that our fans are worse than those they encounter. But there have been occasions at games at Bromley, Eastleigh and at home against Wealdstone and Tranmere where some of the behaviour from Daggers towards other fans has been less than acceptable, but has been put by those involved under the general heading of “banter”.
<br  /><br  />
It is not possible to draw up a hard and fast rule about what is and isn’t acceptable, but in today’s society what can never be considered right is songs about sexuality, disability, (both of which have been reported to me), just the same as I’m sure everyone would understand that racist songs (which isn’t something that’s happening) are not allowed. It doesn’t matter whether the comments or songs are directed at an individual present or otherwise. They’re just not right.
<br  /><br  />
The same can be said about language. Football crowds are naturally loud and noisy, full of enthusiastic shouting, and a good deal of swearing. Again, there isn’t a list of acceptable or unacceptable swear words, although the stewarding team will always have a word if they hear the word c*** is the word shouted.
<br  /><br  />
The way I have always been taught to assess these things is to apply the reasonable man test.  Imagine you’re on the top floor of the Clapham Omnibus (that show’s my age). If the behaviour is something that a reasonable man would find wrong, then it probably is wrong, so don’t do it.
<br  /><br  />
I have spoken to some of the fans that travel home and away, and there seems to be an eagerness to sort things out within the fan group, which is great. But one or two people can’t do it on their own. They need those who find themselves singing or shouting something they know isn’t right, to take a deep breath and think of something more imaginative to shout. Focus their attention on things that encourage the players, things that emphasise what a great club Dagenham &amp; Redbridge is, and don't cause others to question our reputation.
<br  /><br  />
It is my sincere wish that such self-monitoring will stop the current trend, and again I repeat what I said at the beginning, there is no suggestion that our fans are any worse than others. The last thing I want to end up doing is having to use ground regulations, ejections and bans as a method of dealing with things. But it should always be borne in mind that some of what has been reported is not only a breach of the regulations that apply to entry to any ground, but in some cases is also a breach of criminal law, so the unacceptable stuff must stop.
<br  /><br  />
This season we’re all able to watch some exciting football on the pitch. Soak it up, be enthusiastic and get behind your team. Like Mike says before every game “Make some noise for the boys and enjoy the match”.
<br  /><br  />
Tony Payne
<br  />
Safety Officer
<br  /><br  />
If anyone wishes to raise any issues regarding this entry on the website / forum please feel free to contact me direct on the email address safety@daggers.co.uk
<br  /><br  />
To see the ground regulations at the Chigwell Construction Stadium click <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/ground-regulations-298654.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/newgen86292-3115254_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/newgen169292-3115256_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-19 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>