<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3373607-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/fa-youth-cup-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-vs.-braintree-town-3373607.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>FA Youth Cup Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge vs. Braintree Town</headline>
  <page_title>FA Youth Cup Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge vs. Braintree Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>FA Youth Cup Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge vs. Braintree Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Dagger’s progressed into the first round proper of the FA Youth Cup with an extra time victory over Braintree Town. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The home side opened the scoring in the seventeenth minute with a well taken goal but the Daggers pressed hard for the equaliser. Chances were created by the young Daggers but the Braintree custodian was in fine form when called upon.
<br  /><br  />
Five minutes into the second period the Daggers got their reward when Scott Mitchell fired home at the back post from a corner. Jordy Mongoy saw an effort crash against the crossbar but from the resulting clearance the home side retook the lead when goalkeeper Carter blocked the initial effort but was unable to keep the follow-up out.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers threw everything into attack to get an equaliser and in the ninety-second minute a throw in saw the crossbar rattled again. The ball broke to the left and Jordy Mongoy whipped in a cross that caught a Braintree defender on the side and flew into the net to send the game into extra time.
<br  /><br  />
The home side could have taken the lead early on into the additional period when a striker found himself alone in the penalty area from a cross but fired over the beat with only Carter to beat. At the other end Tyrique Hyde saw his effort hit the woodwork for the third time in the match.
<br  /><br  />
The turning point was on 109 minutes when a Daggers goal bound shot was saved with his hands on the line by the Braintree number four who was duly dismissed. Joe White made no mistake from the resulting spot kick to put the Daggers ahead for the first time.
<br  /><br  />
Three minutes later and substitute Mustapha slotted the ball past the home keeper to make the game safe for the visitors and progress into the next round with a 4-2 scoreline.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers</strong><strong >:</strong> Carter, Arbour, Gordon, Bonds, Walker-Brown, Mitchell, Gordon, Hyde, white, Mongoy, Florence, Burston. <strong >Subs</strong><strong >:</strong> Chapman, Lee
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/fayouthcup86292-2046342_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/fayouthcup169292-2046343_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-20 11:28:57 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Away Fixture,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>