<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3374356-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/john-gowens-macclesfield-preview-3374356.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>John Gowens: Macclesfield Preview</headline>
  <page_title>John Gowens: Macclesfield Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>John Gowens: Macclesfield Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Gowens discusses the Emirates FA Cup draw and how the players are developing</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Yes we’ve got FC Halifax Town in the draw but I don’t take anything from the draw, it’s about how we approach the game, if we approach it the way we have been in our league games with all the attributes we have been showing then it shouldn’t be a problem. But you can never count on the FA Cup it’s very unpredictable.
<br  /><br  />
Tyrique Hyde has progressed very well, the jump from academy football to professional can be quite daunting for some players and they struggle physically more than anything. Hyde has that physical attribute so he has been able to cope well with the switch. You do have to be careful as you have still got to remember his age as he’s still developing which we are keeping an eye on. John Still knows he’s developing well and has experience of managing these younger players, so he’s giving him the game time where he feels is appropriate for him to play.
<br  /><br  />
Ahead of the three hard fixtures, we don’t let any of these harder games influence what we do. We carry on with the plan we’ve been implementing which has shown to be successful so far. We are playing some hard teams next week so at the end of the week it will be interesting to look back to see where we are and even more importantly where we need to be.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Players like Maguire-Drew and Okenabirhie have been developing well, as staff we do have meeting to discuss how players are developing and we do think they have been progressing better than we thought they would have. More importantly we are really happy with how they mould as a team and how well they are working together. 
<br  /><br  />
Luke Guttridge went back in to training, although he’s had a little minor setback when his hamstring tightened up in training last week so we decided to pull him back out and put him into a stretching programme. He’s back up and running with me, hopefully if he keeps progressing the way he is and everything goes to plan he’ll join back into training next week and we’ll go from there. 
<br  /><br  /><p class="p1" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div><br  /><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/gowens-86292-3374339_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/gowens-169292-3374340_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-20 16:30:55 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,First Team,Home,Injury,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>