<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3376445-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/squad-update-3376445.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Squad Update</headline>
  <page_title>Squad Update</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Squad Update</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Two new signings and one short loan deal announced.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers are delighted to announce to new additions to the current squad ahead of our home fixture against Macclesfield Town Tomorrow, with forward Shomari Barnwell and midfielder Scott Heard putting pen to paper.
<br  /><br  />
Scott Heard, 23 signed from Folkestone Invicta where he was a key member of the teams midfield playing all 17 games so far this season. Originally signing from Ryman League Division One South side Whitstable Town where he started his career. Heard’s impressive form at Whitstable Town earned him trials with the likes of Gillingham, Chesterfield and Maidstone, with Ebbsfleet also wanting to sign him when Steve Brown was in charge.
<br  /><br  />
Addition Number two, Shomari Barnwell signing from Bowers &amp; Pitsea is a 21 year old forward, totalling 15 appearances for his previous club with 5 goals and 1 assist, four of the goals being this season. The 21-year-old was first noticed by the Daggers after playing in the Essex Senior League last season.
<br  /><br  />
Scott and Shomari have joined the Dagger’s signing a contract until June 2018, Heard will wear number 21 and Barnwell number 22.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers can also announce that forward Chris Assombalonga has gone on loan to Ryman South side Whitehawk on a 1 month loan deal.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/signings-86292-3376422_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/signings-169292-3376423_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-21 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,First Team,Home,League,Signing,Team,Transfer</Tags>
</News>