<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3380791-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-dagenham-redbridge-1-4-plymouth-argyle-3380791.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 4 Plymouth Argyle</headline>
  <page_title>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 4 Plymouth Argyle</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 4 Plymouth Argyle</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18's fell to a cup defeat against Plymouth Argyle on Saturday.  </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Plymouth Argyle’s youngsters struck four times at Parkonians as the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s were dumped out of the FA Youth Alliance League Cup.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Pilgrims took the lead from the spot twenty minutes in, doubling their advantage with a clinical effort from the away number ten fifteen minutes later.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Dylan Florence gave the hosts a glimmer of hope late on with a cool finish after the away number nine registered himself on the scoresheet to give the visitors a three-goal cushion.</div><div ><br /></div><div >And the Pilgrims number seven curled in neatly to round off a good day for Argyle at the expense of a tired looking Daggers side.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Having conjured up an impressive winning run in the FA Youth Cup, the Daggers were looking to replicate their rich vein of form in today’s League Cup tie against the Pilgrims in a bid to ignite and maintain a second cup run.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Their FA Cup campaign has been decorated with positives having brought a beautiful brand of passing football along with an array of tremendous results to the tournament, seeing off Portsmouth, Cheshunt, and Braintree Town in convincing victories that oozed goals, excitement, and energy.</div><div ><br /></div><div >But fatigue may have gotten the better of them on this League Cup occasion having played three games within the space of a week.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It took half an hour for the encounter to spring into life, with neither side having tested the resolve of either goalkeeper until Joe Carter was faced with the challenge of stopping a penalty after Kieran Walker-Browne fouled the away number seven, but was sent the wrong way from the spot by the number nine, who tapped coolly into the bottom right corner.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Prior to the spot-kick, the Daggers were largely in control but failed to test the away goalkeeper with the chances that fell to them.</div><div ><br /></div><div >On two occasions, Jordy Mongoy cut in from the left and fired over after the Pilgrims, who themselves blasted two chances hopelessly high and wide in the opening fifteen minutes, left pockets of space vacant on the edge of their box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >A powerful effort from the Daggers wideman did eventually force a taxing save from the away stopper, who regularly frustrated the Daggers having twice denied Joe White from close-range, sparing the blushes of the away number six, whose errors led to both chances having mis-kicked a clearance before failing to head an airborne ball to safety, releasing White.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The striker was also inches away from connecting with a Liam Gordon cross after Mongoy threaded through to the wingback, but to the relief of the Pilgrims, who still only lead by a narrow margin, the linesman flagged for offside.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With the game having gathered momentum following a sluggish opening half hour, the Daggers began to enjoy more of the ball, but were thwarted against the run of play as they found themselves defending against a counter attack that resulted in the away number ten firing powerfully into the far corner after a right-wing cross was midriffed out to the midfielder. </div><div ><br /></div><div >At 2-0 down, the Daggers were looking to their creative talents to restore some hope, but Jordy Mongoy and Mustaphe Ali were frustrated in their attempts to break forward with the ball, and Joe White struggled for service as a result, although a skilful run and cross from Liam Gordon required the attention of the away stopper, who diverted the wingback’s low ball on the stroke of half time.</div><div ><br /></div><div >However, amidst their arrays of pursuits forward, the hosts were dealt another blow an hour in as the Pilgrims number nine finished off the away number seven’s ball to give his side a three goal lead, and a display of good strength from centre-back Jack Lee diffused another potentially harmful Pilgrims breakaway after Florence had nearly ignited a revival when he controlled a cross and fizzed wide of a gaping goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >And the substitute striker did eventually provide some reprieve for the hosts, collecting a free-kick from midfield and stroking high into the net on the turn with fifteen minutes remaining on the clock.</div><div ><br /></div><div >But there was another sting in the tale for the Daggers, who bowed of the league cup on the brink of the full time whistle as the away number seven, who was the creator of most of the Pilgrims attacks, turned goalscorer, curling finely into the top left of goal after twisting and turning his way into the box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on a relatively frustrating tie:</div><div ><br /></div><div >“There was a lack of quality today, the goal we scored was the only real bit of quality we showed, their attitude and application was without question, but we lacked control of the game”, said Hyde.</div><div ><br /></div><div >“We couldn’t really get ourselves going, but they have played a lot of games and they have coped well with it, but today we lacked retention in attacking third in the first half, and the second half we were poor defensively, overall by recent standards we have been a lot better,” stressed the Daggers coach.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Line-up:</strong></div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1. Joe Carter, 2. David Agboola, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Harvey Brown, 5. Kieran Walker-Browne, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. Mustaphe Ali, 8. Jimmy Burston(T),9. Joe White, 10. Blue Gallagher, 11. Jordy Mongoy, 13. Louie Chapman, 14. Jack Lee, 15. Dylan Florence, 16. Deniz Alici(T)</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Goalscorers:</strong></div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Dylan Florence 76’</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-24 11:10:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Home</Tags>
</News>