<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3382036-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/shomari-barnwell-on-signing-for-the-daggers-3382036.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Shomari Barnwell On Signing For The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Shomari Barnwell On Signing For The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Shomari Barnwell On Signing For The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Shomari Barnwell on signing for the Daggers and looking back at his debut on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["It was really good to make my debut, obviously I would have liked to get more minutes and more touches of the ball, but the atmosphere was good and I really enjoyed it apart from the result."
<br  /><br  />
"At the minute I am just taking every day as it comes, I will train hard and hopefully I am able to get my spot in the team."
<br  /><br  />
"It was quite a shock as to hear Dagenham &amp; Redbridge was interested in me but I was really joyful when I heard and it was too good an offer to turn down for me."
<br  /><br  />
"One of the key points that I signed was because of what the manager does with young players by help develop, so that was a main reason that I signed here."
<br  /><br  />
"I would like the chance to show that I can play with this team and contributes with goals and hopefully we can push on for promotion this season."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/shomari-86292-3382040_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/shomari-169292-3382041_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-24 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>