<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3383977-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-interview-corey-whitely-on-the-aldershot-game-3383977.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Interview: Corey Whitely On The Aldershot Game</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Interview: Corey Whitely On The Aldershot Game</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Interview: Corey Whitely On The Aldershot Game</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Corey Whitely on getting the winning goal in yesterday's game against Aldershot. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"We are delighted to get the win yesterday, we have three tough opponents this week with one left to come on Saturday and we want to get the maximum points we can."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"With the game on Saturday against Macclesfield, the late equaliser killed us but we didn’t want that to happen again today, we wanted to get the three points and thankfully we managed to do that."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"I managed to score yesterday in about the 80th minute and I was thinking, let’s just hold on to the win now to keep the three points, as I wanted my goal to be the winner and I’m glad I have been able to get another winner for the team."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"Elliot Justham is a brilliant keeper for us and some of the saves he makes, you just think to yourself - how has he managed to save that, but he is a top keeper which is good for us."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"Playing out on the wing means that I am able to get at the defenders and cut in or get crosses in for Hawkins, as he wins most of the balls that go into him and you can trust that he will be able to hold onto the ball and link up the play and that’s what has been going well for us with him in the team."</div><div ><br /></div><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/whitely-86292-3384489_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/whitely-169292-3384490_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-26 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>