<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3383593-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-daggers-1-0-aldershot-3383593.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 Aldershot Town</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 Aldershot Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 Aldershot Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham and Redbridge came out victorious in what was a competitive encounter against Aldershot Town.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Corey Whitely scored the only goal of the game nine minutes before the full time whistle, earning the three points for the Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
John Still was forced to make changes to his side, as both Fejiri Okenabirhie and Craig Robson suffered injuries in last Saturdays draw to Macclesfield.
<br  /><br  />
Sam Ling came in at right-back, which meant that Frankie Raymond returned to his usual midfield position and Joe Widdowson moved back to the other side of defence.
<br  /><br  />
Josh Staunton started alongside Scott Doe at centre back and Corey Whitely was pushed out to the right of the attack.
<br  /><br  />
The Dagger very nearly got an early goal dead on the fifth minute, Whitely delivered a corner into the box and Staunton was unlucky, after his header clipped the right-angle of the woodwork.
<br  /><br  />
In a matter of seconds, Hawkins found himself clear on goal and slotted it past the Aldershot goal stopper, however the forward was ruled offside.
<br  /><br  />
Seven minutes in and the Daggers were still searching for an early goal, this time Matt Robinson headed high just after Hawkins headed down a Whitely cross.
<br  /><br  />
The first real chance for the visitors came in the 12th minute, Former Dagenham player, Matt McClure couldn’t keep his shot on target.
<br  /><br  />
Half an hour into the first half and Hawkins received a heavy challenge, Jordan Maguire-Drew was then unable to beat the keeper with the direct free kick.
<br  /><br  />
Aldershot had a good chance to take the lead 10 minutes into the second half, Anthony Straker found the head of McClure, but Elliot Justham superbly denied the ex-Dagger.
<br  /><br  />
John Still made his first substitution of the game, it was Scott Heard who made his debut for the Daggers, after he replaced Ling in the 70th minute.
<br  /><br  />
77 minutes in, a Daggers free-kick is driven into Doe, but the header was powered over Jake Cole’s bar.
<br  /><br  />
A minute later and Whitley took a shoulder charge from a defender and sprinted into the box, but his shot was saved by Cole.
<br  /><br  />
The goal eventually came in the 81st minute, Hawkins showed good strength to beat Evans off the ball and then played Whitely through, the winger then slotted it in from 10 yards.
<br  /><br  />
Justham did just enough in the 90th minute to deny Scott Rendell, as the goalkeeper saved the shot onto the post.
<br  /><br  />
Seconds later the Daggers goal-stopper denied the visitors again, from the corner, to ensure the Daggers earned the full three points.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers will turn their heads towards this weekend’s away fixture against, table toppers, Forest Green.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Doe (c), Robinson, Raymond, Hawkins, Maguire-Drew, Boucaud, Ling (Heard 70), Whitely, Staunton
<br  /><br  />
Aldershot: Cole, Straker, Bellamy (Walker 83), Evans, Rendell, McClure, Mensah, Alexander, Gallagher, Kanu (Allen 69), Reynolds (c)
<br  /><br  />
Attendance: 1,371 (247 away fans)
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-25 21:37:11 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>