<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3385540-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-forest-green-rovers-v-dagenham-redbridge-3385540.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Forest Green Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Dagger's National League away tie at Forest Green Rovers on Saturday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Located in Nailsworth 13 miles south of Gloucester, Forest Green Rovers play at the 5,140 capacity New Lawn Stadium.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Constructed in 2006 following Forest Green’s move from The Lawn Ground, The New Lawn is an eco-friendly stadium that features the world’s first organic football pitch. The stadium consists predominantly of terracing, with the 2,000 capacity Main Stand providing the sole seated accommodation. The ends behind both goals are modern covered terraces, while the Barnfield Terrace is uncovered and runs along one side of the pitch opposite the Main Stand. The New Lawn also operates as a vegetarian football stadium, meaning no meat is served inside the ground.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>DAGGERS FANS:</strong></div><div >Daggers fans have been allocated the Nympsfield Road North Stand which is a covered terrace with a capacity to hold 900 spectators. This stand offers unrestricted views of the playing area, and uniquely for this level features electronic turnstiles! Food inside the ground is restricted to a vegan diet, so if you fancy a burger or a hotdog, make sure you eat pre-match.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong></div><div >As previously mentioned, The New Lawn is the first vegetarian/vegan football club, and as such does not serve meat based products inside the stadium. Due to Forest Green’s somewhat rural setting, there is not a lot in terms of food in close proximity to the stadium, so if you want a bite to eat you are best served heading into Nailsworth which is a 15-minute walk down a fairly steep hill. Located here is also the Village Inn which is listed in the CAMRA Good Beer Guide. If you are arriving by train, the Lord John is a JD Wetherspoon outlet along Russell Street, while Stroud itself also houses a far larger range of restaurants and fast food chains. The Forest Green clubhouse also admits away supporters.</div><div ><br /></div><div >An away travel guide for Forest Green Rovers can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-forest-green-rovers-3383422.aspx">here</a>.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-forest-green-rovers-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3369871.aspx">here</a>.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-27 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>