<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3386271-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-heard-on-signing-for-the-daggers-3386271.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Heard On Signing For The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Heard On Signing For The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Heard On Signing For The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Mideiflder Scott Heard on signing for Dagenham and Redbridge and making his debut for the club on Tuesday against Aldershot Town. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["It was a really tough game on Tuesday, especially coming on as a sub for my debut, as it was quite late on the game but the manager told me to just stay calm and get into the positions where I can be effective."
<br  /><br  />
"I wanted to defend from the font foot, and the manager showed great faith in me to put me on when I only signed last week, so I was really buzzing to get on in the game."
<br  /><br  />
"Playing alongside players like Boucaud and Robinson and even training with them you can see the experience and skill that they have, and I just want to learn of these players."
<br  /><br  />
"I really want to improve and I feel that I am still young enough to improve my game, and I am thankful for the chance that the manager and the club have put in me and want to repay that faith when I am on the pitch."
<br  /><br  />
"Looking ahead to Saturday’s game we have just got to play our own game and to our strengths which will help us to get a result."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/heard-86292-3386370_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/heard-169292-3386373_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-27 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>