<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3391879-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-0-1-barnet-3391879.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 1 Barnet</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 1 Barnet</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 1 Barnet</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Defeated By Barnet</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A 55th minute strike resigned the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s to defeat at Parkonians as the Barnet FC U18s took the points back to North London courtesy of their number ten’s winner.
<br  /><br  />
The away player scored the only goal of the game for the Bees as the east London side were left regretting missed chances of their own.
<br  /><br  />
A first-half Blue Gallagher header was the closest Micah Hyde’s side came to, what would have been, a much-deserved opener had the away stopper tipped the midfielder’s effort over the bar from a Harvey Brown corner.
<br  /><br  />
Chances were, without doubt, created by Micah Hyde’s youngsters, particularly in a bright first half, but the Achilles heel of the hosts on this occasion was dispatching the opportunities.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers frontman Dylan Florence was presented with the Daggers first chance, but scuffed his effort wide from Joe White’s headed pass, and central defender Jack Lee headed Harvey Brown’s corner over fifteen minutes in.
<br  /><br  />
And the hosts were nearly made to pay for missing their early chances, but to the relief of the Daggers, who later saw a Liam Gordon shot fizz wide, a Bees man curled an effort onto the post shortly after the away number nine side-footed horribly wide of a gaping goal.
<br  /><br  />
Mustaphe Ali was the Daggers most hopeful attacking outlet having outwitted his marker on two notable first-half occasions, the first of which resulted in Joe White firing a header over the bar from the wideman’s delicious cross, the second culminating in the away stopper stretching to divert Ali’s far-post effort.
<br  /><br  />
Although the desire and endeavour remained, the overall performance with the addition of clinical finishing would undoubtedly have met the criteria for a commendable victory.
<br  /><br  />
Academy Coach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the game:
<br  /><br  />
“Everything we tried to do today was good and with intent, although we didn't ask enough questions of their goalkeeper with our endeavours in the final third,” said the former Watford and Burnley player.
<br  /><br  />
“Pleasing with such a young side with a couple U16s gaining experience, and good improved individual performances. We was the dominant team, the game being played predominantly in the oppositions half. The approach play and application, creating opportunities from positive play, was good in every aspect today except for what we did in the final third, end product and testing the keeper ”, the coach continued.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up:</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 13. Louie Chapman, 2. Kieran Walker-Browne, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Harvey Brown, 5. Jack Lee, 6. David Agboola, 7. Mustaphe Ali, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Joe White (C), 10. Blue Gallagher, 11. Dylan Florence, 14. Scott Mitchell, 15. Luke Hirst(U16), 16. Mekhi Hyde(U16), 17. Jordy Mongoy, 18. Deniz Alici
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-31 10:07:08 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>