<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3393242-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-john-still-on-the-forest-green-rovers-game-3393242.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Forest Green Rovers game</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Forest Green Rovers game</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: John Still on the Forest Green Rovers game</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts on the Forest Green Rovers game on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["We came to win, we always play to win. I thought it was a fantastic effort from to be honest a depleted side, playing Luke Guttridge is something I didn’t want to do but we had no one else. We had to put Frankie Raymond back to left back, Sam Ling hasn’t trained all week even up to this morning we were doing fitness tests at the hotel so I thought it was a remarkable performance and a fantastic goal from Hawkins, if ever you could see a textbook header that was it. All round we had some great performances Boucaud was good, the work rate was great always trying to press the game."
<br  /><br  />
"The twenty minute spell they had in the second half where they were strong, we looked like we had one or two that needed a bit of fitness but we made the change. We didn’t want to give Guttridge that much time on the pitch but he said he wanted to and said he could give a little bit more. But as always the boys responded like a team and it worked."
<br  /><br  />
"We brought Paul Benson on and Benson’s been out for a while, but we told him he might have to do 10-15 minutes, we just needed the experience at times just to come on and give us a bit of experience on the pitch to help the younger players. But for me that was a first class performance, from a first class bunch of players."
<br  /><br  />
"I think we have a team ethic, we are going to play well every week no one is going to question about our ability to fight and I think this is the first time we have come back from a goal. We don’t come to defend we come to attack, we come to win we didn’t just shut up shop once we got the equaliser. It’s the first goal they’ve conceded in 8 games, they were very lucky in the first half the ball just didn’t go over the line."
<br  /><br  />
"We don’t see the incidents as well as the referee sees them, both teams will look at the decisions made today and say they were questionable. I’m not a referee, it can be the most difficult job in the world you just want them to get the big decisions right especially the handball in the middle of the box."
<br  /><br  />
"To have taken 5 points, we knew the two home games were going to be tough and I didn’t really set a points target but to take 5 points from the two home games and the game on Saturday I’m delighted with that. Especially with the players we have out at the moment and to maintain what we are doing gives us hope for the second half of the season we just got to keep digging in."
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johns-86292-3393234_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johns-169292-3393235_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-10-31 17:35:05 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,First Team,Home,Injury,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>