<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3394529-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-josh-staunton-post-forest-green-rovers-3394529.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Josh Staunton Post Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Josh Staunton Post Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Josh Staunton Post Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Josh Staunton looking back to the Forest Green Rovers game last weekend</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[It was good to come away with the point from the Forest Green Rovers match, it was disappointing to go a goal behind although we did match them we played really well. Both teams had good chances, we especially had some good chances in the first half. 
<br  /><br  />
We were unlucky not to get the three points from Macclesfield, disappointing to concede in the last minutes of the game. To take 5 points in the last three fixtures and stay unbeaten through that week and perform as well as we did.
<br  /><br  />
Obviously we have had a few injuries recently but the squad has definitely pulled together, we all get on really well and help each other out. There is a lot of younger players in the squad so to have the older more experienced players in the squad really does help. But together we have shown our strengths as a squad as we have been relatively short for options but with players coming back we should get some fresh legs on the pitch and gives us more chance to get points.
<br  /><br  />
We have had a very different looking back four throughout the season but that doesn’t affect me, everyone knows their job and everyone knows each other’s jobs so it has made the transition of positions relatively problem free. For example Frankie Raymond has filled in at left back and done a great job, Joe Widdowson hasn’t looked out of place once at right back and me, Robson and Doe playing in centre half who have all done well, we’ve just got to try keep it tight and get used to playing with each other in all different positions and keep clean sheets.
<br  /><br  />
I’m always looking to learn off Scott Doe, he is much older than myself and has played more games than me, you look at things he’s done and I ask myself how I can learn from that. He’s a great player to have on and off the pitch so he’s a good person to learn off.
<br  /><br  />
We expect FC Halifax Town to come at us fast, we’ve just got to treat it like every other game get the job done and hopefully progress into the next round. Saying that, no game in the FA Cup is easy we’ve seen that before with Wealdstone who gave us a good running around in parts and we are expecting more of the same on Saturday.          
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/staunton-86292-3394525_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/staunton-169292-3394526_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-01 16:08:53 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>