<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3397711-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-preview-ian-culverhouse-on-fc-halifax-town-3397711.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Preview: Ian Culverhouse on FC Halifax Town</headline>
  <page_title>Match Preview: Ian Culverhouse on FC Halifax Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Preview: Ian Culverhouse on FC Halifax Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Ian Culverhouse gives his thoughts ahead of the Emirates FA Cup home game against FC Halifax Town on Saturday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Everyone is training today and looking good, we got Hawkins and Robinson back from England C Team duty, the atmosphere is good so we are ready for Saturday. From the feedback we had from the England Camp we know the boys have worked hard so it’s a good morale booster and the training ground seems to buzzing at the moment.
<br  /><br  />
 Saturday against Forest Green Rovers the players showed some great character, it’s the first time we have come back from being a goal down and getting something from the game. The manager did say on Saturday that he felt that we finished the stronger of the two sides which is important because they are a good side, also there financial advantage compared to us is very different.
<br  /><br  />
This Saturday will be a hard game, Halifax have just recently been relegated we have been watching them and they are a very physical side so it will be a tough game and will be a good test for the squad. We are looking forward to it, it will be a good battle but the main thing is to get through to the next round and hopefully get another good draw.
<br  /><br  />
Even though they did lose last week, FC Halifax Town will come to us full of confidence, the run before their loss last weekend was outstanding, by all accounts they play some really good football, and we have got to be ready for whatever they’re going to give us.
<br  /><br  />
When I was at Norwich we lost in two FA Cup semi-finals, so I’ve never actually got over that final hurdle which is a shame, but I was involved with some real good runs with Norwich.
<br  /><br  />
I thought the academy was outstanding last night, full credit to Micah Hyde he’s got the boys working really hard and full credit to the squad for sticking to the game plan and coming out with a great win.
<br  /><br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/ianculverhouse-86292-3397981_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/ianculverhouse-169292-3397983_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-03 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>