<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3398053-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-player-commentary-3398053.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Player Commentary</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Player Commentary</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Player Commentary</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Live commentary will be available this Saturday, for those unable to make the game, on the Daggers FA Cup tie with FC Halifax Town on Daggers Player.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Daggers player is now running at its same level as last season after a number of challenges since our relegation to the National League.
<br  /><br  />
When the Club first started their Daggers Player Commentary service, it was provided by BBC London as part of their coverage of the Football League. Despite the new agreement between BBC Local Radio and the National League signed last summer BBC London are unable to cover our National League games.
<br  /><br  />
The club therefore had to set up our own alternative. The first part was to recruit a commentator and this was achieved with James Glass joining us.
<br  /><br  />
The equipment used by BBC London involved Glensound equipment working on an ISDN line which gives the listener crystal clear clarity from the commentator. This sort of equipment costs in the region of £5,000, including the headsets and microphones. Therefore commentary on the early season matches was carried out using an ordinary telephone line until the club were able to source and fund the ideal tools.
<br  /><br  />
We’re happy to report that club now owns its own ISDN equipment and this was used for the first time at the home game with Aldershot Town. A number of supporters have since let the club know how much better the commentary sounds with the new equipment in place.
<br  /><br  />
We would like to thank supporters for their understanding whilst the transition has taken place and former Daggers player commentator Stuart Smith for his help on using the equipment.
<br  /><br  />
As well as full match commentary, home and away, the Daggers Player also provides extended match highlights of all First Team games and exclusive video interviews and works on mobile, tablet and desktop.
<br  /><br  />
At just £4.49 per month, or as low as £37.99 for an annual pass, why not be part of the action? For full details, T&amp;C’s and how to sign up please click <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/Buy" >HERE</a><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/daggersplayer-86292-3398049_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/daggersplayer-169292-3398050_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-03 18:30:07 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Premium Video</Tags>
</News>