<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3399926-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-joe-widdowson-fc-halifax-town-preview-3399926.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Joe Widdowson FC Halifax Town Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Joe Widdowson FC Halifax Town Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Joe Widdowson FC Halifax Town Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Joe Widdowson discusses the Daggers' up and coming Emirates FA Cup fixture against FC Halifax Town and his thoughts on filling in at right back</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[I do like FA Cup weekend as it is a nice little change from the normal league routine, everyone knows the incentive of the FA Cupand we want to progress as far as we can and hopefully get a good game like we did last season.
<br  /><br  />
We definitely want to continue our good form, unbeaten in 5 now but nothing changes in our preparation, we won’t be underestimating Halifax but we will want to get the win especially as we are at home. Halifax will have come a long way, although it is the FA Cup and as people are always saying anything can happen, they’ll definitely be up for it so it will be a massive game for us.
<br  /><br  />
The Whitehawk games last season in the FA Cup were difficult games, particularly on the away leg there were tough conditions and they were a tough opposition so we won’t be underestimating Halifax as you see upsets at all different levels throughout the FA Cup so we don’t want to be one of those teams that lose to lower opposition.  
<br  /><br  />
The Everton game was a great experience for everyone and that’s what we are looking for, it’s a big incentive for the boys here at Dagenham being able to test ourselves against higher level opponents.
<br  /><br  />
I do enjoy playing right back, I’ve never played in the position before the manager put me there so it’s been a learning process. Although it is the same position but on the opposite side of the pitch it is still very different in terms of positioning and now I’m trying to use my right foot a lot more and I’m getting much more comfortable doing so. 
<br  /><br  />
It’s good to have competition in the squad, Frankie Raymond has been doing really well in the left back spot and when Curtley Williams is fit to play again he will be raring to go, so it will be good for the squad to have some competition for places again.
<br  /><br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/widdowson-86292-3228193_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/widdowson-169292-3228192_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-04 17:07:37 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>