<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3401138-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-0-0-fc-halifax-town-3401138.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 FC Halifax Town</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 FC Halifax Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 FC Halifax Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers will need to put an away fixture into their agenda as they were held to a goalless draw against FC Halifax Town. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[John Still made only one change to his side after last week’s draw away to Forest Green in the National League. Goalkeeper Elliot Justham was rotated for Mark Cousins.
<br  /><br  />
It was a quite start to the match, Jordan Maguire-Drew had a chance from the right as he cut in, however he was unable to keep his shot low.
<br  /><br  />
Luke Guttridge found Corey Whitely in the middle of the six yard box with a great cross 19 minutes into the game and Steven Drench was then forced to save the ball onto the crossbar. 
<br  /><br  />
Tom Denton then won a header inside the box, however Cousins was there to catch the ball.
<br  /><br  />
Whitely was clear on goal just before the half time whistle, but the shot was an easy one for the Shaymen goal stopper.
<br  /><br  />
The visitors pressed up high in the opening minutes of the game, Denton with a couple of chances for his side.
<br  /><br  />
Maguire-Drew then decided to take a shot from distance, but the ball took a deflection and fell nicely for Drench.
<br  /><br  />
62 minutes into the game, Maguire-Drew won a free kick from shooting distance, he then took it and nearly found the bottom corner of the goal, it wasn’t to be as Drench was there with another save for the visitors.
<br  /><br  />
After that both teams failed to take the lead and will need to play the replay on the 15th November away at the Shay.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers: Couisins, Widdowson, Doe, Robinson, Raymond, Hawkins, Maguire-Drew (74’ Sam Ling), Boucaud, Guttridge (85’ Paul Benson), Whitely, Staunton
<br  />
Unused subs: Justham, Hyde, White, Mitchell
<br  /><br  />
FC Halifax Town:  Drench, Roberts, Wilde, King, Hotte, Garner, Macdonald, Lynch, Denton, Sinnott, Simmons (75’ Hibbs)
<br  />
Unused subs: Nicholson, Peniket, Moyo, Burrow, Kosylo, Barrows
<br  /><br  />
Attendance: 1,387 (219 away fans)
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-05 17:40:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>