<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3404154-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-post-fc-halifax-town-3404154.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Post FC Halifax Town </headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Post FC Halifax Town </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Post FC Halifax Town </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Darren Currie discusses the teams performance on Saturday and looks ahead to the replay on the 15th November </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[I thought we started very slowly in the first half, which was a similar situation in the previous round against Wealdstone. We highlighted to the squad that we needed to start the game quick and not let them get comfortable but we didn’t do that and ended up finding it hard to break them down.
<br  /><br  />
With the pace and the attributes we have in our front four, we are constantly asking them to run in behind and get the oppositions back four facing their own goal and as we saw there was only really Corey Whitely’s opportunity with the last kick of the first half that we put a ball in with quality and had a willing runner in behind apart from that a lot of what we done in the first half was played in front of them and they were very difficult to break down.
<br  /><br  />
Luke Guttridge has been out a while and he’s still finding his feet and match fitness so it’s difficult for him, we know he is very capable of finding that one killer ball although that didn’t happen today except from that excellent cross he did play into the box in the first half.
<br  /><br  />
Whether it is a cup match or a league match we are always going into the game looking for a win, ultimately though we can take from the game that we are still in the draw and can still get into the next round.
<br  /><br  />
The replay is not something the team or the club particularly wanted especially with the England C call ups but we had the home advantage to get through to the next round but we didn’t take it.
<br  /><br  />
We have got one or two players that are close to coming back and on a positive you can look at this games squad and see that we have had two academy players on the bench today that have done ever so well in the FA Youth Cup earlier in the week here against Colchester United and on Saturday find themselves in the first team in a FA Cup fixture, so I’d rather put a positive aspect on it rather than a negative.
<br  /><br  />
If you look at the season as a whole we’ve been strong at home, strong away from home, we’re in good momentum, we’re in a great place in the league, and we are disappointed that we didn’t win today at home to go through to the next round in the FA Cup but let’s be positive about it we kept a clean sheet, seasons going well. Obviously disappointed with the outcome today but the season as a whole has been a real plus at minute and we have got to try and remember that.  
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/currie-86292-3404118_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/currie-169292-3404119_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-07 13:30:36 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>