<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3404909-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-reaction-mark-cousins-post-fc-halifax-town-3404909.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Reaction: Mark Cousins Post FC Halifax Town</headline>
  <page_title>Match Reaction: Mark Cousins Post FC Halifax Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Reaction: Mark Cousins Post FC Halifax Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Goalkeeper Mark Cousins gives his thoughts on Saturday's Emirates FA Cup draw against FC Halifax Town.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"I thought that both teams gave it a good go in the second half, but I felt that we was always on top of the game as we created quite a few chances and their goalkeeper made a few good saves."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"We limited them to few chances so defensively we can be happy but offensively we didn’t have the killer chance in the game."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"They had a big striker upfront and the main thing for us was to not foul him as with his size, we knew that he was going to be able to hold the ball up."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"Our defenders were smart as they are not tall so they let him have the ball and picked up the second balls off the striker to stop them creating chances."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"Obviously as a goalkeeper you always want to be able to play all the time, but Justham has been doing really well and I have had to wait for my chance in the cup games and as long as I am impressing the manager I am happy."</div><div ><br /></div><div >"We are still in the cup and we know in the replay that Halifax are going to be up for it as they were on Saturday but we will go up there knowing that we have to perform and win the game."</div><div ><br /></div><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/markcousins-86292-3404905_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/markcousins-169292-3404906_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-08 11:00:07 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>