<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3406158-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/statement-8th-november-3406158.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Club Statement: Board Notice</headline>
  <page_title>Club Statement: Board Notice</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Club Statement: Board Notice</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Notice to Full &amp; Life Members and Supporters</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Since the recent Company meeting to discuss the proposed change in the structure of Dagenham &amp; Redbridge FC Ltd, a number of Members has privately contacted members of the current Board of Directors. They have expressed concerns and indicated that they would now not support the proposed vote on the 'Scheme of Arrangement', which was to be held in mid-December. Certain Board Members have subsequently concluded that there is now no likelihood of the proposed vote achieving the required 75% majority.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The Board has therefore held talks with Mr Tamplin and, despite Mr Tamplin's Consortium still being extremely keen to complete its proposed investment in the Club, the Board of Directors has decided to withdraw its support for the Consortium.  Accordingly, the Consortium has withdrawn from the process.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The Board would like to express its sincere thanks to the individual consortium members for their offer and, in particular, Mr Glenn Tamplin who has conducted himself in an exemplary manner during the whole process.
<br  />
  
<br  />
Unfortunately the step proposed by the Board has been just too much for the current membership.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The current Board will now arrange for the necessary finance to be put in place for the Club to continue at its current level.  It will hopefully submit new proposals to its Members at its upcoming AGM.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The scheduled Fans Forum that is due tonight will still go ahead but now hosted by Managing Director Steve Thompson.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/newgen86292-3115254_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/newgen169292-3115256_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-09 12:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>