<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3412399-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-doe-gateshead-preview-3412399.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Doe Gateshead Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Doe Gateshead Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Doe Gateshead Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Scott Doe gives us his thoughts on return to league football this weekend for our fixture against Gateshead</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Return to the league this week, Gateshead will be a tough game as they all are but it is a home game so we want to get the win in front of the home crowd. FA Cup is done now for the time being so we just need to concentrate on Saturday.
<br  /><br  />
Ideally we would have wanted to beat Halifax at home so we didn’t have to have the replay and the journey but it wasn’t to be. With a lot of games over the next coming weeks, we have to have a fit squad, it has been hard on us because we have had a lot of injuries but we still have enough fit players that are looking good in training and working hard, so the amount of games won’t be a problem.
<br  /><br  />
Boucaud whenever he does get an international call up it’s a good thing for him to represent his country, but I see it as an opportunity for someone else to come into the team and show their authority. It will be a miss for the team but we have had this before and we know how to cope in light of this.
<br  /><br  />
The Christmas period is a very important period, we have lots of games coming up and we want to close that gap with Forest Green Rovers, although it is a long season we have already played them at their place and got the draw, we still will have to play them at home but all we have to focus on right now is taking game by game and concentrate on getting points.
<br  /><br  />
 Ideally in football if you could keep your keeper and back four together as much as you can it does help, but Craig Robson has come in and he was unfortunate with injuries because I thought he was getting better with each game he played. Josh Staunton is another player who has come in and done very well while keeping a lot of clean sheets so a credit to the both of them.
<br  /><br  />
There’s no hiding that fact that you do hear things about the takeover, everyone has social media account so we do hear things that go on outside the club, but the manager has ensured all the players that there is nothing to worry about and it’s a credit to the players that there has been no drop in form.
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /></p><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/scottdoe-86292-3412371_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/scottdoe-169292-3412372_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-11 12:00:03 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>