<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3414308-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-fc-halifax-town-v-dagenham-redbridge-3414308.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: FC Halifax Town v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: FC Halifax Town v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: FC Halifax Town v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Dagger's Emirates FA Cup away tie at FC Halifax Town on Tuesday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >The home of FC Halifax Town, The Shay, has an overall capacity of 14,061 (5,830 seated), with the ground being a mixture of both seating and terracing.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The South Stand is a terraced stand behind the goal for home fans which gives an excellent view of the playing field. Fans can enjoy a pre and post-match pint in the South Stand Bar. The Skircoat stand is all seater down the Skircoat Road side of the MBi Shay Stadium and when open is for away supporters. The North Stand provides a great view however this stand is unused.</div><div >Lastly the East Stand is a magnificent stand holding 4000 fans giving a unobscured view of the playing area and holds Banqueting Suites, bars, food areas and hospitality boxes.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong></div><div >The address for the club is; MBi Shay Stadium, Halifax, HX1 2YT, use the postcode HX1 2YS for sat nav's. From the M62 motorway, take the A629 at Junction 24 and follow the signs for Halifax. The ground is on the right-hand side after about three miles. Parking at the stadium is limited (£3), however there is some street parking to be had, but only if you arrive early. Otherwise it is a case of parking in one of the town centre car parks.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>BY TRAIN:</strong></div><div >Halifax railway station is only five minute walk away from the ground. On exiting the station approach turn left onto Church Street. Keep straight on this road, passing the Pump House and Three Pigeons pubs and you will reach the stadium entrance on your right. The station is on the Trans Pennine route between Leeds &amp; Manchester.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong></div><div >The supporters club are looking to book a coach for the Emirates FA Cup replay next Tuesday and need to know how many people would be interested in going to the game by coach. The coach will be departing Victoria Road at 12:30pm and prices for the travel are £23.00. To book your place, or if you have any further questions, please call the Supporters Club travel Hotline on: 07989901686.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>DAGGERS FANS:</strong></div><div >The Daggers fans will be based in the East Stand which is a magnificent stand holding 4000 fans giving a unobscured view of the playing area and holds bars and food areas. This game is a segregated fixture, but tickets will be available to buy on the turnstiles on the day of the game.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong></div><div >Food available inside includes; 1/2lb Cheeseburgers (£4.50), 1/2lb Burgers (£4), 1/4lb Cheeseburgers (£2.90), 1/4lb Burgers (£2.70), Hot Dogs (£2.50), a range of Pies (Chicken Balti, Cheese &amp; Onion, Meat &amp; Potato, Steak &amp; Kidney all £2.80) and Chips (£1.50).</div><div ><br /></div><div >Ticket information for the game can be fund <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-fc-halifax-town-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3410974.aspx">here</a>.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-14 09:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>