<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3415588-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-dagenham-redbridge-0-2-southend-united-3415588.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 2 Southend United</headline>
  <page_title>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 2 Southend United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 2 Southend United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers Academy fell to a 2-0 defeat at home to rivals Southend United. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >A cold and wet morning in east London saw the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s beaten 2-0 by rivals Southend United in an intense encounter at Parkonians.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The visitors took a first-half lead when the away number four fired in from the edge of the box, and a second-half penalty paved the way for the Seasiders to wrap up the victory in the latter stages of the contest.</div><div ><br /></div><div >A much-improved second-half display saw Micah Hyde’s youngsters apply a tighter grip on the encounter and take the game to Southend, producing more moments of quality and creativity than they managed in the opening 45.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Scott Mitchell came close to igniting a Daggers comeback with a header that flew over the crossbar from a Harvey Brown corner, before Brown himself went for goal with a powerfully driven free-kick that forced a taxing save from the away stopper.</div><div ><br /></div><div >But the wind was taken slightly out of the hosts’ sails just as they began to acclimatise to the game with a dubious penalty decision from the referee after a Seasiders man went down in the box, and Chapman was sent the wrong way from the spot as the taker swept in from twelve yards.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Despite being two goals down, the Daggers continued to play with positivity as they kept the Seasiders pinned back in their own half, being more expressive with their creativity and impressively conjuring up some intricate passages of play as they sought to, at bare minimum, contribute to the scoreline.</div><div ><br /></div><div >And a spectacular opportunity to do so fell to right-back David Agboola, who was clean through but couldn’t direct his lobbed finish towards goal from a tight angle, before Jordy Mongoy’s dipping volley from 25-yards following forced the away stopper into a lunging save.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers created a wonderful passing move that broke down at the last second as the away defender eventually managed to get a foot in following some great combination play as the home side kept the Seasiders pinned back in their own third in an action-packed second half.</div><div ><br /></div><div >As the encounter drew a conclusion, midfielder Blue Gallagher made a last-ditch attempt to set up a tense finale, cutting in from the left and firing low with a right-footed effort, but the keeper was equal to the shot as the Seasiders held on for the victory.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the tie:</div><div ><br /></div><div >“I was impressed with some of the things I saw from my players. We were generally better in the second half, in the first half we weren’t as good, and the the quality in some areas, particularly in final third, could have been better ”, expressed Hyde.</div><div ><br /></div><div >“Winning is an extremely important component in their development, but our aim is to develop U18 players to the standard required for the first team and not having them at my disposal, is exactly what we want. It gives our younger players invaluable competitive experience to develop their game understanding to create scoring opportunities, retaining the ball better in the final third, beating players with the ball and with passes, as they physically they can not compete. And in that we didn’t ask enough questions of their defence today, which was the similar way it went in previous league performance”, continued the Academy Manager.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Line-up Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1. Louie Chapman, 2. Kieran Walker-Brown, 3. Liam Gordon, 4.</div><div >Harvey Brown, 5. Jack Lee, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. James Turvey, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Dylan</div><div >Florence, 10. Mustaphe Ali, 11. Jordy Mongoy, 1. Joe Carter, 13. David Agboola, 14. Blue</div><div >Gallagher, 15. Deniz Alici</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-14 10:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>