<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3416533-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-york-city-3416533.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: York City</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: York City</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: York City</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of Travelling to Bootham Crescent for the Daggers’ fixture against York City, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div ><strong>DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong></div><div >Take the A64 towards Scarborough and York. When you near York, join the A1237 ring road and continue on until you reach Junction 19. Turn right at this junction and take the A19 towards York City Centre. Follow this road until you see a pub on your left called the Burton Stone Inn, at which point you should turn left into Burton Stone Lane. From here, take the first right into Grosvenor Road for Bootham Crescent. Supporters are allowed to park at the nearby York Hospital for a small charge of £2.50 per vehicle. This is allowed during the hours of 1-6pm and supporters should download the necessary voucher from the York City website, <a href="http://www.yorkcityfootballclub.co.uk/">here</a>.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>BY TRAIN:</strong></div><div >York is served direct by trains from London Kings Cross at a rate of around five trains per hour. The journey takes two hours or so, with fares starting at £62.50 for an adult return ticket without a railcard. From the station, Bootham Crescent is around a 20 minute walk away and supporters should also take into consideration the busyness of York City Centre on a Saturday afternoon.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong></div><div >The supporters club will be running a coach to this fixture at a price of £23 for members and £28 for non-members. It will depart Victoria Road at 8:15m and will be making a 45 minute service stop en-route. Supporters are advised that due to the good form of the team on the pitch, coach spaces are filling up fast, so book today to avoid disappointment!</div><div ><br /></div><div >Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-york-city-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3397653.aspx">here</a>.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-15 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>