<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3418429-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-fc-halifax-town-reaction-3418429.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still FC Halifax Town Reaction</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still FC Halifax Town Reaction</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still FC Halifax Town Reaction</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still discusses the teams performance and current injury situation after defeat to FC Halifax Town.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"With the ten men, we went to win the game instead of taking the draw and going into extra time as extra time wasn’t going to help us as we are running on empty at the moment."
<br /><br /></div><div >"We have had a difficult few days with injuries and having to change the team, but I thought that we responded well from Saturday’s game."
<br /><br /></div><div >"We are asking people to do jobs that they are not really comfortable in doing, as we have had to play Hawkins at centre half yesterday and Benson wasn’t really ready to play a full 90 minutes."
<br /><br /></div><div >"Tyrique Hyde has come into the team as well and he played well, and Raymond has been playing left back instead of centre midfield as we are low on defenders."
<br /><br /></div><div >"Sometimes playing people in not their normal positions and having injuries can pick up on you, but that is fine as there is a while to go through the season yet."
<br /><br /></div><div >"Mark Cousins has played well and we are lucky as we have two very good goalkeepers and overall the boys played well today so I am pleased with that."</div><div ><br /><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johnhalifax-86292-3418427_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johnhalifax-169292-3418428_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-16 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Injury,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>