<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3418425-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-paul-benson-post-fc-halifax-town-3418425.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Paul Benson Post FC Halifax Town</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Paul Benson Post FC Halifax Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Paul Benson Post FC Halifax Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Paul Benson gives us his thoughts on the defeat to FC Halifax Town and his current fitness.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["I think that in the first half we wasn’t really good enough and unfortunately it has took us to go down to ten men and having a penalty save from Mark to spark us into the game."
<br  /><br  />
"After that I think that we played well, the intensity and tempo we showed to get back into the game was first class, and to then lose it was a killer blow for us."
<br  /><br  />
"I really thought that after the sending off we was the team in the ascendancy and was the team that would go on to get the winner, so concede right at the end was a kick in the teeth."
<br  /><br  />
"It obviously doesn’t help that we have got a lot of injuries but we don’t want to start making excuses as we have players that can come in and are more than capable to play."
<br  /><br  />
"We had a team for the game that was good enough to get the result, but for 60 minutes we wasn’t quite good enough, so we need to go into the York game and put in the shift and effort that we did in the last 30 minutes of yesterday’s game."
<br  /><br  />
"Corey had a good game and he was a constant threat, I think that it helped him going up top near the end of the game as we had his pace over the top which showed with the goal he scored as it was an excellent finish."
<br  /><br  />
"I have got to try and build my match fitness up now as we have some Tuesday games coming up as well now so the more I play, the fitter and sharper I will get and I feel better with every game at the moment."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/benson-86292-3418424_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/benson-169292-3418423_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-16 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>