<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3418383-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-fc-halifax-town-2-1-dagenham-and-redbridge-3418383.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: FC Halifax Town 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: FC Halifax Town 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: FC Halifax Town 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers were knocked out of the Emirates FA Cup in the first round by FC Halifax Town with the game finishing 2-1.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >The Daggers fielded a unfamiliar line up for the Emirates FA Cup 1st round replay at FC Halifax Town as forward Oliver Hawkins started as a centre back, Tyriqye Hyde starting his first game for the first team in midfield and Paul Benson starting for the first time since getting injured.</div><div ><br /></div><div >FC Halifax Town had the better of the first 10 minutes with two disallowed goals, the first after just one minute and then forward Tom Denton had a header disallowed after a good cross from Kevin Roberts in the ninth minute. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Halifax continued to have the better of the game and on 15 minutes Mark Cousins had to punch a dangerous cross clear before Denton was able to get a header on goal. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Jordan Maguire-Drew picked up the first booking of the game in the 25th minute after a late challenge on defender Josh Macdonald. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Two minutes later Halifax had another chance as Alex Simmons was denied at the front post from Mark Cousins, the Daggers went up the other end quickly and only a great last ditch challenge from defender Scott Garner stopped the Daggers from getting a shot on goal. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers had their first shot on target in the game on the 30th minute as Corey Whitely had a shot from a tight angle on the right hand side pushed over the bar for a corner. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers then had a goal disallowed themselves after Corey Whitely was penalised for offside as Paul Benson put the ball in the back of the net. </div><div ><br /></div><div >A minute later Halifax took the lead after forward Tom Denton hit a half volley into the top right hand corner after a cross was deflected into his path.</div><div ><br /></div><div >There was a succession of two corners in the 42nd minute, and from the second corner Hawkins had a shot that flew just wide of the box, and there was no further action in the first half. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Into the second half and the first chance was in the 55th minute when Jordan Maguire-Drew got the ball on the right hand side and beat two players but his shot flew just over the bar from outside the box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers found themselves down to ten men in the 57th minute as Oliver Hawkins, who was playing in a centre back role, was shown a red card by the referee as he was the last man when he was judged to have made a foul. </div><div ><br /></div><div >FC Halifax Town were given a penalty for the foul, but Mark Cousins made a good save down to his right hand side to keep the score at 1-0. </div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 73rd minute Matt Kosylo, who had just came on for Halifax, had two shots on goal, the first being blocked and the second needing a good save from Mark Cousins. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers got their equaliser in the 74th minute as the ball was played through to Corey Whitely and he placed the ball into the bottom corner. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Matt Kosylo put a ball into the box and a header from Tom Denton was saved in the 76th minute and six minutes later Kosylo was involved again as he had a shot that required a low save from Mark Cousins.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Jordan Maguire-Drew had a chance in the 88th minute when he won the ball in the final third but his shot rose over the bar.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Two minutes later and Halifax got the winner as Matt Kosylo, who was a constant threat when he came on, had a shot from around 30 yards which flew past a few defenders and went into the bottom corner.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><div>Halifax (4-4-1-1): Drench; Roberts, Hotte, Garner, Wilde; Macdonald, King, Lynch, Simmons (Kosylo 68); Sinnott (Hibbs 74); Denton</div><div>Subs: Nicholson, Peniket, Moyo, Barrow</div><div><br /></div><div>Daggers (4-4-2): Cousins; Widdowson, Doe, Hawkins, Raymond; Whitely, Staunton, Guttridge, Hyde, Maguire-Drew (White 90); Benson</div><div>Subs: Justham, Mitchell, Brown, Gordon, Mongoy</div><div>Sent off: Hawkins 57</div><div><br /></div><div>Attendance: 1,465 (including 51 Daggers fans)</div><div><br /></div><div>Referee: Thomas Bramall</div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3316004_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-15 23:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>