<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3419552-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-york-city-v-dagenham-redbridge-3419552.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: York City v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: York City v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: York City v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Dagger's Vanarama National League away tie at York City on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >The home of York City since 1932, Bootham Crescent has an overall capacity of 8,256 and operates as the fifth largest stadium in the National League.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The ground is a mixture of both seating and terracing. The terracing is comprised of the 3,062 capacity David Longhurst Stand and Grosvenor Terrace which holds 1,785 supporters and is reserved solely for away supporters. Adjacent to the terracing is the fully covered Popular Stand which runs alongside the pitch and seats 1,652 spectators. The stadium is completed by the Main Stand which stretches midway into the half at either end and has the capacity to hold 1,757 supporters. It is the larger of the two seated stands in the ground.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>DAGGERS FANS:</strong></div><div >Daggers supporters have been allocated a section of the Grosvenor Road Stand and a part of the Popular Stand. The Grosvenor Stand is an uncovered terrace open to the elements, but offers an unrestricted view of the playing surface. The Popular Stand meanwhile, is all seated and undercover but is restricted by a number of stanchions and poles which get in the way of the action. This game is a segregated fixture, although tickets will be available to buy on the day.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong></div><div >Although there isn’t a great deal in terms of food outlets on the immediate exterior of the ground, York City Centre offers a wide range of restaurants and fast food establishments catering for all tastes. Food is also available in the York City clubhouse which admits away supporters, with reasonably priced sausage roles available at 80p on previous visits. In terms of pubs, the clubhouse admits away supporters as already mentioned, and also shows Sky TV alongside serving four local ales. ‘The Burton Stone Inn’ is located on the A19, while the ‘Old Grey Mare’is opposite although is generally a lot quieter. In the City Centre, the ‘Three Legged Mare’ is small and modern but offers a choice of real ales, while the ‘Hole in the Wall’ franchise slightly earlier on is highly recommended and serves good food. Other pubs include the ‘Stone Roses Bar’ on King Street and ‘The Postern Gate’ which is a JD Wetherspoon outlet.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-york-city-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3397653.aspx">here</a>.</div><div ><br /></div><div >An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-york-city-3416533.aspx">here</a>.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-18 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>