<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3421670-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-frankie-raymond-york-city-preview-3421670.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Frankie Raymond York City Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Frankie Raymond York City Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Frankie Raymond York City Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Frankie Raymond discusses Tuesday's game against FC Halifax Town and looks ahead to Saturday's game against York City</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Tuesday night was disappointing, especially in the FA Cup we did want to get through to the next round but with the vast amount of injuries we have had it has been a tough period for us.
<br  />
 
<br  />
In the game I felt in the first half it was quite even, although in the second half I thought we had the upper hand especially when we went down to 10 men. We stepped up to what was asked of us but it was disappointing to not come out with the result in the end.
<br  />
 
<br  />
All credit to Hawkins I think he done really well at centre back seeing as he has never played in that position before, looking at the incident I think he was unlucky to be sent off. It doesn’t help having all these injuries but we have to push on, we have a good enough squad to fill in for the players missing so we cannot use is it as an excuse.
<br  />
 
<br  />
I have enjoyed playing in the full back position it has been a learning curve for me as I have not really had much experience in the position before this season. Whether I’m playing left back or centre midfield I don’t really mind to be honest as long as I’m in the team and getting game time.
<br  />
 
<br  />
With 19 games played I think we are doing well, we are where we want to be in the table and obviously we want to be right at the top but I think we are going in the right direction to reach that target. The last few weeks have been tough because of the injury situation but as we start to get players back we’ll become stronger and stronger.
<br  />
 
<br  />
We go into every game wanting to win but in this league no game is easy, there’s always going to be upsets in this league as we have seen with some of the league’s results so far. We are going up to York confident and will try our best to get the result.
<br  />
 
<br  />
It was a tough game for Tyrique to get his first 90 minutes in but I think he done brilliantly, he dug in well and showed some real top quality football and I think he has got all the attributes to become a great player.
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>
 
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/raymond-86292-3421657_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/raymond-169292-3421660_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-17 17:45:24 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>