<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3423002-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-maidstone-united-v-dagenham-redbridge-3423002.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Maidstone United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Maidstone United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Maidstone United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Dagger's Vanarama National League away tie at Maidstone United on Tuesday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The home of Maidstone United since 2012, The Gallagher Stadium has an overall capacity of 3030 with a mixture of Terrace and seating stands.
<br  /><br  />
The Gallagher stadium is a very modern one, having been opened in 2012. On the approach to it from the town centre, there is little to see as the stadium is built into a hillside. Even from the main Club car park, there is not much to be glimpsed of the interior. Once inside though it is a different matter. On one side is the smart looking Main Stand. This all seated stand has a cantilevered roof, meaning that there are no supporting pillars to contend with. It is also raised above pitch level, meaning that spectators have to climb a small set of stairs to enter it. This Main Stand was extended in 2015 so that it now has a capacity of 750 seats. Oddly the team dugouts are not located in front of the Main Stand but on the other side of the ground. This side has no facilities for spectators as such, just a small flat standing area, behind the perimeter fence. The team dugouts almost seemed to have been an afterthought as they receded into the standing area. With just two small covered terraces at either end (one of these the Loucas End is just seven steps high), then the ground is very much an open one, with plenty of surrounding trees and greenery on view.
<br  /><br  /><strong >DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong><br  />
Leave the M20 at Junction 6 and take the A229 towards Maidstone. Go straight across two roundabouts and on entering Maidstone at the third roundabout (where there is a large white office building on your right hand side) take the third exit into James Whatman Way. You will now see the stadium right in front of you. At the T-junction turn left and the stadium entrance is further down on the right.
<br  /><br  /><strong >BY TRAIN:</strong><br  />
There are two railway stations located close to the stadium. Maidstone East which is only a quarter of a mile away and Maidstone Barracks, which is half a mile away. However most fans are likely to end up at Maidstone East as it is served by trains from London Victoria and Ashford International. Maidstone East is only about a five minute walk away from the Gallagher Stadium. As you come out of Maidstone East Station walk up the station approach to the main road. At this road turn left and then go straight across the next two roundabouts and you will find the stadium located in front of you. Turn left at the T-Junction and the main entrance is down on the right.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
The usual array of Cheeseburgers (£3.25), Burgers (£3), Hot Dogs (£3), Chips (£2), as well as Chicken Fillet Burgers (£3.25) are available inside. Plus if fans are not segregated then behind the Loucas End is the 'Pie Hut,' which offers locally produced pies by Kentish Mayde. For £4.50 you can have your choice of pie with mushy peas, chips and gravy. Maidstone are a well-supported Club as this can make for a good atmosphere on matchday.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-maidstone-united-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3422334.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-21 10:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>