<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3423074-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-york-city-dagenham-redbridge-3423074.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: York City 0 - 2 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: York City 0 - 2 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: York City 0 - 2 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Two first-half goals set Dagenham &amp; Redbridge on their way to an impressive 2-0 win at York City in the National League.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1" >Daggers made three changes, with Scott Heard handed a first start, while Elliot Justham and Andre Boucaud were recalled to the line-up.</p><p class="p1" >The visitors could have taken the lead in the seventh minute, but Corey Whitely’s shot from just inside the area was well saved by Scott Flinders.</p><p class="p1" >Four minutes later, Justham showed good reactions to get down low and deny York striker Robbie McDaid from 15 yards.</p><p class="p1" >With 24 minutes left in the half, Jordan Maguire-Drew saw his close-range shot blocked behind for a corner that Oliver Hawkins narrowly headed over.</p><p class="p1" >Daggers took the lead in the 28<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute when Hawkins nodded in a brilliant ball from the right by Maguire-Drew.</p><p class="p1" >On the stroke of half-time, Luke Guttridge doubled Daggers’ lead from close range after Maguire-Drew had flicked the ball into his path.</p><p class="p1" >In the second half, though, Justham was required to pull off two saves in as many minutes with around a quarter of a hour gone to deny Aidan Connolly and Sean Newton.</p><p class="p1" >With eight minutes remaining, the hosts had Adriano Moke sent off and from there, Daggers held on to win.</p><p class="p1" >York (3-4-1-2): Flinders; Holmes, Klukowski, Fry; Heslop, Cooper, Moke, Newton; Connolly; Fenwick (Nti 58), McDaid (Rzcona 78).</p><p class="p1" >Subs: Rooney, Dixon, Bruton.</p><p class="p1" >Sent off: Moke 82 (violent conduct).</p><p class="p1" >Daggers (4-2-3-1): Justham; Widdowson, Doe, Staunton, Raymond; Boucaud, Heard; Maguire-Drew (Benson 90+2), Guttridge, Whitely; Hawkins.</p><p class="p1" >Subs: Cousins, Hyde, Barnwell, Mitchell.</p><p class="p1" >Attendance: 2,410 (including 131 Daggers fans)</p><p class="p1" >Referee: Martin Coy</p>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-19 19:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>