<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3428371-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-luton-town-vs.-dagenham-redbridge-3428371.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Luton Town 4-3 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Luton Town 4-3 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Luton Town 4-3 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers youth team fell on the wrong end of a 4-3 thriller away at Luton Town FC to bow out of the FA Youth Cup.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A Dylan Florence hat-trick was not enough for the East Londoners as Luton Town scored a spectacular winner with 8 minutes left of a tie requiring extra time to decide a victor. They opened the scoring in the 9th minute with a 20-yard drive, before Dylan Florence netted a brace in the final 6 minutes of the first half to take Dagenham into the break with a 2-1 lead.
<br  /><br  />
The Hatters equalised 9 minutes from the end of normal time as a result of an effort from Arthur Read creeping in at the near post and forcing extra time.
<br  /><br  />
Florence completed his hat-trick just before the end of extra time first half to give the Daggers a 3-2 lead with a quarter of an hour to go, however, Luton hit a double in successive minutes to take the Bedfordshire side into the 3rd round proper of the FA Youth Cup.
<br  /><br  />
The opening minutes of the encounter were quiet until a strike in the ninth minute beat Daggers keeper Joe Carter to give the home side the early lead.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers almost responded with a goal immediately after the restart when Liam Gordon’s attacking run down the left earned a corner kick for his team. Harvey Brown’s corner was met by the head of Scott Mitchell who rose highest but the ball was headed just over the bar.
<br  /><br  />
The remaining minutes of the first half saw the Daggers dominate as Tyrique Hyde, Joe White, and Dylan Florence continuously linked up well going forward. The home side’s best efforts for a reply to their visitors came in the form of counter attacks which were to little avail.
<br  /><br  />
In the 28th minute, another run down the left side by Gordon almost led to an assist for Florence whose shot was cleared off the line. Four minutes later, another chance for Dagenham was created this time on the opposite side of the pitch by right back Kieran Walker whose low cross found White but his snapshot was well saved by Parker as the ball almost crept in at the near post.
<br  /><br  />
The daggers continued to pile on the pressure as they pushed for an equaliser which finally came in the 39th minute. Elliot Bonds cut inside from the left side to whip in a cross which was chested down by White into the path of Florence who made no mistake finessing the ball into the bottom right of the net and sending Parker the wrong way.
<br  /><br  />
It was a well-deserved equaliser before another Florence goal gave the daggers the lead on the stroke of half time. Tyrique Hyde’s superb cross found the winger at the far post, who took a touch to set himself up for a calm finish that beat the helpless Hatters keeper for the second time in the space of six minutes.
<br  /><br  />
On 53 minutes, Hyde went close to extending the visitor’s lead with a threatening 20-yard effort going over the bar after some good link up play with White.
<br  /><br  />
The following 20 minutes saw the Daggers set the tempo and take control of the game. In 80th minute for the next serious attempt at goal when Hyde and White linked up well to set up Bonds for a shot from the edge of the area which had Parker well beaten, but the post came to Luton’s rescue.
<br  /><br  />
Thirty seconds after surviving the scare, Luton equalised in the 81st minute with a strike beating Carter at his near post.
<br  /><br  />
Extra time was called to separate the two sides and it was Dagenham who struck first when Florence hit a superb effort which found the left side of the net just a minute before the end of extra time first half. A fantastic long pass by Bonds was received by White who cut inside to set up Florence for his hat-trick which gave Dagenham a 3-2 lead.
<br  /><br  />
A 2nd round exit loomed for the Hatters, however, the home side ensured that the game wasn’t yet over in the 110th minute when a Luton player drove the ball into the bottom left corner to level the scores to 3 a piece.
<br  /><br  />
A minute later, the hosts hit a spectacular effort from 22 yards which smashed the top right corner of the net and ultimately send Luton Town into the next round where they will travel to Sheffield Wednesday F.C at their Hillsborough ground.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge F.C: Carter, Walker-Brown (Agboola), Gordon, Brown, Lee,
<br  />
Mitchell, Bonds, Hyde (Turvey), White, Florence, Mongoy.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-21 12:30:30 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Away Fixture,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>