<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3429421-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-reaction-john-still-on-the-win-against-york-city-3429421.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Reaction: John Still On The Win Against York City</headline>
  <page_title>Match Reaction: John Still On The Win Against York City</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Reaction: John Still On The Win Against York City</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts on the win against York City on Saturday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[We are running on empty we really are, we played Tuesday, trained Thursday and then travelled Friday. Robinson’s not fit, we then had to bring Heard in and Guttridge who desperately needs to have a rest and is still not match fit. It became a problem as we did not have any changes in that central midfield area, in the end we had to bring Benson in to fill the wide area because Jordan hasn’t been well.
<br  /><br  />
Guttridge is finding his match fitness again and did play well today but as I said if Robinson was fit today we wouldn’t have played him. He does need to be rested we have pushed him and today we would have liked to of give him a rest; we just do not have the players. We had Tyrique Hyde on the bench just in case but he played twice this week in both the FA Cup and the FA Youth Cup and we have got to be sensible with what we do with young players like Tyrique.
<br  /><br  />
Although, Hawkins was a handful today, scored a great goal and assisted in the second goal. I think we could have had 1 or 2 more but they did have a few good efforts on goal but yet again we dug in well and did not concede any goals away from home. Gary Mills has come in and is doing a good job with the side, he’s brought some players in and with them getting a good result against Eastleigh last week which we had watched we thought it was going to a really tough match, it was tough but we dug in played like how Dagenham should play and got a positive result.
<br  /><br  />
Jordan Maguire-Drew has been feeling poorly over the last couple of weeks and we’ve been trying to give him a rest but at the moment we have no options to be able to rest him but he’s played again today and done very well and assisted both goals. With Chris Assombalonga coming back from his 1 month loan at Whitehawk he will definitely be used in up and coming fixtures.
<br  /><br  />
We said before this month that it was going to be tough, but with our injuries they have not been one or two week injuries they have been serious six to eight week injuries and people do not realise that I know we do have a full time squad but we had a five and a half hour trip back from FC Halifax Town on Tuesday, it took us seven hours for us to get to York today it’s a lot of travelling a lot of time on the coaches and it’s not conducive for people being fresh so that is why I am especially happy with  the performance today.   
<br  /><br  />
I said before the game Forest Green Rovers got beat as long as we win that’s a great result for us because we are a game in hand and are closing on the league leaders.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johnyork-86292-3429419_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johnyork-169292-3429420_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-21 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>