<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3430487-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-maidstone-united-dagenham-and-redbridge-3430487.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Maidstone United 0 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Maidstone United 0 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Maidstone United 0 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Luke Guttridge’s first half goal was just enough for the Daggers to come out victorious against Maidstone United. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Manager John Still made just one change to his side, following the 2-0 victory at York, Jimmy Shepard came in for Scott Heard.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Corey Whitely had the first chance for the Daggers nine minutes into the game, after he was found just outside the box, but he was unable to keep his shot down. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Whitely then did very well to beat his man down the wing and found Oliver Hawkins open inside the box, however the striker was unable to connect with the ball.</div><div ><br /></div><div >22 minutes in and Maidstone won a dangerous free kick just outside the box, Elliot Justham  then did very well to deny Alex Flisher, who aimed for the bottom left hand corner of the goal. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The opening goal of the game came in the 26th minute, Joe Widdowson found Whitely from a throwing, near the corner flag, the forward then picked out Guttridge, who then slotted the ball into the back of the net. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Hawkins came close to extending the lead for the Daggers, as Jordan Maguire-Drew found the head of the centre forward, but Lee Worgan did well to deny him.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With three minutes left of the half, Justham produced another great save, this time keeping out Jack Paxman’s low driven shot.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers were still searching for the second goal just before the break, Maguire-Drew weaved his way into the box, however the shot was blocked.</div><div ><br /></div><div >56 minutes gone and Justham did very well to deny the Stones from scoring an equaliser through Jamar Loza. </div><div >Another great chance came for the Daggers, as Whitely found Maguire-Drew with another brilliant cross, but the forward was unable to keep the header down.  </div><div ><br /></div><div >Maguire-Drew hit the crossbar in the 73rd minute, after the ball fell to him from a Frankie Raymond deflected shot.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With five minutes left of the match, Maguire-Drew was found by Whitely, but Worgan did well to deny the forward once again. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers made it six points out of their two away games in the space of three days, they will now need to prepare for this Saturday’s game at home against Barrow. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Doe (45 Benson), Shepard, Raymond, Hawkins, Maguire-Drew, Boucaud, Guttridge, Whitely, Staunton</div><div ><br /></div><div >Unused subs: Cousins, Assombalonga, Heard, Hyde</div><div ><br /></div><div >Maidstone: Worgan, Mills, Coyle, Lokko, Rogers (74 Odubade), Sweeney, Paxman, Flisher, Taylor (84 Enver-Marum), Twumasi, Loza (80 Hudson-Odoi)</div><div ><br /></div><div >Unused subs: Evans, Greenhalgh</div><div ><br /></div><div >Attendance:  1,970</div><div ><br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-22 23:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>