<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3432329-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-on-the-away-win-to-maidstone-united-3432329.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still On The Away Win To Maidstone United</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still On The Away Win To Maidstone United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still On The Away Win To Maidstone United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Still gives us his thoughts on the performance of the squad and how he is dealing with injuries.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["We’re missing a lot of player and getting injuries all the time; the boys have been filling in excellently. Hawkins has been magnificent for us filling in at centre half, but then he’s a big miss up front, I look at tonight as a good win away from home, it’s always hard to win away from home especially mid-week. I will have to look at tonight’s injuries and suspensions and look ahead to Saturday’s game."
<br  /><br  />
"Hawkins has been playing well in centre half but we miss his quality up front, I think he is the best from Division 1 down at what he does. Benson hasn’t been playing a lot of football because of the form of Hawkins and he’s still trying to get fit. We was able to push Luke Guttridge through games to get him fit but we haven’t been able to do that with Benson."
<br  /><br  />
"Guttridge is a very influential player, he actually will need a rest now we will give him a few days off. We decided just before kick-off to go through and play Guttridge when we got here and looked at the playing surface so that was a positive for us. This surface was a bit different to Sutton’s pitch and was wetter which was a positive for us."
<br  /><br  />
"Jimmy Shepherd came in today and played well and with what we have had to do with our back four especially this year is incredible; to be doing so well as we have been and get where we are in the table. I give every credit to the players as we have had to chop and change the back four, we’ve had people playing out of position and looking at our injuries we have Luke Pennell, Scott Doe, Craig Robson and Curtley Williams so to keep these clean sheets has been exceptional."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johnmaidstone-86292-3432262_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johnmaidstone-169292-3432263_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-23 11:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Injury,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>