<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3434732-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-chris-assombalonga-previews-the-barrow-game-this-saturday-3434732.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Chris Assombalonga Previews The Barrow Game This Saturday</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Chris Assombalonga Previews The Barrow Game This Saturday</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Chris Assombalonga Previews The Barrow Game This Saturday</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Forward Chris Assombalonga gives his thoughts on the game against Barrow and talks about his loan spell at Whitehawk.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["While I was at Whitehawk I got a lot of game time, I think that is what I really needed because training and playing games are totally different. With the skills I was improving in certain areas on the training ground I needed to integrate this into a match scenario, in which I believe I have done that while I was at Whitehawk getting my 90 minutes and I’ve improved my game so it was a really good experience for me going out on loan."
<br  /><br  />
"The type of player I am, I like running I have a high work rate in training and in games so I think my fitness has always been there, so if I am given the opportunity to play 90 minutes for the Daggers I will be able to perform."
<br  /><br  />
"It’s good to be back home and in and around the boys, being able to come in and train every day is where I want to be so I can keep working hard so that when my opportunity does come I will be fully ready to prove myself to the manager."
<br  /><br  />
"Unfortunately the squad is riddled with injuries but it is an opportunity for me to come in and show my ability. I know that I have just got to be ready anytime whether there are injuries or suspensions, so I feel like when my opportunity does come I’ll definitely be ready for selection."
<div ><br /></div><div >"With the players playing out of position, what you’ve got to remember is that the main thing is first and for most its all about the team and the manager knows what he’s doing, so whatever position he wants me to play at if its Striker, winger or centre midfield I’ll fill in that position and give 100% as we are a team that are destined to go back into League Two and I want to be part of that."
<br /><br />
"Every game in this league is tough and very unpredictable as we have seen so far this season. Barrow’s unbeaten record is impressive but whatever team we come against we don’t need to worry about them we just need to play our game."
<br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/chrisassombalonga-86292-3436073_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/chrisassombalonga-169292-3436074_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-25 15:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>