<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3437225-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-barrow-3437225.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 4 Barrow</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 4 Barrow</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 4 Barrow</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>A failure to take chances turned out to cost the Daggers, on another tough afternoon at home, as they were beaten by Barrow 4-1.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[John Still made two changes to his side after Tuesday’s 1-0 victory away to Maidstone. Magnus Okuonghae was called up to the starting line-up after his recent return back to the club, he replaced Scott Doe and Scott Heard came in for Andre Boucaud.
<br  /><br  />
Barrow started the match very attacking and came close to scoring through Harrison, but Staunton headed inches wide a Luke Guttridge corner in the fifth minute.
<br  /><br  />
The visitors were then awarded a dangerous free kick, Jordan Williams did well to put it over the four man wall, but Justham was there to catch it.
<br  /><br  />
Just before the first quarter of an hour, Bennett was clear on goal, but his shot flew over Elliot Justham’s goal.
<br  /><br  />
A minute later saw a brilliant individual performance from Guttridge taking on two men and crossing the ball into Hawkins, Whitely then fired a half volley that Erlandsson pushed over the bar.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers were awarded five corners in the space of two minutes, however Barrow showed great defensive attributes to deny the east Londoners to take the lead.
<br  /><br  />
With four minutes left of the first half, Hughes headed the ball from a Williams corner, the ball was then cleared away by Maguire-Drew, however the goal was given to the visitors.
<br  /><br  />
Barrow were then up by two goals in the 45th minute as they caught the Daggers on a break, which resulted in Harrison tapping into an open goal.
<br  /><br  />
Four minute into the second half and the Daggers had a double chance as Whitely saw his shot saved, the ball then came to Raymond and his effort was brilliantly saved by Tim Erlandsson.
<br  /><br  />
The visitors came close to scoring a third, the ball fell for Alex-Ray Harvey, whose shot from distance ended up going just wide of Justham’s goal.
<br  /><br  />
The third then came in the 63rd minute, the ball bounced kindly for Bennett who fired his shot into the top right hand corner of the Daggers net.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers reacted quickly to that third goal as Guttridge had a shot saved by Erlandsson, but Whitely was there to put the rebound in.
<br  /><br  />
71 minutes gone and Guttridge had a low drive saved by Erlandsson as he sent the ball just wide of the Barrow goal.
<br  /><br  />
A penalty was awarded to the visitors in 77th minute, Okuonghae held an attacking players shirt inside the box, Byron Harrison stepped up and made it four.
<br  /><br  />
Justham did very well to deny the substitute Ross Hannah from making it five in the dyeing seconds of the game.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers will now be looking towards this Tuesdays match against Torquay who currently sit in 17th position.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Okuonghae, Heard (81 Hyde), Whitely, Shepard (67 Assombalonga), Hawkins (77 Benson), Maguire-Drew, Raymond, Guttridge, Staunton
<br  />
Unused subs: Cousins, Mitchell
<br  /><br  />
Barrow: Erlandsson, Beeley, Aderton, Livesey, Diarra, Harvey, Bennett, Williams (83 Meikle), Hughes, Harrison (83 Hannah), Yates
<br  />
Unused subs: Haworth, Wright, Anderson
<br  /><br  />
Attendance:  1,228
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-26 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>