<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3441213-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Job Vacancy: Head Groundsman</headline>
  <page_title>Job Vacancy: Head Groundsman</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Job Vacancy: Head Groundsman</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge FC are currently looking for a Head Groundsman</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Main responsibilities are to maintain and prepare the playing surface to the highest level to ensure all games can go ahead as scheduled. To assist where necessary the maintenance of the training pitch and maintain the surrounding areas of the stadium to the same high level.
<br  /><br  />
This is a Full-Time position with a standard working week of 35 hours.  However flexibility in this role is essential as there will be a requirement to work additional hours where necessary and including evenings, weekends and bank holidays.
<br  /><br  />
Salary between £19,500 and £22,000 depending on experience.                                  
<br  />
20 Days Holiday.                                                  
<br  />
Contributory Pension Scheme.
<br  /><br  />
Qualifications &amp; Requirements
<br  /><br  />
Proven grounds experience along with a recognised Turf Maintenance (NVQ Level 2) or equivalent qualification.                                 Spraying licence preferred but not necessary.                                       
<br  />
A good level of physical fitness is required.                                             
<br  />
The ability to work independently of others.
<br  /><br  />
Specific Duties
<br  />
•    At all times adhere to high standards in relation to Health and Safety.
<br  />
•    Prepare the playing surface to a high standard undertaking all duties to ensure the best possible playing surface.
<br  />
•    Take such action as is deemed necessary to ensure that games go ahead. This may involve frost protection, drainage measures or any other additional action required to ensure games go ahead on schedule.  This may also involve actions in relation to public areas to ensure safety.
<br  />
•    Ensure that the pitch and stadium is prepared correctly for fixtures and other events involving the playing surface.
<br  />
•    Ensure that all machinery is maintained to a safe and adequate standard.  No maintenance of machinery should be carried out by employees where this may result in a significant risk to health and safety.
<br  />
•    Maintain the areas around the ground including culverts, banks, hedges and car park ensuring public safety and good cosmetic appearance.
<br  />
•    Assist with the maintenance of the training pitches when required.
<br  />
•    Move and maintain advertising hoardings as requested by line manager and where general maintenance becomes apparent.
<br  />
•    Undertake general maintenance tasks in relation to the playing surface and stadium.
<br  />
•    Accept and check deliveries as required.
<br  />
•    Undertake other duties as designated by line manager and cover other duties where required to support the smooth running of the Club.
<br  /><br  />
Applications together with full CV should be sent to the Club Secretary, Mark Southgate, at <a href="mailto:%20secretary@daggers.co.uk" >secretary@daggers.co.uk
<br /></a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/newgen2-86292-3115258_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/newgen2-169292-3115259_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-28 11:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>