<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3443378-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-dover-athletic-3443378.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: Dover Athletic</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: Dover Athletic</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: Dover Athletic</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of Travelling to the Crabble Athletic Ground for the Daggers’ fixture against Dover Athletic, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div ><strong>DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong></div><div >Leave the M25 at Junction 2 and take the A2 and then the M2 towards Dover. On the outskirts of Dover, you will reach a roundabout which has a McDonalds on the left. At this roundabout, take the fourth exit onto Whitfield Hill (signposted Dover North/River). At the bottom of this roundabout you will reach another roundabout where you should take the first exit onto London Road, going towards Dover Town Centre. At the next set of lights turn onto Crabble Road and after passing under the railway bridge, the entrance to the ground is further down on the left. Free parking is available at the rugby ground, inside the entrance.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>BY TRAIN:</strong></div><div >Dover Priory Station is accessible via train from London Victoria and London St. Pancras at a rate of around six trains every hour. The journey takes just under two hours, and costs either £21.10 or £23.70 for an adult return ticket without a railcard dependent on which station you depart from. From Dover Priory, it is advised supporters take a taxi to the ground as it is located over two miles away. Alternatively, supporters may wish to stay on to Kearnsey Station which is a more manageable 15 minutes from the Crabble Ground. Supporters should also be aware of the steep hill leading to the stadium itself from the main road.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong></div><div >The supporters club will be running a coach to this fixture at a cost of £13 for members and £18 for non-members. It will depart Victoria Road at 12pm and will not be making a service stop en-route. Supporters are advised that due to the good form of the team on the pitch, coach spaces are filling up fast, so book today to avoid disappointment!</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-29 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>