<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3443790-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-torquay-united-3443790.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 1 Torquay United</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 1 Torquay United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 1 Torquay United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge suffered a disappointing 1-0 loss at home to Torquay United in the National League.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Daggers made two changes, with Scott Doe replacing Jimmy Shepherd and Andre Boucaud coming in for Scott Heard.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the ninth minute, Luke Guttridge tested Brendan Moore with a half-volley from 18 yards which the Torquay keeper pushed over for a corner.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Seven minutes later, Oliver Hawkins only narrowly failed to connect with Corey Whitely’s ball across goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With 22 minutes remaining in the half, Whitely went close, but fired his shot from 10 yards straight at Moore.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 43rd minute, Whitely almost struck, but fired wide after Jordan Maguire-Drew’s cross was deflected into his path.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The half, though, ended goalless, but Whitely nearly found the deadlock within a minute of the restart, but fired narrowly over from 25 yards.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 57th minute, Jordan Maguire-Drew nearly turned Guttridge’s shot into the net, but was denied by a stunning stop from Moore.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With 20 minutes remaining, Justham did well to keep out a Kieffer Moore header before Nathan Blissett headed the rebound over.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers fell behind in the 76th minute when Kieffer Moore found the net from just inside the box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers could not find the equaliser they craved and will want better at Dover Athletic on Saturday.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><br /></div><div ><br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-29 20:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>