<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3443342-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/friends-for-a-fiver-solihull-moors-braintree-town-3443342.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Friends For A Fiver: Solihull Moors &amp; Braintree Town</headline>
  <page_title>Friends For A Fiver: Solihull Moors &amp; Braintree Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Friends For A Fiver: Solihull Moors &amp; Braintree Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are offering a Christmas and New Year offer for season ticket holders for the next two league games.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div style="font-size: 10.6667px;" ><span style="font-size: 10.6667px;">Season ticket holders will be able to bring a friend to the Solihull Moors and Braintree Town games for just five pounds.</span></div><div ><div><span style="font-size: 10.6667px;"><br /></span></div><div>The offer means that each season ticket holder is able to bring one additional person to the games, which can be either an adult, junior or senior. </div><div> </div><div>When buying the tickets for a fiver, the season ticket holder must show their season ticket and redeem voucher A for Solihull Moors and/or voucher B for Braintree Town.</div><div><br /></div><div style="">With the last Saturday game before Christmas traditionally being the lowest attended weekend in football in England and the New Year fixture now being played on Monday 2nd January at 7.45pm, we hope that as many season ticket holders as possible can take up the offer as we look to give John Still and his squad the best support possible in this very busy period whilst at the same time thanking our loyal supporters.</div><div><br /></div><div>Tickets will be available up until 5.00pm on the 16th December for Solihull Moors and 5.00pm on the 30th December for Braintree Town.</div><div><br /></div><div>And don’t forget our Christmas Carol Service following the Solihull Moors game which gives even greater value, with this starting from 5:30pm until 6:45pm. </div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-29 15:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>