<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3444606-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-john-still-on-the-torquay-united-defeat-3444606.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: Darren Currie On The Torquay United Defeat</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: Darren Currie On The Torquay United Defeat</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: Darren Currie On The Torquay United Defeat</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Darren Currie gives his thoughts on the home defeat to Torquay United on Tuesday evening. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["We wasn’t ruthless enough in front of their goal and we got punished at the other end in front of our goal, we had enough opportunities to win the match last night but we didn’t take them.
<br  /><br  />
There was enough chances there for us last night and I know that the boys are usually better than they were yesterday in front of goal.
<br  /><br  />
The longer that the games goes on without you taking your chances you get more frustrated and we have ended up with nothing and we only have ourselves to blame for not being ruthless enough.
<br  /><br  />
Whitely was at his dynamic best again last night, he was causing problems wherever he was on the pitch and it would have been nice for him to get a goal to top his performance but it wasn’t to be.
<br  /><br  />
Hawkins fell down onto his lower back and unfortunately it stiffened up quite quickly after that so he wasn’t able to continue but hopefully he will be ready to go again on Saturday.
<br  /><br  />
We will look into the positives of the last two games in that we are still creating a lot of chances in games we just need to start taking the chances when they come.
<br  /><br  />
We will look back at the games and show the players the good parts of play that we had and also show them where we need to improve, and go back to how we was performing at the start of the season.
<br  /><br  />
We know that despite the last two home games that we have a real opportunity of getting back into the Football League next season and that is what we are all hoping to achieve."
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-30 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>