<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3444612-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-magnus-okuonaghae-on-the-defeat-to-torquay-3444612.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: Magnus Okuonaghae On The Defeat To Torquay</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: Magnus Okuonaghae On The Defeat To Torquay</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: Magnus Okuonaghae On The Defeat To Torquay</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Defenders Magnus Okuonaghae gives his reaction to the defeat to Torquay United on Tuesday.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["The boys are devastated with the defeat, I felt that we created enough in the game and the more chances that you miss the other team start to get a lift.
<br  /><br  />
Torquay then got a goal which meant that we were chasing the game and that always makes it tough.
<br  /><br  />
I have been training with the squad for a while, me and the manager kept the dialogue open, so I felt that it was only a matter of time before I signed.
<br  /><br  />
I am frustrated with how my first to games have gone but I am delighted to be back here and delighted to be playing football again.
<br  /><br  />
I have played for a few clubs in my career so far but Dagenham, were always a club that I would look out for and I was devastated to see the club go down last year.
<br  /><br  />
Now I have got the chance to get the club back to where I believe it should be and it is a family club and I believe that when you play for the Daggers you end up falling in love with the club as we play with a passion and a pride.
<br  /><br  />
We are all disappointed at the minute but we all believe that we have enough to turn this bad spell around.
<br  /><br  />
Sometimes you can have spells where you are creating chances but not taking them and the opposition are taking them when they are playing against you, it is tough but we need to stand up and be strong."
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div></div><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-11-30 15:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>