<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3446437-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-andre-boucaud-dover-athletic-preview-3446437.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Andre Boucaud Dover Athletic Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Andre Boucaud Dover Athletic Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Andre Boucaud Dover Athletic Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Central Midfielder Andre Boucaud gives us his thoughts on Tuesday's defeat and looks ahead to Saturday's game against Dover Athletic</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["Looking back to Tuesday we did have the chances to score that we didn’t take, if we would have took the chances we did have I think it would have been a completely different game. The longer you go in games like Tuesday’s without scoring the harder the game gets, Torquay took their chances that they did create and won the game which I am extremely disappointed about."
<br  /><br  />
"It’s hard to put my finger one thing that has changed our performance in the last three games at home, we have had a tough month with a lot of games. The injuries do not help, although we cannot use that as an excuse as we do have a good enough squad for players to fill the positions, but again it has been difficult where we have had close to 14 injuries. Before the three home games I had thought we had been dealing with games really well but we have just got to get back to what we was doing earlier in the season."
<br  /><br  />
"Me and Robinson did build a good partnership, he was doing very well for the team so it is a big loss for him to be injured, but this is football you get injuries throughout the season, it has given another player a chance to fill that spot and give them an opportunity."   
<br  /><br  />
"The Manager has pointed out the positives we have had in our recent games, but he’s been picking up on the negatives also as we can’t keep making the same mistakes. The manager tells us we have to push on, we’ve worked hard to get to this point, and we are halfway through the season and still in and around the top spot we have just got to go into these games over the Christmas period and get some good results."
<br  /><br  />
"Dover are doing well this season, it will be a difficult game although we did play them earlier on in the season and beat them. Although we have beaten them before we can’t go there and take them lightly as they are a good side but so are we so we will just have to continue to work hard and pull together."     
<br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/andreboucaud86292-3446403_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/andreboucaud169292-3446404_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-01 16:30:20 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>