<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3447754-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-gowens-injury-update-ahead-of-dover-athletic-3447754.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Gowens Injury Update Ahead Of Dover Athletic</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Gowens Injury Update Ahead Of Dover Athletic</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Gowens Injury Update Ahead Of Dover Athletic</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Physio John Gowens gives an unjury update ahead of our game against Dover Athletic on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["Hawkins is sore on his hip area and on the side of his knee, his injury was more about how he landed rather than the coming together. He will hopefully be available for Saturday but we will re-assess him tomorrow before the game to see how he is and if he will be able to play.
<br  /><br  />
Matt Robinson had an x-ray last week, we assessed him on Saturday and unfortunately he tried to hop and he suffered a fracture of his fibula. He will be seeing a consultant tomorrow to find out what the next step will be for him and hopefully this will be no more than having to wear a protective boot, but we will know for sure next week.
<br  /><br  />
Robson and Okenabirhie are both back in training doing some running. Fekiri had a MRI scan which came back with just some bone bruising which is good news and we are gradually increasing his work load to get him to do some ball work.
<br  /><br  />
Craig Robson is ahead of Okenabirhie in regards to work as he has started some ball work, but he still has a little bit of pain in his knee where his injury was, although he is at the last part of his recovery now so he shouldn’t be too far away from full time training.
<br  /><br  />
Curtley Williams is another one where we have to manage him right, he is about another week away from starting some running but we will have to see how he copes with getting back into some training.
<br  /><br  />
Luke Howell had a cartilage operation a week ago and his knee looks good but he still has some stitching in so he is limited to what he can and can’t do, but he will be seeing the consultant again next week where we hope he will get the all clear to start pushing on with his recovery.
<br  /><br  />
Sam Ling had a slight thigh strain, he was outside doing some work today but suffered a bit of a reaction so he will probably be another week or so away from joining in with the team again.
<br  /><br  />
Unfortunately it has been a slow process where we are monitoring the players day by day to see how they are doing. I have been here 12 years now and this is the worst injury period that I have ever had, so it is hard.
<br  /><br  />
All the injuries that we have had, none of them could have been prevented, they have been down to some bad luck and some incidents what we have not been able to control."
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/johngowensdover-86292-3447152_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/johngowensdover-169292-3447153_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-02 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>