<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3448522-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dover-athletic-dagenham-and-redbridge-3448522.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dover Athletic 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dover Athletic 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dover Athletic 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Two first half goals from Jordan Maguire-Drew and Paul Benson help the Daggers back into play-off places.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" >The league’s top scorer Ricky Miller missed a penalty, however he did bring the home side back by one, minutes later, but the Daggers defended well till the end.</div><div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" ><br /></div><div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" >Two changes were made to the team as Christian Assombalonga came in for the suspended Frankie Raymond and Paul Benson replaced Oliver Hawkins, who came off injured last game against Torquay.</div><div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" ><br /></div><div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" ><div>In the opening minutes of the game, Corey Whitely did very well to dispossess Richard Orlu near the corner flag, the forward then put in a dangerous low ball which went straight past the face of the goal.</div><div><br /></div><div>The Daggers then took the lead through Maguire-Drew, as he won a free kick 30 yards out and put it past the Dover stopper with a curling dipping shot in the 12th minute.</div><div><br /></div><div>Scott Doe’s headed clearance fell for Ricky Miller, but the Dover forward struck the ball over Elliot Justham’s goal.</div><div><br /></div></div><div style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-family: wf_segoe-ui_normal, 'Segoe UI', 'Segoe WP', Tahoma, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; -webkit-tap-highlight-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);" ><div>Maguire-Drew did very well to pick out Whitely with a brilliant long ball, the forward then smashed a shot on target, but Arnold pushed it out for a corner.</div><div><br /></div><div>Seconds later in the 42nd minute, Paul Benson extended the lead for the Daggers, the corner came in and the forward headed in his first goal since his return to the Daggers.</div><div><br /></div><div><div>It was a quite start to the second half, the Daggers’ only real chance came in the 62nd minute, after a great build up play which lead to Benson’s shot being saved.</div><div><br /></div><div>The game started to get busier when Dover were awarded a penalty in the 68th minute, after Luke Guttridge pushed Miller. However Justham managed to save Miller’s penalty. </div></div><div><br /></div><div><div>Miller did get one back in the 83rd minute, but it wasn’t enough as the Daggers came out with the three points.</div><div><br /></div><div>The Daggers will now need to prepare for next Saturday’s match against Worthing FC in the FA Trophy.</div></div><div><br /></div><div><span style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);">Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Doe, Benson, Maguire-Drew, Boucaud, Guttridge, Whitely, Staunton, Assombalonga (89 Hyde), Okuonaghae</span></div><div><div>Unused subs: Cousins, Heard, Mitchell, Barnwell</div><div><br /></div><div>Dover: Arnold, Magri, Thomas (76 Pinnock), Orlu, Stevenson, Miller, Grimes, Sterling, Emmanuel, Lafayette, Kinnear Jnr (77 Parkinson)</div><div>Unused subs: Walker, Modeste, Marsh</div><div><br /></div><div>Attendance: 1,234</div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-03 20:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>