<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3451485-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-0-0-peterborogh-3451485.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Peterborogh</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Peterborogh</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Peterborogh</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Dominate In Peterborogh Draw</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A spirited performance from an upbeat Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s saw Micah Hyde’s youngsters shine in a Daggers-dominated stalemate with the Peterborough United Academy at Parkonians.
<br  /><br  />
In a thoroughly entertaining encounter, the hosts did just about everything but score as they took control of the tie and created an abundance of chances, but occasionally lacked composure in front of goal.
<br  /><br  />
On another day, the hosts would undoubtedly be enjoying a huge victory, but the quality of finishing was sometimes below-par in contrast to the quality of build-up play.
<br  /><br  />
Striker Joe White and winger Mustaphe Ali were presented with the best chances of the game, but both missed the target at key moments, and Dylan Florence saw a first-half shot from four yards blocked on the line.
<br  /><br  />
Aside the goals, the hosts replicated, and in some cases bettered, the performance that saw them claim an emphatic 4-1 away victory against the East Anglian side back in September.
<br  /><br  />
They attacked powerfully and with intent, dominated possession, and made full use of the space in slick pass and move situations as they constantly stretched their opponents, who were let off purely on chances missed by the Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
The hosts were on top from the start, and threatened early as Joe White struck the upright from a free-kick after Jordy Mongoy was fouled 25 yards out, before the striker dragged his best chance wide of a gaping goal after controlling an airborne ball and running clear.
<br  /><br  />
The forward also side-footed over after Harvey Brown sent in a low corner before just missing a low Liam Gordon cross as the U’s were left breathing a sigh of relief.
<br  /><br  />
The in-form left back, along Jordy Mongoy, were the Daggers most promising creative outlets, with their skillful runs and dangerous crosses constantly hassling the U’s backline.
<br  /><br  />
On the counter, the latter effortlessly skipped past the away number six, but the wide man’s first-time cross was cut out before his second lead to a corner that Jack Lee headed into the away stopper’s gloves, before the former coasted past a host of United defenders before laying off to Dylan Florence, whose cross was lashed wide by Elliot Bonds.
<br  /><br  />
Moments later, Kieron Walker-Brown’s powerful strike from thirty-yards was tipped over the bar by a busy U’s stopper before Dylan Florence’s finish on the rebound of Liam Gordon’s driven effort was blocked on the line as the half-time whistle loomed.
<br  /><br  />
It was more of the same from the Daggers in an enthralling second-half that saw the Daggers go all out to secure a victory fitting of their colourful display.
<br  /><br  />
On two occasions, Jordy Mongoy worked his way deep into the U’s six-yard box, but the final ball was unproductive, before Joe White uncharacteristically scuffed high and wide of a gaping goal after being fed by James Turvey with an inviting cross.
<br  /><br  />
Having been played down the line by Mongoy, substitute forward Turvey sent in a cross that Mustaphe Ali controlled but thumped over as the hosts applied further pressure on a fragile looking U’s backline, and Elliot Bonds was close with a curled effort that was collected by the away goalkeeper.
<br  /><br  />
With the game drawing to a close, the Daggers had one last throw of the dice as worked corner landed at the feet of Joe White, who was in an inviting position but could not get his shot away as the forward held off two away defenders in a crowded penalty area.
<br  /><br  />
Although the result was not reflective of the events of the encounter, the Daggers have a catalogue of positives to reflect on from a highly impressive display.
<br  /><br  />
Academy Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the game:
<br  /><br  />
“I’m pleased we kept a clean sheet and good defensively, pleased with the way we passed the ball and opportunities we created today, we did everything but put the ball in the net, which is unusual, but many positives to take out of the performance today,” said a pleased Hyde.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 13. Camron Greaves, 12. Kieron Walker-Brown, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Harvey Brown (C), 5. Jack Lee, 6. David Agboola, 7. Jordy Mongoy, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Joe White, 10. Dylan Florence, 11. Mustaphe Ali, 1. Louie Chapman, 14. Deniz Alici, 15. Blue Gallagher, 16. James Turvey
<br  />
 
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-05 09:50:07 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>