<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3452627-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/paul-benson-post-match-interview-away-at-dover-athletic-3452627.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Paul Benson Post Match Interview Away At Dover Athletic</headline>
  <page_title>Paul Benson Post Match Interview Away At Dover Athletic</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Paul Benson Post Match Interview Away At Dover Athletic</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Forward Paul Benson gives us his thoughts on scoring his first goal of the season and the teams performance on Saturday against Dover Athletic</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["To be totally honest I am happier that we won the game than getting my goal, the main aim for Saturday was to come here get the win and make up for the defeat we suffered Tuesday night in which we have done. We definitely had to dig in second half we were under a lot of pressure, although performances like that are who we are, Tuesday night wasn’t really us we were a lot better on Saturday and I think we deserved to win."  
<br  /><br  />
"As John Still says it was a proper Dagenham performance today, everyone gave it their all and won their personal battles. Guttridge and Boucaud in the middle worked brilliantly together, I think they won us the game to be honest; they got on top of their middle two, kept us driving forward and also gave good screening for the back four. It was a great team performance there was no real individual performances."
<br  /><br  />
"It does mean a lot to me to be scoring again, it would have been nice for my last goal for Dagenham to of been at Wembley but that’s gone now and I just want to keep playing and keep scoring as many goals as I can for this club as it is my club, its where I made my name and I have the most affection for the people here, so every time I put on the shirt I’m so proud; just scoring goals is a bonus."
<br  /><br  />
"I’m really not sure about our form at home, the manager has picked up on it how we are doing so well away from home but how we need to pick it up at home, but as I said I can’t really answer your question maybe we relax more at home because we think we are going to win the game and in this league you can never do that. We show when we are on it we’re a match for anyone and Dover are a good side, I think if we can have that same mentality we have away when we are at home then we’ll be fine."
<br  /><br  />
"I haven’t started at home yet since rejoining Dagenham, so if I can have a chance to start at home that would be nice, again I look to carry on scoring and helping the team win games."    
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/bensoninterviewtemplate86292-3452233_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/bensoninterviewtemplate169292-3452234_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-05 15:00:16 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>