<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3455656-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-tyrique-hyde-on-heybirdge-swifts-defeat-3455656.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: Tyrique Hyde On Heybirdge Swifts Defeat</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: Tyrique Hyde On Heybirdge Swifts Defeat</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: Tyrique Hyde On Heybirdge Swifts Defeat</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Midfielder Tyrique Hyde gives his thoughts on the Heybridge Swifts defeat and talks about being captain for the game last night</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"We put out a young team last night which was good for us and it was a good experience to play against some older and physical players.</div><div ><br /></div><div >I thought that in the first half we didn’t start quickly enough and didn’t have the urgency that we needed, but in the second half I believe we showed that we just weren’t clinical enough in front of goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >I thought that we were the team in the ascendancy before they got the first two goals, but we made some mistakes and when you make mistakes in football you get punished.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the second half their goalkeeper pulled off some great saves and on another day some of them chances would have gone in and we could have won the game but it wasn’t to be.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It was a bit of a surprise when I got told that I was captain but I embraced it. I am confident in myself and I just tried to do my best.</div><div ><br /></div><div >For me and the rest of the young players we have learnt that in first team football if you make mistakes you will get punished, unfortunately that it was happened last night and you have just got to carry on and try again."</div><div ><br /></div><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div></div><div class="copy-paste-block" ><strong><br /></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/hydeesc86292-3455630_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/hydeesc169292-3455631_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-07 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>