<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3456376-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Santathon 2016: Sunday 11th December </headline>
  <page_title>Santathon 2016: Sunday 11th December </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Santathon 2016: Sunday 11th December </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Again Host the Annual Santahon In Aid of St Francis Hospice</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The annual Santathon in aid of St Francis Hospice will again be held this coming Sunday, the 11th December.
<br  /><br  />
Full details can be found on the St Francis Hospice <a href="http://www.sfh.org.uk/santathon" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />
The route is just 5km so why not join the estimated 500 other “Santa’s” for what is always a great family fun event. Check in starts at 9.30am with the run due to commence at 11.00am.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers Chairman, Paul Gwinn JP, who is also a Trustee of the Hospice will again be leading the organising on the day and he stated that “the event has raised many £,000’s over the years for the important work St Francis Hospice does and it is always great to see so many Daggers supporters also supporting such a fantastic charity”.
<br  /><br  />
This year our very own assistant manager, Darren Currie, together with his wife and two children will also be running and he has urged as many supporters as possible to come along as well, maybe even pushing the number nearer the 1,000 mark.
<br  /><br  />
It costs just £12.00 for Adults and £8.00 for children to enter and if you are unable to book a place in advance don’t worry as you will can still register on the day.
<br  /><br  />
The Met forecast for Sunday is dry and bright so we look forward to seeing you on Sunday.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-07 15:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>