<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3458827-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-preview-jordan-maguire-drew-on-the-worthing-fixture-3458827.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Preview: Jordan Maguire-Drew On The Worthing Fixture</headline>
  <page_title>Match Preview: Jordan Maguire-Drew On The Worthing Fixture</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Preview: Jordan Maguire-Drew On The Worthing Fixture</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Jordan Maguire-Drew previews the game this Saturday and gives his thoughts on playing his former club Worthing</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"Training has been sharp this week, we have had a lot of injuries so a rest during the week was well needed and now we are looking forward to the game on Saturday.
<br /><br />
Obviously with the FA Trophy it is a chance to get to Wembley and that is a big thing for the club as you are able to make a lot of money from the tournament.
<br /><br />
I am looking forward to Saturday as I will be playing my old team, which was a good time for me. I was out for four months last year and went on loan to Worthing for the end of the season, done well and managed to get some goals.
<br /><br />
We play with a freedom and I don’t think we should fear any team we play, we always find little gaps and play good balls in behind the defence and always create a lot of chances and our forward players are unbelievable and our back four and midfielders and strong and solid as well.
<br /><br />
It was a good result for the team last week as it breaks up the little blip we had at home and I am sure we will put it right Saturday and then start to push on.
<br /><br />
Corey Whitely can draw defenders in to him and then that creates space out wide for myself and he always makes good runs in behind and I think me and him have a good partnership together.
<br /><br />
I am happy and settled here and I want to stay, but we will have to see what happens come January, I want to concentrate on my football but my aim is to help get the club back into the Football League as it is a great club."
<br /><br /></div><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.
<br /><br /></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jmd86292-3457926_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jmd169292-3457928_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-09 16:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>