<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3460974-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-0-0-worthing-3460974.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Worthing</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Worthing</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Worthing</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham and Redbridge were knocked out in the first round proper of the FA Trophy by Worthing.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Paul Benson’s first half goal gave the Daggers the lead, but that was cancelled out by two second half goals, the first a Josh Staunton own goal and the winner was by Lloyd Dawes.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Two changes were made to the Daggers after last week’s away victory at Dover, Luke Guttridge and Elliot Justham, were both swapped for Frankie Raymond and Mark Cousins.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It was the visitors who had the better of chances in the first ten minutes of the game, but they weren’t enough to test Cousins. </div><div ><br /></div><div >17 minutes into the game and Worthing looked to have been one up, after Omar Bugiel’s shot managed to beat Cousins, but it ended up coming off the post.</div><div ><br /></div><div >A minute later, Paul Benson played whitely through the middle of the Worthing defence, however the forward was unable to keep his shot on target.  </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers took the lead five minutes before half time, it was Paul Benson who tapped it into an open goal. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Corey Whitely had a chance a minute into the second half, as he cut in from the right and curled it towards goal, the shot ended up being easily caught by Jack Fagan. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Jordan Maguire-Drew showed great individual play in the 53rd minute, as he beat his marker and cut in, but the final shot was poor. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Minutes later and Maguire-Drew was still creating chances as he played a low ball across goal, Benson was then close to getting on the end of it.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The visitors got the equaliser in the 63rd minute, Josh Staunton put it into the back of his own net after Will Hendon crossed the ball into the box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Lloyd Dawes came very close to scoring a spectacular, as he controlled it in mid-air and volleyed from the edge of box, however the ball ended up inches over the crossbar.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Seconds later the goal came for the visitors an Error from Magnus Okuonghae enabled Dawes to run onto goal and put it past Cousins in the 71st minute. </div><div ><br /></div><div >Dawes came very close to getting a third for Worthing, but Cousins did well to deny him at the near post.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers will now need to focus on next week’s league match against Solihull Moors.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers: Cousins, Widdowson, Doe, Raymond, Assombalonga (45 Hawkins), Benson (78 White), Maguire-Drew (88 Heard), Boucaud, Whitely, Okuonaghae, Staunton</div><div >Unused subs: Justham, Gordon</div><div ><br /></div><div >Worthing: Fagan, Hendon, Rents, Wills, Cook, Heath, Dawes, O'Neill (69 Edwards), Bugiel, Newton, Sparks (88 Brodie)</div><div >Unused subs: Belward, Boiling, Watson</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-10 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>