<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3463928-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-2-1-cambridge-united-3463928.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 2 - 1 Cambridge United</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 2 - 1 Cambridge United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 2 - 1 Cambridge United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Cruise to Cambridge Victory</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[An 84th minute header completed a sensational comeback as the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s came from a goal down to beat Cambridge United’s Academy in a riveting ninety minutes of football.
<br  /><br  />
Brimming with enthusiasm and energy, an upbeat Dagenham &amp; Redbridge were in full control throughout the contest, despite falling behind in the first-half, when the away number eight swept into the far corner after the hosts surrendered possession from a throw.
<br  /><br  />
But striker Dylan Florence preserved his impressive goal scoring streak with a finely curled effort that brought his side back on level terms.
<br  /><br  />
Prior to the winner, Blue Gallagher was presented with arguably the best chance of the encounter to steer the hosts towards three vital points, but couldn’t divert the ball goal wards from a powerful right-wing cross.
<br  /><br  />
Little did it matter however, as the Daggers perseverance and belief, matched by an admirable exhibition of skill and quality, paid off in the closing stages to give the hosts a confidence-boosting win.
<br  /><br  />
Ideally, today’s result would have been the Daggers’ second consecutive victory following last week’s classy display at home to Peterborough United, where the hosts did just about everything but score having completely dominated the tie but been stunted by a lack of cutting edge in the final third, failing to take key chances when it mattered.
<br  /><br  />
This time, they were not, as a flamboyant and visionary Daggers side that set the pitch alight with their positivity and ambition looked much sharper in front of goal, evidenced by the quality of Florence and Turvey’s efforts.
<br  /><br  />
Maybe the east London outfit should have registered two or three more strikes on the scoreboard given the immense volume of chances they created, but will undoubtedly be delighted with their match-winning performance, and rightly so.
<br  /><br  />
They were on top from the get-go, and nearly took an early lead when James Turvey met Harvey Brown’s cross, but the forward’s downward header was smothered by the U’s goalkeeper.
<br  /><br  />
The hosts moved the ball around swiftly and confidently, much to the frustration of a powerless U’s side that could scarcely get a touch in, and were lucky to escape going a goal down when volleys from Elliot Bonds and Harvey Brown were blocked either side of Blue Gallagher’s attempt to tuck in the rebound from Bonds’ shot.
<br  /><br  />
Given the nature of the tie, a Daggers goal was almost inevitable by this point, but the away side stunned when they drew the first blood against the run of play, as the U’s number three took possession and worked his way deep into the Daggers penalty area before pulling back for his teammate to sweep a mid-height shot into the far corner.
<br  /><br  />
It was a goal that could have, and should have, been avoided, as the hosts carelessly surrendered possession following a throw-in close to their own area.
<br  /><br  />
But Micah Hyde’s side demonstrated great spirit to bounce back and resume their domination of the game, with Dylan Florence almost profiting from a defensive error after seizing possession, but the forward’s shot was blocked by the last standing defender, and David Agboola, powerfully bombing forward from his right-back position, sent in an inviting cross that just evaded several Daggers boots.
<br  /><br  />
Elliot Bonds, who cut a busy figure in an energetic Daggers midfield, played a big part in the next two chances that fell the host’s way.
<br  /><br  />
The central midfielder tried for goal with a half-volley after finding space 25-yards out, but unluckily sliced high and wide of goal, before his tremendous tackle dispossessed a forward-breaking U’s man before releasing Florence to feed wide man Jordy Mongoy, who couldn’t quite organise his feet amidst a crowd of advancing defenders.
<br  /><br  />
Having undeservedly gone into half-time a goal down, the hosts returned with a real sense of determination and hunger to turn the game on its head, and they could not have wished for a better start.
<br  /><br  />
Barely two minutes into the second half, Dylan Florence equalised fantastically, collecting from Mongoy’s prodded cross and holding off his man before turning and curling in off the post with a low ten-yard effort.
<br  /><br  />
It was clever play from left winger Mongoy that brought about the leveler, and further skill from the wide man nearly gave the Daggers the ascendancy, but his inviting cross was cleared to safety before a cross from the opposite flank deflected the wrong way off a helpless Blue Gallagher, and James Turvey saw a low shot from distance turned round the post.
<br  /><br  />
After a Daggers man was felled forty yards from goal, the Daggers committed several men forward to attack the resulting free-kick that was launched into the box by midfielder Harvey Brown, and James Turvey, met it with a flicked header into the far corner to earn the hosts a much-warranted victory from a thorough display.
<br  /><br  />
After the game, Academy Head coach Micah Hyde reflected on a pleasing performance:
<br  /><br  />
“I liked the way they performed today, I’ve asked the players to show more quality, and they did that today. The attitude of the group is very good and I’m starting to see consistent signs of independent learning, among the players” said Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“Maybe there were two or three occasions our game understanding in final third could have been better, but overall it was a well-deserved win, but it’s important they understand how, and apply this to continually get positive performances,” continued the Coach.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1. Joe Carter, 2. David Agboola, 3. Deniz Alici, 4. Harvey Brown, 5. Jack Lee, 6. Scott Mitchell (C), 7. James Turvey, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Dylan Florence, 10. Blue Gallagher, 11. Jordy Mongoy, 12. Paul Symes, 14. Mustaphe Ali, 15. Kieran Walker-Brown.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-12 12:00:15 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>