<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3464691-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/st-francis-hospice-santathon-2016-3464691.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Saint Francis Hospice Santathon 2016</headline>
  <page_title>Saint Francis Hospice Santathon 2016</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Saint Francis Hospice Santathon 2016</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The annual St Francis Hospice Santathon took place last Sunday around the streets of Dagenham; starting and finishing at the Chigwell Construction Stadium.   </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Over 300 hundred competed including the Dagger’s assistant manager Darren Currie, his wife and two children, as well as other clubhouse staff. Runners were dressed predominantly in Santa suits with some dressing up as snowmen and reindeer along with their dogs also adorning Christmas outfits. Santa’s from “Cone of Thrones” also made an appearance!
<br  /><br  />
The winner completed the 5km course in a time of 19minutes 4 seconds, but the real winner was Saint Francis Hospice who hope to beat last year’s amount raised of over £18,000.
<br  /><br  />
A special mention to the all those who helped out on the day including the clubs staff, stewards, St John Ambulance and police, ensuring the event went smoothly.
<br  /><br  />
The event was followed by a Christmas Market and a Light Up a Life event all to support the Hospice.
<br  /><br  />
Paul Gwinn, Trustee at Saint Francis Hospice and Daggers Chairman said “Next year’s Santathon will take place on Sunday 10th December 2017 so please make a note in your diary. It really is a fun morning and all in aid of our local Hospice.”
<br  /><div ><br /></div><div >Other pictures from the event can be viewed at our photographers, TGSPhoto, website <a href="http://tgsphoto.photoshelter.com/gallery-slideshow/G0000FUvdDzRb9xw/C00002tPrMzpnWE8?start">here</a>. </div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/santathonrun86292-3466361_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/santathonrun169292-3466362_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-13 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>