<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3465770-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-scott-doe-on-the-defeat-to-worthing-3465770.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: Scott Doe On The Defeat To Worthing</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: Scott Doe On The Defeat To Worthing</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: Scott Doe On The Defeat To Worthing</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Captain Scott Doe gives his thoughts on being knocked out of the Buildbase FA Trophy by Worthing on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["There was some hard words said from myself and a couple others at half time and again from the manager after full time which is rightly so as there is no excuse for Saturday.
<br  /><br  />
Personally I think that when we play away from home we play more percentage football and we play in the opposition half more.
<br  />
 
<br  />
At home maybe we seem to think that we can turn up as this is our home ground and play football, which we can, but it is not happening at the moment for us so personally it think that we may have to go back to the way we are away from home at home until we are able to turn it around.
<br  /><br  />
The manager has rightly said that you are going to get beat in football and it is how you get beat. On Saturday we allowed ourselves to get beat we didn’t pass, or battle we made errors and we were not doing the things that are the basics in football.
<br  /><br  />
We want to put on performances for our fans, the staff and ourselves but we are not doing that, at the moment the manner of the defeat is hard to take but we will need to put it to one side when we are back into training on Monday.
<br  /><br  />
The FA Trophy was a chance to play at Wembley and I have been lucky enough to play there, but not many players get too and I would have loved to go back there as it was a great place to play.
<br  />
 
<br  />
It is hard as we believe with what we have in or squad we would have had a very good chance of going there but they fully deserved the win on Saturday and we will have to just concentrate on the league now."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/scottdoeworthing86292-3466307_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/scottdoeworthing169292-3466309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-13 11:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>