<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3465313-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/post-match-reaction-john-still-on-the-worthing-defeat-3465313.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Post Match Reaction: John Still On The Worthing Defeat</headline>
  <page_title>Post Match Reaction: John Still On The Worthing Defeat</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Post Match Reaction: John Still On The Worthing Defeat</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts on the Buildbase FA Trophy defeat to Worthing on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["They were the better team and I thought that we were fortunate to be in front and I think they deservedly equalised. Their second goal was a Sunday league type of goal from our point of view, but it was a good goal from them.
<br  /><br  />
I tried to tell the players that when we play here we have to play different to when we are playing away. We haven’t got natural wingers in our team, so we have to work the ball and to do that we have to move the ball quickly.
<br  /><br  />
On Saturday we never moved the ball quick enough and we scored a goal through Paul Benson but apart from that we had about two other shots that I can remember.
<br  /><br  />
Sometimes you can get some complacency but I didn’t see that on Saturday and I can see some players trying too hard to be good at home instead of being effective.
<br  /><br  />
We always want to play football, but sometimes you don’t get into the areas to play how you want to play and we said before the game that Worthing would sit two players in the midfield in front of the back four.
<br  /><br  />
What we had to do was to try and get past them, and we had to get the first pass behind their midfield quickly and we weren’t doing that.
<br  /><br  />
With Okenabirhie, Robson Williams and Ling I would say that they are still another three weeks away and the injuries are not clearing up quickly, but the result on Saturday was not to do with injuries.
<br  /><br  />
The injuries have been a problem for us, home and away, and we do need to give some players a rest.
<br  /><br  />
I have no problems with being beat, playing the way you want to play you are going to get beat sometimes, I have been beaten before and it will happen again.
<br  /><br  />
But on Saturday we didn’t play the way we wanted to play or the way we had to play. We have been doing it perfectly away from home but not so much at home.
<br  /><br  />
It could be down to personnel as Okenabirhie gives us power going in behind defenders so we are missing that, Robinson gives us great energy in midfield to win the ball back early which we haven’t got at the minute.
<br  /><br  />
We have struggled for a right back without Williams, Josh Staunton has done a good job there but we haven’t got the natural right back to get forward and support the wide player and get balls into the box."
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jstill86292-3465308_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jstill169292-3465309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-12 17:59:31 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>