<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3466843-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Daggers v Solihull Moors 17th December 2016</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers v Solihull Moors 17th December 2016</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers v Solihull Moors 17th December 2016</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Christmas Special</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[To get everyone in the Christmas spirit and to thank all our loyal supporters and welcome all the “<a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/friends-for-a-fiver-solihull-moors-braintree-town-3443342.aspx" >Friends for a Fiver</a>” guests the Club will be slashing its bar prices throughout the Club House from opening at 11.00am right through till 8.00pm.
<br  /><br  />
For this day only all draft beers and premium bottle beers will be just £2.50 a pint / bottle. A glass of wine just £2.00 and a half pint of draft lemonade or coca cola just 50p.
<br  /><br  />
Saturday is a very busy day at the Club.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Firstly there is our important Vanarama National League match v Solihull Moors where the Daggers look to reverse recent poor home form and return to winning ways in the race at the top of the table. 
<br  />
But for supporters looking to top and tail there will also be live HD Premier League action throughout the Club when Crystal Palace take on Chelsea at 12.30 and then later in the day action from the Hawthorns where West Brom entertain Man Utd at 5.30.
<br  /><br  />
For supporters and friends wishing to enjoy a more traditional evening the Club’s annual <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/dagenham-redbridge-christmas-carol-concert-2016-3458581.aspx" >Christmas Carol Concert</a> commences at 5.30 in the Traditional Builders Stand.
<br  /><br  />
To help finish the day a free buffet will be served in the Victoria Lounge from 6.15.
<br  /><br  />
This will be the Daggers last home game until the 2nd January and hopefully our Christmas Special will give everyone that opportunity to raise a festive glass or two with their fellow supporters, toast our success so far and to the second half of the campaign yet to come.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-16 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Community,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>