<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3471207-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Football Weekend At The Daggers: 17th December</headline>
  <page_title>Football Weekend At The Daggers: 17th December</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Football Weekend At The Daggers: 17th December</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Enjoy a packed weekend of football at the Daggers Bar. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers bar will show West Brom's home game against Manchester United on BT Sport which kicks off at 5:30pm on Saturday. To get everyone in the Christmas spirit and to thank all our loyal supporters the Club will be slashing its bar prices throughout the Club House from opening at 11.00am right through till 8.00pm. 
<br  /><br  />
For this day only all draft beers and premium bottle beers will be just £2.50 a pint / bottle. A glass of wine just £2.00 and a half pint of draft lemonade or coca cola just 50p. Full details can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/daggers-v-solihull-moors-17th-december-2016-3466843.aspx" >here</a>. 
<div ><br /></div><div >Football Sundays will also be back between 1:00-7:00pm on Sunday with Bournemouth hosting Southampton in the South Coast derby which kicks off at 1:30pm and Manchester City taking on Arsenal in a battle between two teams in the title race, with a 4:00pm kick off. 
<br /><br />
Take advantage of the Football Sundays offers on selected drinks at £2.49, which include; Carling, Cask Ale, Bottle Coors, Carling English Cider and Koppaberg. <strong>Please note that these offers are for the Sunday only.</strong><br /><br />
These offers are open to members only. Season ticket holders are automatically members but anyone wishing to buy a membership on the day can do so by asking a member of bar staff. So make sure you buy your membership for just £2!</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/newgen86292-3115254_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/newgen169292-3115256_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-16 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>