<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3471212-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Interview: Oliver Hawkins Ahead Of Solihull Moors</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Oliver Hawkins Ahead Of Solihull Moors</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Oliver Hawkins Ahead Of Solihull Moors</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Oliver Hawkins talks ahead of the of Solihull Moors game this Saturday, after his hat-trick against them at the start of the season. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[We caught up with Daggers’ top goal scorer Oliver Hawkins after the squads training session today to discuss his thoughts going into Saturday’s fixture against Solihull Moors.
<br  /><br  />
Although Oliver Hawkins has been struggling with an injury in his back the forward has returned to training and is ready for the game Saturday “I am feeling fit again after the little knock that I had which put me out for a week, but I am back in full training now working hard and trying to get back into the team and we are looking forward to the game on Saturday.”
<br  /><br  />
With Hawkins being out of the starting 11 for the past two games it has given a chance to Veteran Daggers striker Paul Benson to fill his boots and with Benson scoring in both games, the manager will have a tough choice when it comes to selection for the positon come Saturday. “I love pressure and having people fighting for places and I am glad that Benson has got two goals in the previous two games as he deserves it and has done really well.”
<br  /><br  />
“All, strikers will go through periods where they can’t score and at the moment I am going through that period but I am just going to keep getting into the box and the chances and goals will come.” The leagues previous top goal scorer has not scored since mid-November when scoring the opener against York and since then has had to play out of position filling in at centre half and suffered an injury but Hawkins told us he is confident he can pick it up on Saturday “It feels like I haven’t scored in a while but hopefully I can get back into the goals on Saturday and repeat what I done against them earlier in the season.” The last time that we played Solihull Moors, Oliver Hawkins was in the middle of his goal streak scoring three goals in our home fixture against Wrexham and grabbing another hat-trick against tomorrow's opposition on Saturday 10th September.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-16 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>