<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3472185-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-solihull-moors-preview-3472185.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Solihull Moors Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Solihull Moors Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Solihull Moors Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>John Still previews the home game against Solihull Moors on Saturday and talks about our recent home form. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“ This week not a lot has changed in regards to injuries, same group of players training today as there has been in previous weeks. It’s the case at the moment of trying to find as many round pegs to fit as many round holes as possible.”
<br  /><br  />
“Guttridge missed last week’s game and I wouldn’t say he was injured but we did bring him back reasonably quickly off the back of his injuries and he played quite a few games, so the medical team felt that he should have a rest but he is back in training this week. So this week we are one player better off than last week, it will be a similar group of players that we would have chosen from in the Dover game.”
<br  /><br  />
“Paul Benson has been getting more game time recently and is gradually getting fitter, Hawkins had the back problem and couldn’t play in our game against Dover. Our intention Saturday was just to play him 45 minutes, I didn’t know at the time where I would play him but we was always going to give him 45 minutes just to see how he was. Oliver is back in training this week so he is now back in the frame and we’ll have to decide what setup we are going to go with for Saturday.”
<br  /><br  />
“I’ve never lacked response from players at this club, it’s strange this weird and wonderful game we have. When we went to York we were improving daily we went there and won, we went to Maidstone we won and we went to Dover and we won, but these were not just wins these were convincing wins with really pleasing performances.”
<br  /><br  />
“Then we look at the home games and it’s a completely different story. One of the things we’ve tried to look at this week is how we are changing the side because if we change one player we normally have to change three positions. For example if I put Frankie Raymond in at left back, it then means I have got bring some into the midfield and then bring someone else into the squad and the changes add up. At home where we are expected to have the ascendancy but we don’t seem to be really of got into our stride, I always feel at home we are always trying to get into our stride. As a team we have had to compromise with the structure due to our injuries and I don’t think we done that particularly well on Saturday, I don’t particularly think that in the other home defeats I just don’t think that the teams shape and how we went about playing against Barrow and Gateshead we were at our best.”
<br  /><br  />
“We have to improve from Saturday and as I said before in training this week we’ve been trying to get as many round pegs in round holes, if we can do that we’ll find our way back to winning home and away.”
<br  /><br  />
“I get dismayed with football to be honest over the years, I think they are some wonderfully talented young English Managers around that for whatever reason have had to leave their club and they’re not going to get another chance. I really find it difficult to understand all of the reasons behind it, we have just seen it with Gary Rowett at Birmingham and I really do not know what the answer is. The way I see English football at the moment is within 5 years I’m not sure how many English managers will be managing in the Premier League.”
<br  /><br  />
“We expect at tough game Saturday as they all our in this league, but I never really worry about the opposition before a game, I always feel if my team is right the other team has got to be good and if the team are better than you sometimes that is the case in football and we have to accept that. I point out to players that we’ve already got results from most of the teams we are battling for the promotion spots, so whenever we play the so called better teams we don’t get beaten very often, we always looks proper competitive. As the season has gone along perhaps at home I think we have lost a bit of shape of how we do things that is not a criticism of anybody, I think it is just criticism of the situation we find ourselves in.”
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jstill86292-3465308_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jstill169292-3465309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-16 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>