<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3474399-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-4-4-solihull-moors-3474399.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 4 - 4 Solihull Moors</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 4 - 4 Solihull Moors</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 4 - 4 Solihull Moors</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge played out a thrilling 4-4 draw with Solihull Moors in the National League.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Daggers made four changes for the clash, with Elliot Justham, Oliver Hawkins, Luke Guttridge and Tyrqiue Hyde coming in to the starting line-up.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Inside three minutes, Daggers fell behind when Harry White found the net from the edge of the area.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Two minutes later, a Corey Whitely cross found Hawkins in the box, but the striker nodded wide.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 19th minute, Daggers conceded a second when Omari Sterling found the net for Moors from 25 yards.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Six minutes later, the Essex club let in a third when Jack Byrne slammed home a rebound from close range.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 34th minute, Daggers were handed a route back into the match when Scott Doe turned in a header from Hawkins on the line.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Seven minutes later, Hyde scored his first Daggers goal when slotting the ball past Daniel Lewis in the Solihull goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >In the 49th minute, Daggers fell two goals adrift once more as Sterling rounded Justham before slotting home.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With seven minutes remaining, Hawkins tapped in from close range for a third Daggers goal of the match.</div><div ><br /></div><div >And just two minutes later, the Essex club were level when Whitely struck from close range.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-17 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>