<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3474610-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/john-gowens-injury-update-3474610.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>John Gowens: Injury Update</headline>
  <page_title>John Gowens: Injury Update</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>John Gowens: Injury Update</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Physio John Gowens gives an injury update on the players who are out injured at the moment</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[We start off with Luke Pennell who attained an ACL injury in pre-season. He is making very good progress and has been out on the training field doing some ball work and some very light jogging with Dave Richardson who is now back with the staff.
<br  /><br  />
Luke Howell, who has had another cartilage operation, saw a consultant last Friday and he has been given the go ahead to progress on with his rehabilitation. Luke’s knee is very good according to the surgeon who is very pleased with the progress he is making.
<br  /><br  />
Craig Robson has a medial knee ligament problem and went to see the consultant on the same day as Luke Howell. Craig has done everything that we’ve asked of him, including ball work, running, twisting and turning, but the one thing he has not been able to do properly is strike the ball. This is a common issue associated with this type of injury. Over a period of time the injury tends to settle down, but with Craig this has not been the case. As a result, we had the injury injected and we’ll be looking to start picking up his workload again in the coming days.
<br  /><br  />
Matt Robinson has suffered a fracture and he will be going back to the consultant on December 20th. He will have his injuries re-x-rayed to see how the calcification of the fracture is healing. If everything is ok, he can have his foot put into a boot which will allow him to participate in particular rehab work which we will then monitor. Curtley Williams is another one set to see a consultant - this time on Wednesday. It is looking increasingly as though he will require a jab to settle his knee down due to some slight infusion and swelling on the injury. Hopefully we can get that done this week so it is sorted.
<br  /><br  />
Moving to Fejiri Okenabirhie, hehad an MRI scan which showed some bone bruising. This a very strange type of injury where you can’t really do a lot with outside means to speed up the healing process. There is no operation or jab that will settle it down and unfortunately it just takes time. At the moment he is focusing on twisting and turning and side foot volleys, with his main issue – like Craig Robson – that of striking the ball. Fejiri can only really feel the injury when he points his foot down (similar to a ballerina’s position), so it’s all about managing it to the best of our capabilities and allowing it to settle down.
<br  /><br  />
Sam Ling who had a thigh strain will hopefully will be back in training next week. He has progressed very well and is another person who has done everything asked of him in his rehabilitation. He should be back in the manager’s plans very soon.
<br  />
Clearly, the treatment room has been every busy with regards to the injury’s we’ve had which has prompted people to ask questions which is only natural. When you compare our injury list with other teams’; for example West Ham who have had a tough time with injuries, you can see that we’re not alone in having a lot of players out. Unfortunately for us, however, our injuries have all come to key players.
<br  /><br  />
In terms of staff we’ve brought Dave Richardson back and his help has been invaluable on the rehabilitation side of things. We also have Sarah Halton who has taken over from Darren Gildersleeve in looking after the youth team and we also have an intern, Michael Staggs, so we have plenty of hands on deck, all of whom have been a massive help with the workload we’ve had of late. Hopefully over the Christmas period we can get people back to fitness and back available for the manager on a Saturday.Maybe then I can put my feet up!
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/injuryupdate86292-3474946_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/injuryupdate169292-3474951_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-17 22:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Injury,Team</Tags>
</News>