<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3477624-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/john-still-post-solhull-moors-3477624.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>John Still Post Solihull Moors</headline>
  <page_title>John Still Post Solihull Moors</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>John Still Post Solihull Moors</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers manager John Still discusses Saturday's whirlwind performance against Solihull Moors </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“I really don’t know where we to start with Saturday’s result, I can tell you we conceded 5 against Gateshead which can happen its football, we conceded 4 against Barrow and we’ve conceded 4 today. I can make as many excuses about back four changes as I like but the end story is we’re not defending at home, away we are fine but our home record in the last three games has been probably the worst in the league. We done unbelievable to come back and as the manager to be honest I wasn’t sure if we could but we did and that is a positive but we have got to defend better at home.
<br  /><br  />
We lack knowledge and experience and when I brought Paul Benson on I actually wanted to bring the young striker Joe White on but I brought Paul on because of his experience we haven’t got nowhere near enough of it but that’s okay. When we started the season we was fully aware how the budget was and I was fully aware that we was going to have to work hard with young players so I have no problems with that, the problems I have got is we shouldn’t be conceding two fours and a five at home. 
<br  /><br  />
When we come back to Victoria road in the New Year I would have been at the club for a year, looking back at the year I wasn’t happy we got relegated, I’m happy we have responded in the league to being in that top group and we need to push on into the second half of the season. If I look back on this season it’s probably gone as well on the pitch as I actually could have hoped, up until quite late really we were very young and very naïve but we’ve been able to find a way to keep going.
<br  /><br  />
Local derbies are good games to play at Christmas time so I look forward to it, I look forward to all the games but I like the closeness between the two teams and to come up against my good friend Hakan Hayrettin will be good.”      
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jstill86292-3465308_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jstill169292-3465309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-19 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>