<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3479019-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/tyrique-hyde-on-his-first-goal-for-the-club-3479019.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Tyrique Hyde On His First Goal For The Club</headline>
  <page_title>Tyrique Hyde On His First Goal For The Club</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Tyrique Hyde On His First Goal For The Club</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We talk to Daggers youngster Tyrique Hyde to find out what it meant to him to score his first goal for the club</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["Saturday’s game was an exciting game to play in, it wasn’t the result we were looking for but nevertheless I think the players showed great character to come back and draw the game.
<br  /><br  />
It was my first league start, I was told by the manager the day before the game and I had mixed emotions going into the game, I was nervous but really excited to get out there and play my game and the goal is obviously a bonus.
<br  /><br  />
I don’t think we deserved to be 3-0 down but we was and it was just about finding our feet again and playing how we know we can play, when we find the intensity and the urgency that we needed we got the two goals back quickly and went into half time looking like we could come out and win the game, but obviously it wasn’t to be.
<br  /><br  />
When I was in front of goal I had a moment to compose myself before shooting, it did seem like the world stopped for a moment after the first touch and it felt like I had all the time in the world to slot the ball away. The goal I scored in was in front of the stand my family were in so it’s nice to celebrate in front of them and the academy players were also up there as well and without both of them I wouldn’t be where I am today.
<br  /><br  />
When I came off the pitch I just wanted the team to push on and win the game and grab the three points. It was nerve-racking to watch the game from the side-lines especially when we had a few chances to win the game in the dying embers.
<br  /><br  />
I’m grateful I’ve been given the chance to be in the starting eleven, I’m learning each day by getting information from the coaches and the players and see where it takes me. Guttridge and Boucaud helped me massively on the pitch on Saturday but not only that they help me in training to improve my game and I’m very grateful for that."
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/hydeesc86292-3455630_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/hydeesc169292-3455631_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-20 11:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>