<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3480674-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/ramsey-moore-community-cup-u14-tournament-3480674.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Ramsey Moore Community Cup U14 Tournament</headline>
  <page_title>Ramsey Moore Community Cup U14 Tournament</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Ramsey Moore Community Cup U14 Tournament</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Saturday's Community Cup Winners CM Futsal Academy won the entire tournament without losing a single game</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Our game against Solihull Moors on Saturday saw our second Tournament of this year’s Ramsey Moore Community Cup; we were joined by 6 local football teams at Goals in Dagenham for a two hour tournament before the day’s game.
<br  /><br  />
The teams that took part consisted of players from CM Futsal Academy, The Flyers, Goodmayes, Little Thurrock Dynamos and Loass Hurricanes. It was a great contest with some great football on display throughout the entire tournament. Our winners CM Futsal Academy defeated all competition and beat runners up The Flyers to win the tournament unbeaten.
<br  /><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge and Ramsey Moore would like to thank all of the teams who competed and hope they enjoyed the day. The next Tournament will be for U13 teams taking place on the 21st January for our game against Bromley.
<br  /><br  />
To book your team in for this tournament or for any enquires about the tournament please contact our commercial department by phone: 020 8592 1549 ext: 33 or by email: <a href="mailto:%20commercial@daggers.co.uk" >commercial@daggers.co.uk
<br /></a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/ramseymooreccu1486292-3480666_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/ramseymooreccu14169292-3480667_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-21 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>