<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3483566-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/joe-widdowson-previews-the-braintree-town-double-fixture-3483566.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Joe Widdowson Previews the Braintree Town Double Fixture</headline>
  <page_title>Joe Widdowson Previews the Braintree Town Double Fixture</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Joe Widdowson Previews the Braintree Town Double Fixture</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Player interviews defender Joe Widdowson on the upcoming Braintree Town double fixture over the holiday period</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“Looking back to Saturday I think we have to look at the whole game, obviously it was disappointing to go 3-0 down I don’t think we deserved to be 3-0 down at any point in the match. Our defending was not good enough but then again I thought it was a great effort from everyone to come back and score four goals especially when coming from three behind to get a draw that’s definitely a positive.
<br  /><br  />
We’ve been conceding too many goals at home there’s no doubt about that, we are much tighter away from home which is strange. I think at home we are more expansive and attacking which we want to be but earlier on in the season we were keeping the ‘back door shut’ and not conceding as many. I can’t put the blame on one reason why we are conceding, the team has had to change a lot due to injuries, people playing different positions so we haven’t had a settled back four for a long time. Although I do not think it’s just down to the back four it’s down to the whole team to ensure we keep it tight and make it hard for the opposition to break us down and at the moment it’s been too easy for teams to score against us.  
<br  /><br  />
Over Christmas we are aiming to do the double over Braintree, getting back to back wins will help us get back on track in the league. Obviously they will be tough games like the Solihull game was we definitely won’t be taking these games lightly or underestimating them. We will be going into the two games looking for the win and it will be good to end the year with a win and start 2017 positively. 
<br  /><br  />
I think as a team we have done really well, I think it’s been a great effort from all the players and the staff. Considering some of the players the amount of football they have been playing and due to injuries some players have had to fill in for the players who cannot play. Hopefully though in the New Year the injured players will start to return and be ready for the second half of the season and come in and make the squad stronger. We are still in a good position, the top teams seem to be changing all the time so as long as we can keep in that pack we can try and make a late surge for promotion.”
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/joewiddowson86292-3483551_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/joewiddowson169292-3483554_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-23 10:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>