<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3483040-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-preview-john-still-on-braintree-town-3483040.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Preview: John Still On Braintree Town</headline>
  <page_title>Match Preview: John Still On Braintree Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Preview: John Still On Braintree Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts ahead of the double header of fixtures against Braintree Town </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >"At home we are conceding too many goals but away from home we have been very good. The pleasing aspect from the Solihull Moors game was the fact that we scored four goals and managed to get ourselves back from 3-0 down to get a draw.
<br /><br />
We have changed a little bit out training and it has been difficult with Raymond playing midfield and left back, Widdowson playing right and left back, and also Staunton moving from right back into centre back.
<br /><br />
We have lacked a bit of cohesion defensively and with all the injuries defensively we have struggled all season to have a settled back four.
<br /><br />
At the moment, especially at home where you expect to have the ascendancy, we have been hit by the counter attack too many times at home, but we have worked on that again this week and hopefully we can rectify that.
<br /><br />
All of the young players like Tyrique and Joe White have done well and even players like Whitely and Hawkins who are inexperienced at this level, their progress this season has been very good.
<br /><br />
Hakan is someone who I took to Luton with me and he done a good job with me there and I believe that he learnt a lot. He got the opportunity at Braintree and he has done well since he has been there.
<br /><br />
We just want to go to Braintree and win the game and I wish Hakan all the best wherever he goes as I believe he has all the ingredients to do well, but I hope that is not in our next two games."
<br /></div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div><div ><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/jstill86292-3465308_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/jstill169292-3465309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-23 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>