<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3487513-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-braintree-town-3-2-dagenham-and-redbridge-3487513.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Braintree Town 3 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Braintree Town 3 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Braintree Town 3 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge suffered a 3-2 loss at Braintree Town in the first part of their National League double header.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Daggers made one change for the trip to Cressing Road, with Sam Ling replacing Luke Guttridge, who missed out through injury.
<br  /><br  />
Inside the first minute at Cressing Road, Corey Whitely saw a free-kick narrowly deflected over by the wall.
<br  /><br  />
It took 27 minutes for the next decent chance to arrive, but Tyrique Hyde saw his effort blocked by Sean Clohessy after being played in by Oliver Hawkins.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers took the lead five minutes later when Jordan Maguire-Drew found Oliver Hawkins with a cross into the box from the right.
<br  /><br  />
The striker headed in his 14th goal of the season, but only after his effort had been pushed onto the post by Town keeper Sam Beasant on its way in.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers were pegged back four minutes later when Michael Cheek lashed home after a spot of ping-pong in the box.
<br  /><br  />
And Daggers went into the break a goal down when Sim Akinola scored a penalty in first half stoppage time after Josh Staunton fouled Reece Hall-Johnson in the box.
<br  /><br  />
Less than 60 seconds into the second half, Daggers were awarded a penalty after Clohessy handled in the box.
<br  /><br  />
Hawkins saw his initial spot kick saved, but Jordan Maguire-Drew slammed in after a melee in the box.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers were reduced to 10 men in the 59th minute when Scott Doe was sent off for a second bookable offence.
<br  /><br  />
And six minutes later, Akinola struck again to send the Iron back in front, though the hosts had Ebou Adams dismissed for a second yellow card with 17 minutes left.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers, though, could not find an equaliser as the lost for the first time in four games on the road.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-27 09:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>