<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3490377-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/darren-currie-previews-the-second-of-the-braintree-town-double-3490377.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Darren Currie Previews the second of the Braintree Town Double</headline>
  <page_title>Darren Currie Previews the second of the Braintree Town Double</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Darren Currie Previews the second of the Braintree Town Double</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Player interviews assistant manager Darren Currie on the upcoming Braintree Town home fixture</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“We was very comfortable at 1-0, I thought we started the game really well, we got our opportunity to score which was a great ball in and a good goal from Hawkins. One little poor decision and an organisation problem that we had mentioned previously and they found themselves getting the equaliser and getting back in the game, after that it became a bit of a Basketball game attacks coming from either side.
<br  /><br  />
Then the game was turned on its head with the sending off and the injury, going down to 9 men made life very difficult for ourselves, we gave away a cheap penalty. It was another bad day really, it is disappointing at the minute because we did go 1-0 up and should manage the game better when we’re in front.
<br  /><br  />
When we first started changing our back four with Raymond playing left back and Widdowson in right back we were on a very good run. It’s not ideal changing the back four as much as we have been but we have had good form with people out of position and now currently we are in not so good form with players out of position, if we blame it on that too much it becomes an excuse. Our players are good enough they have all proven that we’re just not doing the simple and basic things and we are conceding way too many goals; we are too easy to play against at the minute.
<br  /><br  />
In the early part of the season when we was playing well a lot of the focus in training and our discussions in meetings were all about focusing on us and not so much about the opponent. I don’t think we need to focus too much on Braintree for Monday, we give them the respect they deserve and they’ll be one or two points highlighted. The most important thing is for the group is to get ourselves to the levels we’ve set not so long ago, I think one stat in our favour at the moment is that there is only one or two teams that won more games than us.”
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/darrencurrietorquay-86292-3444707_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/darrencurrietorquay-169292-3444708_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-29 15:30:37 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>