<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3491272-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/live-football-over-the-new-year-3491272.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Live Football Over The New Year</headline>
  <page_title>Live Football Over The New Year</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Live Football Over The New Year</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Come down to the Daggers this weekend to watch live Premier League action including this weekend's two London Derby's </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers will be showing a variety of live Premier League action all over this New Years weekend.
<br  /><br  />
We kick off the action packed weekend tonight at 8pm with struggling Hull City playing at home to Everton off the back of the away sides 2-0 win away to Leicester City.
<br  /><br  />
On Saturday the clubhouse will be closed from 3pm-7pm, all ready for our New Years Family Disco starting at 7pm; click <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/new-years-eve-disco-at-the-daggers-3430504.aspx" >here</a> for full details of the event.
<br  /><br  />
Football Sundays will be back between 12:00-7:00pm on Sunday with two London derby's being shown live on Sky Sports and BT Sport, the first being Watford playing at home to Tottenham Hotspur kicking off at 1:30pm and the second Arsenal versus Crystal Palace at 4pm..
<br  /><br  /><div >Take advantage of the Football Sundays offers on selected drinks at £2.49, which include; Carling, Cask Ale, Bottle Coors, Carling English Cider and Koppaberg. </div><div ><br /></div><div >These offers are open to members only. Season ticket holders are automatically members but anyone wishing to buy a membership on the day can do so by asking a member of bar staff. So make sure you buy your membership for just £2!
<br /><br />
To finish off the weekend of football here at the Daggers, from the great feedback we received from the Solihull Moors game we will be offering the same bar spectacular once again throughout our bars in the clubhouse, so all draft beers and premium bottle beers will again be just £2.50 a pint / bottle. A glass of wine just £2.00 and a half pint of draft lemonade or coca cola just 50p.
<br />
 <span><br /></span> We will also have a full day of Live Premier League action including games from:
<br /><br /><div class="copy-paste-block">Middlesbrough v Leicester City                              KO 12.30pm
<br />
Blackburn Rovers v Newcastle United                    KO  3.00pm
<br />
West Ham United v Manchester United                   KO 5.15pm<span><br /><br /></span></div><div class="copy-paste-block">All this culminating with live action with Dagenham &amp; Redbridge v Braintree Town at the Chigwell Construction Stadium, kicking off at 7.45pm. <span><br /></span></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images/livefootball-86292-3491189_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images/livefootball169292-3491192_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2016-12-30 12:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>