<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3499826-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-joe-widdowson-on-the-home-win-over-braintree-town-3499826.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Joe Widdowson On The Home Win Over Braintree Town</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Joe Widdowson On The Home Win Over Braintree Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Joe Widdowson On The Home Win Over Braintree Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Defender Joe Widdowson talks about the home win over Braintree Town on Monday evening, the Daggers' first home win in six games</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["Yesterday’s win is a great start to the year for the squad, a 3-0 win and a clean sheet we are incredibly happy. In previous games we have conceded goals that we really shouldn’t have so to keep the clean sheet is really pleasing.
<br  /><br  />
With Doe missing out with a two match ban, I was oldest player in the back four although I did think the other three in defence were outstanding. Shaun Donnellan who came into the squad and has only trained about an hour with us, so to come into the team and play as well as he did was brilliant. Again with Staunton he was very solid like he has been throughout the season, Sam Ling has suffered with injuries and has only trained a few times so it was a very mismatch back four but I think the three youngsters did very well.   
<br  /><br  />
Where I have been playing consistently I have been building relationships, if it be Doe when I have been playing on the left or Staunton when playing on the right. It’s all about building relationships with each other and trying to keep it tight, in previous weeks we haven’t been happy with some of the goals we have conceded and we knew we needed to improve so the win and clean sheet was crucial today.
<br  /><br  />
I don’t mind Jordan Maguire Drew having the goal I’ll leave the goals to Jordan, I’m happy for him to score if it was going wide it was good anticipation from him to get onto the back post. I had the opportunity to go forward and I’m happy that I got a chance to create a goal, even better that it was on TV as well.
<br  /><br  />
Jordan Maguire Drew has been very good for us since joining earlier on in the summer, his stats are very good for the club with the amount of assists and goals he has to his name. He’s a young talented player who is learning his trade and I’m sure he will continue to improve.
<br  /><br  />
The last few weeks our form hasn’t been what we want It to be, the manager has said it’s a New Year we want to be trying to stay in and around that top spot, then surge towards the top spot during the end of the season. We are still in and amongst it, no team has really run away with the league just yet, so we have just as much chance as anyone."
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//joewiddowson86292-3483551_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//joewiddowson169292-3483554_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-03 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>