<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3499904-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/support-the-daggers-fund-250-club-3499904.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Support the Daggers Fund 250 Club </headline>
  <page_title>Support the Daggers Fund 250 Club </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Support the Daggers Fund 250 Club </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The "Support the Daggers Fund" 250 club will be running again in 2017 over the next 12 months </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The “Support the Daggers Fund” 250 Club will again be running over the coming 12 months where supporters are again asked to pledge £5.00 per month with the chance of winning monthly prizes of £100.00, £50.00 &amp; £25.00 plus entry into the 2017 Christmas prize, again for £1,000.00, £500.00 &amp; £250.00.
<br  /><br  />
With just 250 members there is a great opportunity to win a prize but with the added bonus of raising over £11,000 per year towards funding our Academy.
<br  /><br  />
In August last year the Support the Daggers Fund donated £20,000 to assist the Daggers Academy and this money is chiefly raised via the 250 Club and the matchday 50/50 draw so your support is greatly appreciated.
<br  /><br  />
The Monthly draw is made on the last home game of every month or during the closed season on the last Sunday of each month.
<br  />
The Grand Annual draw takes place on the nearest home game to Christmas.
<br  />
All prize winners are notified by post and a list of prize winners is published on the Club’s official <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/" >web site</a> and in the matchday programme.
<br  /><br  />
Hopefully existing members will continue their support and will automatically be renewed when subscribing in the same way as they have before.
<br  />
There is however a number of vacancies and new members are welcomed.
<br  /><br  />
Supporters can either pay £5 monthly or £60 annually by way of cheque or monthly standing order.
<br  />
All cheques to be made payable to THE SUPPORT THE DAGGERS FUND.
<br  />
Each participant will be allocated a number for the season and members may hold more than one share.
<br  />
Participants must be 16 or over.
<br  />
For an application form to become a new member please ask in the Club House or download <a xlink:href="tcm:0-550161" title="250 club DEC"   xlink:title="250 club DEC">HERE</a>.
<br  /><br  />
Good luck to all those in Saturday’s draw and thank you to everyone who have contributed over the past 12 months.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//250-club292-259077_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//250-club292-259077_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-01 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>