<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3500754-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-north-ferriby-united-3500754.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: North Ferriby United</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: North Ferriby United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: North Ferriby United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of travelling to the Eon Visual Media Stadium for the Daggers’ fixture against North Ferriby United, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<strong >TRAVELLING BY CAR:</strong><br  />
Follow the M62 Eastbound and continue onto the A63 towards Hull. Stay on the A63 for seven miles until you reach the junction signposted B1231, North Ferriby and Melton Industrial Area. Leave the A63 and at the end of the long slip road you will reach a roundabout where you should take the third exit. At the next roundabout take the first exit towards Swanland and North Ferriby where after a mile you will reach a crossroads where you should turn right into Church Road. After passing the Church on the left, Grange Lane and the ground are slightly further down on the left hand side, but before the railway bridge. Street parking is available on Church Road and the surrounding area.
<br  /><br  /><strong >BY RAIL:</strong><br  />
Ferriby Station is served by trains from Doncaster and Hull, both of which are accessible from London Kings Cross. The cheapest route is splitting your journey into two return tickets from London-Doncaster and then Doncaster-Ferriby which works out at £45 combined for an adult without a railcard. From Ferriby Station proceed directly up the road in front of you and take the first right into New Walk. At the end of this road turn right into Church Road where you will find the entrance to the ground located further down on the left.
<br  /><br  /><strong >SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong><br  />
The Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Supporters’ Club will be running a coach to this fixture at a cost of £21 for members and £26 for non-members. It will depart Victoria Road at 8:45am sharp and will contain a 45 minute service stop en-route. Supporters are advised to book in advance of the Friday in order for places to be allotted on the coach itself.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-north-ferriby-united-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3482285.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-04 11:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>