<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3502550-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Tonight at the Daggers: West Ham United U23 v Norwich City U23</headline>
  <page_title>Tonight at the Daggers: West Ham United U23 v Norwich City U23</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Tonight at the Daggers: West Ham United U23 v Norwich City U23</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Come and watch West Ham’s up and coming talent in their eighth home U23 fixture against Norwich City U23 to see if they can carry on their good form during the season so far</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Just coming off the back of a 4-0 win over fourth place Wolverhampton Wanderers, the Hammers will be looking to get another convincing win over 10th place Norwich and make a challenge for the title this year.  </div><div ><br /></div><div >The game will be played tonight at 7:00pm.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>West Ham United U23 Previous Five Results:</strong></div><div >Wolverhampton Wanderers 0-4 West Ham United
<br />
West Ham 2-3 Swansea City
<br />
West Ham 1-3 Brighton and Hove Albion</div><div >Fulham 4-1 West Ham</div><div >West Ham 1-1 Blackburn Rovers</div><br  /><div >With first team player Sam Byram set to be in West Ham's U23 line up tonight and players such as Sofiane Feghouli and Edimilson Fernandes playing in previous U23 fixtures for West Ham, it makes up for an exciting game of football. The Hammers will want to continue to climb the table after their 4-0 win over Wolves, all in all it’s got the recipe to be a great night of Football here at the Chigwell Construction Stadium. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Night is free for West Ham Season Ticket holders, but everyone is welcome with tickets priced at £5 for adults and £3 concessions. The Clubhouse will be open to enjoy before and after the game.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-09 10:13:19 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>