<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3502251-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-north-ferriby-united-v-dagenham-redbridge-3502251.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: North Ferriby United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: North Ferriby United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: North Ferriby United v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Daggers' Vanarama National League away tie at North Ferriby United on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[North Ferriby United play at Grange Lane which has a total capacity of 2,700, making it the smallest ground at National League level.
<br  /><br  />
The stadium is comprised predominantly of terracing and although the surroundings make it quaint, the ground is well kept and looks smart in its appearance. Both ends behind the goal are made up of uncovered terracing, while a covered stand featuring both terracing and seating runs along the far side of the ground. But it is the West Stand which is the most curious. It is mostly comprised
<br  />
of a flat banking area for spectators, but adjoins in the centre with the clubhouse, players’ dressing rooms and a large green sign that reads ‘North Ferriby United.’
<br  /><br  /><strong >DAGGERS FANS:</strong><br  />
Given the underdeveloped nature of the ground, precautions are not in place to segregate fans so our fixture at Grange Lane will be an unsegregated one. This means that supporters will be allowed to move around the ground at their own leisure.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
North Ferriby is a village of around 4,500 people and as such there isn’t much in the way of chain restaurants or pubs. There is a Sports Bar inside the ground which welcomes away supporters, otherwise the ‘Duke of Cumberland’ pub is around a 10 minute
<br  />
walk away along the main road. Elsewhere you also have ‘Danny’s Bar’ which is less than half-a-mile from the stadium, while the ‘Sandpiper’ also serves food but is a good 20 minute walk away from the stadium. In terms of food only establishments, there is an Italian restaurant called ‘Medici’s’ which is North of the station, while ‘Low Street Pizza’ operates on School Lane which is off of Church Lane heading away from the stadium.
<br  /><br  /><div >Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-north-ferriby-united-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3482285.aspx">here</a>.</div><div ><br /></div><div >An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-north-ferriby-united-3500754.aspx">here</a>.</div><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-06 09:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>