<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3503427-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-shaun-donnellan-on-signing-for-the-daggers-3503427.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Shaun Donnellan On Signing For The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Shaun Donnellan On Signing For The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Shaun Donnellan On Signing For The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Shaun Donnellan gives an exclusive interview to Daggers Player on his debut for the club on Monday and how he is settling into the squad.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“Monday was a good game, obviously they had a player sent off in the first quarter of the match which made the game a bit slower, and we have a really talented group of players here at Dagenham from experienced long season pros to young talents so I’m happy to be here.
<br  /><br  />
There is competition for the centre back spot now but I’ve just go to play well and train well, If I don’t perform on the pitch I’ll get pulled out of the team, there is a lot of competition for places in this team and that’s why Dagenham are high up in the table.
<br  /><br  />
On Monday there was a lot of leaders on the pitch, I was surprised everyone was very vocal and the two players in front of me (Boucaud and Raymond) were fantastic in keeping me in line and telling me if I was doing something wrong but in a positive way.
<br  /><br  />
We are going into Saturday against North Ferriby definitely looking to win, we want to get promoted and hopefully I can play well and impress the management staff.”    
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.</strong></div></div><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//sdonnellan186292-3503424_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//sdonnellan169292-3503415_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-05 16:15:03 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Signing,Team</Tags>
</News>