<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3509275-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Jake Howells</headline>
  <page_title>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Jake Howells</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Jake Howells</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge FC are pleased to announce the signing of 25-year old Jake Howells</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Jake worked his way through the ranks at Luton Town and made his first-team debut on the final day of the 2007/08 season against Huddersfield Town. A regular in the The Hatters side that went on to lift the Football League Trophy at Wembley the following season, he won the club's Young Player of the Season award and he repeated the feat the following two seasons.
<br  /><br  />
When John Still took over as Luton Manager, it was Howells who scored the first goal under his reign in a 1–0 win away to Stockport County and was a virtual ever-present the following season as The Kenilworth Road side won the National League title.
<br  /><br  />
He had a loan spell at Yeovil in 2015 before returning to Luton and, after adding a further 14 appearances, totaled 334 appearances and 31 goals for the Hatters.
<br  /><br  />
His contract was not renewed by Luton and he signed for National League club Eastleigh on a two-year contract, making his debut on the opening day of the season in a 2-1 win at home to Guiseley. His contract was terminated by Eastleigh on 4th January 2017 when manager Martin Allen began reshaping the squad and John Still swooped to sign the left winger.
<br  /><br  />
Jake has played international football for Wales at Under-21 level and for England at C team level.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-09 17:06:30 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Team,Transfer</Tags>
</News>