<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3512041-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-gowens-gives-an-injury-update-on-the-squad-3512041.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Gowens Gives An Injury Update On The Squad</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Gowens Gives An Injury Update On The Squad</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Gowens Gives An Injury Update On The Squad</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Physio John Gowens gives an update on the players that are injured and the players that have recently come back from injury </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Luke Howell is back in full time training coming up to a week now, he’s recovered very well from his operation. For Luke it’s all about building up match fitness, progressing back into games but he has had no reaction in full time training so that’s really good news for him.
<br  /><br  />
Matt Robinson had another X-ray when he visited the consultant last week, he’s now been given the ok to carry on with his rehab. Matt will be doing pool work and we will be increasing his work load over the next coming weeks with Dave Richardson, so for Matt everything seems to be on the up.
<br  /><br  />
Curtley Williams had an injection over the Christmas period he has started his rehabilitation program again specifically tailored for him. He’ll be looking to do that for the next 7-10 days, then hopefully if he suffers no reaction from that then we can progress into running, ball work and then finally full time training again.
<br  /><br  />
Luke Pennell has progressed very well, he’s ahead of schedule. Luke’s been working with Dave Richardson not training but more specific work for example straight line running with sudden stops, accelerating and decelerating. With Luke’s injury you have to be very careful sometimes you can get carried away me and Dave are there to keep the reigns on Luke and to keep him steady so he doesn’t over work himself.  
<br  /><br  />
With Magnus’ knock that he took during the Braintree Town game, as it was such a big hematoma around his face, he had to come off of the pitch as he couldn’t see. Nowadays you have to be very careful with head injuries; there is a lot of protocol. The following Friday he went and saw the club doctor who examined him neurological wise he is fine. Magnus had a head injury four years ago when he played against Dagenham when we played Colchester at their Stadium and Romain Vincelot got injured with him, Magnus got knocked out for a few seconds during that knock and because of that the doctor advised us to it MRI scanned. We got the MRI scans back this week there is no structural problems or injuries so he will be okay to resume training again this week.
<br  /><br  />
Robson and Okenabirhie both returned to the first team on Saturday, both their injuries took a bit longer than we first anticipated but sometimes injuries do happen that way. They’re both back in full time training now, available for the manager in some ways it will be like having two new players into the squad because of the period of time they have been out. So hopefully now they can push on and the competition for places will get harder and tougher for them we players coming back and getting fit.
<br  /><br  />
Corey Whitely was pulled out of training on Thursday with some hamstring problems, more than likely we have examined this a few times and his back is slightly sore so we have been working on his back and building up his core strength but how it has been improving over the last couple of days he will be ready for selection next Saturday. It’s a type of problem you get from players that come from part time training into full time training , where their bodies are exerted that much more instead of when they trained 2 to 3 times a week part time.
<br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a>.<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BXNIP9OwgQY" allowfullscreen="" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0"><br /><br /><br /></iframe></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//injuryupdate86292-3474946_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//injuryupdate169292-3474951_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-11 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Injury,Team</Tags>
</News>