<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3515384-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-fejiri-okenabirhie-on-his-return-after-injury-3515384.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie On His Return After Injury</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie On His Return After Injury</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie On His Return After Injury</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Winger Fejiri Okenabirhie on his return from injury and getting a goal on his first start after being back against North Ferriby United on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >“It’s nice to be back playing football again, it’s been nearly 3 months since I was last playing in a Dagenham shirt. To get a goal and to win the game just makes it even better for me
<br /><br />
The injury that I had was to my ankle and I had severe bone bruising, it took a while for this injury to heal and I am just glad that I am back and playing with the team.
<br /><br />
Having players coming back is what we want after the injuries that we have had and then it is down to the players to perform when they are given the chance.
<br /><br />
We had the period where we had a lot of players out injured, and the players who were playing when we had the injuries, done really well to keep us near the top of the table and in the playoff places.
<br /><br />
Every game now we have got to give 100% as we are going to have a lot of competition to places, so when I am selected I will do my best for the team and help the team to get some wins.”
<br /><br /></div><div ><br /></div><div ><br /></div><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//fejirio86292-3515467_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//fejirio169292-3515468_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-12 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Team</Tags>
</News>