<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3527538-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-elliot-justham-bromley-preview-3527538.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Elliot Justham Bromley Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Elliot Justham Bromley Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Elliot Justham Bromley Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers 'Keeper Elliot Justham Previews the Daggers' Home Fixture Against Bromley This Weekend</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[“We had no game last week but we have been training hard, we had the weekend off but now we are straight back at it this week and the squad looks in good spirit ahead of a tough game on Saturday.
<br  /><br  />
The break was good as it gives a chance for the players who are coming back off injuries and the lads that have come in a chance to bond and work on things at the training ground. There’s competition for places all over and everyone is eager to play Saturday, which is very healthy for the squad.
<br  /><br  />
We had a stage over the Christmas period where we wasn’t playing as we should have been playing; conceding too many goals. It wasn’t just the back four and myself it’s the whole team, it’s a team effort. We don’t see it as a blame game, we had to defend better as a team and like our last two games haved proved, I think people have seen we are back to how we was earlier in the season.
<br  /><br  />
We may have had several changes to the back four this season, but I don’t think this has really effected my play as I know all the boys well. They’re all good enough to do the job so for me there is no preference to who plays there and whoever plays Saturday I’m sure they’ll be looking for a clean sheet as much as I am.
<br  /><br  />
It will be good to have Scott Doe back he’s the captain so everyone respects him very highly and respects everything he does for us on the field, so it’s definitely a boost to have him back from his suspension and I’m sure he will play Saturday.”  
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//justhaminterviewtemplate86292-3527448_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//justhaminterviewtemplate169292-3527454_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-19 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>