<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3527251-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/the-daggers-programme-shop-3527251.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>The Daggers Programme Shop </headline>
  <page_title>The Daggers Programme Shop </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>The Daggers Programme Shop </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers Programme Shop will be open this Saturday, 1st April for our home game against Eastleigh FC, KO 3:00pm</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Programme Shop will be open on Saturday from approximately 12 noon until kick off for our Vanarama National League home fixture against Eastleigh FC and will also be open immediately after the game.
<br  /><br  /><strong >There is a range of different items available from the programme shop including:
<br /></strong> Good selection of current season home and away programmes
<br  />
An excellent current season collection of league and non-league programmes. Many are the result of kind donations from supporters
<br  />
Cup Finals, Internationals, European programmes. There is an excellent range of England internationals
<br  />
All league clubs and many non-league clubs, all London area clubs are available with excellent stocks of Daggers, Arsenal, Tottenham, Chelsea, Southend, Leyton Orient, Gillingham, Charlton and Crystal Palace. Also an excellent selection of West Ham programmes plus general Hammers memorabilia.
<br  />
An excellent range of Badges, Pennants, Team-sheets and Sporting Books
<br  /><br  />
All visitors are welcome inside the Daggers Programme Shop.
<br  /><br  />
Also as an advance notice the Programme Shop "Open Day" will be held on Saturday 27th May 2017 and will be open from 10:30am to 3:00pm.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//newgen86292-3115254_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//newgen169292-3115256_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-28 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>