<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3529058-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-bromley-match-preview-3529058.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Bromley Match Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Bromley Match Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Bromley Match Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Darren Currie previews the National League home fixture against Bromley tomorrow </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["We have got a lot of bodies back in training and we will have a few headaches this week in terms of picking the team which we haven’t had in recent months. We have had a good balance in the last few weeks between rest and hard work and we are raring to go at the weekend now.
<br  /><br  />
We have done well in the last two games keeping two clean sheets and getting seven goals, but with the Bromley game on Saturday we know it will be a tough game as they are direct and have pacey players in their team.
<br  /><br  />
If they have a good day, we know that they are able to cause a lots of problems, but as we have done all season we concentrate on what we do. We have shown signs of us getting back to our best in our attacking play and also defensively keeping clean sheets which means that everyone in the team has been pulling their weight for the team.
<br  /><br  />
The manager is someone who is very experienced and knows this league very well and he said that every team has a sticky patch in a season and our target before Christmas when we had injuries to key players was to stay in and around the play off places.
<br  /><br  />
We managed to do that and we know that we had a bit of a blip where we were conceding far too many goals, but we believe that we have turned that corner now and hopefully the blip is over and we can push on."
<br  /><br  /><div ><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-20 12:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>