<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3534200-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-tranmere-rovers-3534200.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of travelling to Prenton Park for the Daggers’ fixture against Tranmere Rovers, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<strong >TRAVELLING BY CAR:</strong><br  />
From the M6/M56 join the M53 and exit at Junction 4. From here take the B5151 Mount Road from the fourth exit of the roundabout (the ground is signposted from here). After two and- a-half miles, Mount Road will become Storeton Road and from here, you should turn right at the traffic lights which are recognisable by the church on the far right corner. This leads into Prenton Road West and the ground is down this road on the right hand side. There is a car park available for use at the ground, and although street parking is also available there is a strict residents parking scheme in place that supporters should be aware of. Parking is also available at the Birch Tree Pub for £5, the cost of which is refunded against whatever food or drink you may purchase inside.
<br  /><br  /><strong >BY TRAIN:</strong><br  />
Liverpool Lime Street is served by trains from London Euston at a rate of three per hour. The journey takes around two-and-a-half hours and costs £49 for an adult return ticket without a railcard. From Lime Street, supporters are advised that local line services to Rock Ferry and Birkenhead Central are not running due to track engineering works, although rail replacement buses may be laid on instead. Alternatively, bus services 471 and 472 do travel to Birkenhead for £3.80 return. If you use this service, alight at Borough Road which is approximately a five minute walk to the ground. Taxi services are also available.
<br  /><br  /><strong >SUPPORTERS’ COACH:</strong><br  />
The Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Supporters’ Club will also be running a coach to this match at a price of £23 for members and £28 for non-members. It will depart Victoria Road at 8am sharp and contain a 45 minute service stop en-route. Supporters wishing to secure their place on the coach should call 07989901686. Bookings can be taken as late as one day prior to travel, but the later you leave it, the less chance you have of securing your spot on the coach.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-tranmere-rovers-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3513981.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-23 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>