<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3535910-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-doe-season-update-3535910.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Doe Season Update</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Doe Season Update</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Doe Season Update</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers captain Scott Doe gives an exclusive interview reflecting the season so far</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["The last two results against Braintree and North Ferriby were great for us personally and in the greater context of the league. We managed to get revenge in front of our own fans against Braintree for the Boxing Day game, and then a solid performance away at North Ferriby saw us score four goals and keep a clean sheet. The start of the year couldn’t really have gone much better. Add to that we now have previously injured players coming back to the fold and the future is looking very promising indeed. The injured lads coming back creates competition for places which keeps people on their toes and working hard to stay in the team. That said, the back four has been hit particularly hard with injuries and they’re the positions you want to try and keep as familiar as possible throughout the season. We have myself, Craig Robson, Shaun Donnellan, Josh Staunton, Joe Widdowson and Sam Ling, while Frankie Raymond provides cover at left-back. We now have quite a few people fighting for places and when required this also gives the manager the opportunity to rest players with options now available."
<br  /><br  />
"While we always like to keep our feet on the ground, the improvement of the injury situation coupled with two convincing wins to the start the year can only be a positive sign. Every team will go through a bad patch, but you have to come through that and that’s what we have done throughout the season, consistently bouncing back whenever we have been set back by a defeat. To do that amidst so many injuries has been tough, but the fact we have stayed in the pack at the top is a great testament to everyone’s character and it echoes what the manager has always said in that he believes we would get stronger as the season goes on."
<br  /><br  />
"If we look back at the start of the season, as a whole I would have to say we did very well. Considering the severe injuries we have had to Paul Benson, Guttridge, Okenabirhie, Craig Robson, Luke Howell, Ling, Luke Pennell and Curtley Williams, to still be fighting for the top is an incredible achievement. I think everyone would agree that given the circumstances under which we have performed, it has been a very successful first half to the season."
<br  /><br  />
"Although some clubs in the league have games in hand thanks to cup runs – ie Lincoln who beat Ipswich on last week – I am a big believer in having points on the board rather than games in hand. Lincoln will now be playing more towards the end of the season and that could work to our advantage. We have to keep winning games and not worry about other teams, but their situation certainly could work to our advantage in the long run."
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//scottdoe86292-3535896_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//scottdoe169292-3535897_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-24 15:00:03 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>