<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3536121-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-jake-howells-on-signing-for-the-daggers-3536121.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Jake Howells On Signing For The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Jake Howells On Signing For The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Jake Howells On Signing For The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers recent new signing Jake Howells gives his thoughts on joining the Daggers and looks ahead to Saturday's trip to Tranmere Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div ><p class="MsoNormal">"I have played under John Still before at Luton and I really enjoyed my time there playing under him. With the ambition at the club here at the minute with where they are in the league and looking to get back into the Football League, I want to be a part of that and get back into the Football League as well.</p><p class="MsoNormal">It was a brilliant opportunity for me to come here I think that I have settled in well so far with the players treating me well, and I am looking forward to the rest of the season now.</p><p class="MsoNormal">I have only recently come back from an injury, so with the game being called off on Saturday it gives me another weeks training and then hopefully I will be able to be in the squad to travel up to Tranmere on Saturday.</p><p class="MsoNormal">It is always good to have competition for places and I have seen in training that the squad is strong so if you don’t play one week you have to make sure that you train hard and you might be in the team the next week.
<br /></p><p class="MsoNormal">For me personally I just want to get fit and be able to bring something to the team when I play that can help us get out of the league and back into the Football League.
<br /></p><p class="MsoNormal">Tranmere is a very big club for this league and they get good crowds who come to watch them play at home so we know it will be a very difficult game but we are confident that we are able to go there and be able to bring a good result back."
<br /></p><p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jakehowellsinterview-86292-3536147_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jakehowellsinterview-169292-3536148_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-24 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>