<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3536643-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-tranmere-rovers-v-dagenham-redbridge-3536643.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Tranmere Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Tranmere Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Tranmere Rovers v Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Daggers' Vanarama National League away tie at Tranmere Rovers on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Tranmere Rovers play at Prenton Park which is the largest ground in the National League this season with an overall capacity of 16,789.
<br  /><br  />
Originally built in 1912, the stadium underwent radical transformation in the years following the Taylor Report, eventually becoming the all-seater ground it is today in 1995. Running alongside the pitch is the Johnny King Stand with a capacity of 2,414, while opposite is the Main Stand which also doubles up as the largest area in the stadium with the ability to hold 5,957 spectators. At one end is the Cowshed which is reserved for away supporters, while at the other end the Kop has a capacity of 5,696 and is where the most vocal of the home support is to be found.
<br  /><br  /><strong >DAGGERS FANS:</strong><br  />
Daggers fans will be housed in the Cowshed End which is all seated and has a total capacity of 2,500. Depending on the size of travelling support, away fans are generally given the top half of the stand which has excellent facilities and an unrestricted view of the pitch.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
There are plenty of food and drink options in the immediate surrounding area of Prenton Park, including the aforementioned Birch Tree Pub. Other pubs include the Sportsmans Arms on Prenton Road East and the Cock and Pullet on Woodchurch Road, both of which welcome away supporters. Alternatively, supporters travelling by train may wish to spend their time pre-match in Liverpool City Centre which offers a vast array of restaurants, pubs and takeaways to suit your every need. Particularly recommended is the Cavern Club which was home to the Beatles when they first burst onto the scene in the early 1960s.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-tranmere-rovers-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3513981.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />
An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-tranmere-rovers-3534200.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-25 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>