<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3536921-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/west-ham-united-u23-fixture-at-the-daggers-27th-january-3536921.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>West Ham United U23 Fixture At The Daggers 27th January</headline>
  <page_title>West Ham United U23 Fixture At The Daggers 27th January</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>West Ham United U23 Fixture At The Daggers 27th January</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>After Monday's postponement the Chigwell Construction Stadium will once again be hosting West Ham's U23 Premier League 2 fixture this coming Friday, the 27th January when they face Aston Villa</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[West Ham United’s under-23 side are back in action this Friday at the Chigwell Construction Stadium when they host Aston Villa at 7pm in a Premier League 2 Division two game. The Hammers are currently fifth in the table but would leapfrog Wolves, Newcastle and Fulham into second place with a victory.
<br  /><br  />
The two sides met in October at the Banks’s Stadium, Walsall with The Villans winning 2-0 and preventing The Hammers from topping the table.
<br  /><br  />
New signing Nathan Holland is likely to be included in the West Ham side.
<br  /><br  /><strong >West Ham United U23 last Five Results:</strong><br  />
Away v Brighton L0-3
<br  />
Home v Norwich W2-1
<br  />
Away v Wolves W4-0
<br  />
Home v Swansea L2-3
<br  />
Home v Brighton L1-3
<br  /><br  />
Admission to all Hammers U23 games at the Chigwell Construction Stadium is free for West Ham Season Ticket holders with admission costing everyone else £5 for adults and £3 for concessions. The Clubhouse is also open to all supporters before and after the game.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The postponed fixture on Monday against Leicester City in the Premier League Cup has now been rescheduled for Thursday, 9th February, 7pm kick off.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//westhamastonvillau23matchpreview-86292-3537009_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//westhamastonvillau23matchpreview-169292-3537011_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-27 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>