<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3537390-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-ahead-of-tranmere-rovers-3537390.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still about last weekend's postponed match at home to Bromley, recent transfer signings and Saturday's away tie at Tranmere Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Still was disappointed that the Bromley game got called off on Saturday after two good results against Braintree and North Ferriby but says he understands why the decision was made. </div><div ><br /></div><div ><em>"I arrived at the ground early on Saturday and when I had a look at the pitch, I thought that the game would be called off. It was quite disappointing as the break we had before we was due to play Bromley helped us in being able to get players closer to being back from injury but now our break has probably been a little longer than we would have wanted. The weather has been very difficult recently with all of the frost so we trained on Saturday on part of the pitch that was okay to play on and we had Monday off when we would usually train on a Monday, but as the weather was going to be really bad on that day we wouldn’t have been able to train as well as we would have liked. So with having the Monday off we will be training from Tuesday to Friday and we hope that we will be able to do as much as we would need to do leading up to the game on Saturday."</em></div><div ><br /></div><div >John Still says signing Jake Howells was an easy decision because of the 25 year old's versatility and that Sheppard was brought in to add more depth in the full back positions. </div><div ><br /></div><div ><em>"Howells is someone that I know inside out and he done really well for me when we was at Luton as he can play left back, wide left, centre left and he is a great team player who has played nearly 300 games in his career so far at the age of 25. He was absolutely the right player for us to bring into the team because of his versatility and also as he has a winners attitude. With Jake Sheppard, we only have the one right back at the moment with Sam Ling and when he has been injured we have been chopping and changing with Widdowson, Raymond and Staunton in the full back spots. So when we had the opportunity to sign Sheppard we took it as we feel that he is a good young player that will give us more depth in the right back position."</em></div><div ><br /></div><div >Tranmere have the best defensive record in the National League only conceding 8 goals at home so far but John Still wants to concentrate on the Daggers ahead of the big game between the two teams. </div><div ><br /></div><div ><em>"Looking ahead to Saturday, Tranmere may have a very impressive defensive record but when we are training I do not focus on the other team. We focus on how we play, only in the game would I change the playing style if I see something on the pitch that would give us an advantage."</em></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//johninterview86292-3537357_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//johninterview169292-3537362_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-25 15:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>