<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3538876-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-josh-staunton-tranmere-rovers-preview-3538876.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Josh Staunton Tranmere Rovers Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Josh Staunton Tranmere Rovers Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Josh Staunton Tranmere Rovers Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to Daggers Defender Josh Staunton about last week's postponed match against Bromley, competition for places and looking ahead to Saturday's away fixture at Prenton Park  </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After Saturday’s League game against Bromley being postponed until February, John Still’s men will now go another week without playing a game before Saturday’s promotion rival clash against Tranmere Rovers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“It was frustrating not to play on Saturday, we had a nice few days off the weekend before which gave us a chance to have a rest. It was disappointing as we wanted to get back on the pitch and hopefully get the momentum running into the Tranmere Rovers game. Although Tranmere have not had a game either as their league game against Woking was called off so we are both in the same boat.”</em><br  /><br  />
With Scott Doe back from his red card suspension and Craig Robson returning from his MCL injury, completion for the two centre-half spots is something we haven’t seen in previous months due to the injuries the Daggers have sustained.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Compared to a few months ago the manager has now got a selection problem with having too many players. The manager has gone from having to play the same 11 every week to now where people will be missing out if they don’t perform so it will be interesting to see what he does. Competition for places is good as it keeps everyone on their toes and hopefully it will improve the squad more than anything.”</em><br  /><br  />
The Daggers have now had 6 different centre back pairings since the start of the season, whilst still keeping an impressive 13 clean sheets in the league so far this season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I don’t think the changes we have had to make in the defence has affected us too much, we have stood up well and kept a lot of clean sheets and everyone who has come into the squad is good enough to play there. Although sometimes it is nice to build up relationships with the other centre half you are playing with, I have faith in anyone who comes into the squad can do the job in that role.”
<br /></em><br  />
Tranmere currently have the best defensive record in the league and have only conceded 8 goals at home, although Staunton believes that the quality the team possesses up front is enough to damage this statistic.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Last time we played Tranmere it was a 0-0 draw, bar a few slip ups in December I think we have had a good defensive record as a whole. We believe we have got the quality in the top half of the pitch to trouble any defence in this league, so if we play how we know we can play we are sure to cause them problems.”</em><br  /><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//joshstaunton86292-3538804_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//joshstaunton169292-3538815_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-26 15:30:29 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>