<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3539731-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-ahead-of-tranmere-rovers-3539731.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to Darren Currie about last Saturday's postponed fixture at home to Bromley and tomorrow's away game at Tranmere Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After last weekends postponed fixture at home to Bromley, Darren Currie explains how it had effected training this week and going three weeks without a game.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We had a spell in the season where the games were coming thick and fast and we didn’t have many players to choose from and now we have had three weeks without a game with a lot more bodies to pick from. That was down to the weather with the game being called off and that is out of our control, the plus for us is that everybody is looking sharp in training and looking forward to the game on Saturday.”
<br /><br />
“On Saturday we trained on the pitch where it was ok to use and we got an hours training in with the squad and throughout this week we have had to monitor our training. Although the conditions haven't been the best this week we have managed to get some good work into the players and our preparations are going well for the game.”</em><br  /><br  />
New signing Jake Howells is close to being match fit and Darren Currie hopes midfielder Matt Robinson will be back in training in the coming weeks.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Jake Howells has trained for the last five days and is getting stronger each day, this Saturday’s game may come too early for him but I would expect him to be back for next week’s game if he does not make it for the Tranmere game. Matt Robinson has started running again now and he is on the road to recovery and we are hopeful that it won’t be too long until he is back in training and back in the team.”</em><br  /><br  />
Tranmere Rovers have the best defensive record in the league this season with only eight goals conceded at home, but Darren Currie wants to concentrate on the Daggers as he believes we have enough in the team to get a good result.
<br  /><br  /><em >“The record that they have is something that they can be proud of, but for us we are a real threat going forward and we are confident that, despite their statistics, if we are on our game and our attacking players are on the front foot then we will readjust that statistic for them. I am confident in our players and when our forward players are playing as well as we know they can, they will score goals as we have done this season so far.”
<br /></em><br  /><p class="MsoNormal" ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></p><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-27 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>