<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3542090-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-tranmere-rovers-0-2-dagenham-and-redbridge-3542090.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Tranmere Rovers 0 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Tranmere Rovers 0 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Tranmere Rovers 0 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers won for the third game in a row with a 2-0 success at National league title rivals Tranmere Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1" >Daggers made three changes for the match, with Jake Sheppard, Andre Boucaud and Corey Whitely coming into the starting line-up.</p><p class="p2" >Daggers almost took the lead in the 14<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute when Luke Guttridge crossed for Oliver Hawkins from the left, but the striker’s half-volley from the penalty spot went just wide.</p><p class="p2" >Eleven minutes later, Daggers took the lead in slightly fortuitous circumstances through Corey Whitely.</p><p class="p2" >The forward crossed from the edge of the area, but his effort went all the way in and past a helpless Scott Davies in the Tranmere goal.</p><p class="p2" >With five minutes left in the half, Elliot Justham was at full stretch for Daggers to keep out a 20-yard shot from James Wallace.</p><p class="p2" >Daggers doubled their lead in the 47<span class="s1"><sup>th</sup></span> minute when Oliver Hawkins lashed home from 18 yards after a good run.</p><p class="p2" >Seven minutes later, Hawkins saw a header from a corner cleared off the line by Tranmere captain Steve Jennings.</p><p class="p2" >Despite mounting pressure from Tranmere, Daggers were able to hold on and secure a vital away win.</p>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3316004_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3316007_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-28 18:00:49 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>