<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3544691-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-barnet-1-4-dagenham-redbridge-3544691.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Barnet 1 - 4 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Barnet 1 - 4 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Barnet 1 - 4 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Breeze Past Bees</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Four assists from midfielder Tyrique Hyde helped the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s to a glowing 4-1 victory over London rivals Barnet.
<br  /><br  />
In an entertaining derby taking place in the north of the capital, the visitors established a first-half lead when Joe White finished off Hyde’s inviting ball.
<br  /><br  />
The duo combined once again to double their advantage as the Daggers opened up a twogoal cushion, which was extended by Harvey Brown’s exquisite strike midway through the second-half.
<br  /><br  />
Barnet were given a lifeline when they were awarded a penalty for David Agboola’s challenge on the home number nine, who subsequently dispatched the spot-kick to reduce the goal margin, their only shot on target in the game.
<br  /><br  />
But the simplest of finishes from Jordy Mongoy reinstated the Dagger’s three-goal lead as Micah Hyde’s youngsters saw out their confident display with ease.
<br  /><br  />
It was a highly impressive performance from the east London outfit in many respects as spectators were treated to an encapsulating display of attacking intensity from a livelylooking Daggers throughout the contest.
<br  /><br  />
Having played just once since the turn of the year, with their last two fixtures called off due to icy conditions and frozen pitches, Headcoach Micah Hyde will undoubtedly have been delighted to see his players maintain such high levels of fitness and concentration, both of which were key ingredients for a vital victory.
<br  /><br  />
Memories of their emphatic 7-2 thrashing of Northampton Town three weeks ago will also have served as a pivotal confidence-booster upon a delightful introduction to 2017.
<br  /><br  />
On this occasion, the Daggers issued entertaining reminders of the different dimensions they have to their game.
<br  /><br  />
They appeared strong and powerful in the first-half, regularly winning headers, 50-50’s, and outmuscling their opposition, and skilful and intricate in the second, with their forward movement and incisive passing constantly carving open a fragile-looking Bees backline, completely dominating the midfield in the process.
<br  /><br  />
The wide areas proved a particular source of joy for a goal-hungry Daggers, as the firsthalf saw Joe White finish off inviting crosses from an in-form Tyrique Hyde, and Scott Mitchell twice headed second over from left-wing crosses either side of the centre-back sliding into the keeper’s gloves from a Mustaphe Ali pull-back.
<br  /><br  />
Joe White was also close to benefitting from Ali’s wing play, but like Scott Mitchell, the striker placed directly into the palms of the away number one from the wideman’s centre ball, and came also came close with a shot on the turn, but the Bees stopper was equal to the forward’s effort.
<br  /><br  />
The home goalkeeper was also forced into a scrambling save after an away man produced a finely curled effort from the left, before Scott Mitchell’s volleyed cross from the opposite flank deflected off a retreating Bees defender and narrowly escaped a wellpositioned Dylan Florence.
<br  /><br  />
Aside astutely playing their way into the box, the visitors demonstrated their capability from distance, with winger Jordy Mongoy producing a stunning effort from 30-yards that was tipped over the bar by a busy Bees keeper, before Harvey Brown eventually beat the stopper from similar distance with a thumping low drive.
<br  /><br  />
By this point, the Daggers were cruising towards a much deserved three-points, but a slight moment of panic from a Bees breakaway saw an isolated David Agboola bring down the advancing Barnet forward, who placed high into the net from the spot to register, what turned out to be, a mere consolation.
<br  /><br  />
Despite losing the clean sheet, the visitors did not appear at all phased, and continued to in a positive and ambitious manner as the encounter slowly drew to a close.
<br  /><br  />
Having won a corner through sheer persistence, the Daggers once again made the opportunity count at the expense of a tiresome Bees, who failed to clear the danger, allowing Hyde to create the space for Mongoy to poke into an empty net as the visitors ended on a high.
<br  /><br  />
After a pulsating game, Academy Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on another classy Daggers performance:
<br  /><br  />
“We gave a very strong performance today, from the development the players have shown, I felt confident we would show that,” said a pleased Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“We were good in the first half dominating early, once this was established, I felt we relied too much on physical strength and power, I wanted to see more of what we practice Monday to Friday, being creative by using technique, skill, swift pass and move play, and I saw plenty of that in the second half which was pleasing,” continued the U18s coach.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1,Louie Chapman, 5, Scott Mitchell, 6, Paul Symes (c), 2, Jack Lee, 3,Liam Gordon, 4,Harvey Brown, 8,Tyrique Hyde, 11, Mustaphe Ali, 10,Jordy Mongoy, 12,Dylan Florence, 9, Joe White, 14, Deniz Alici, 15,David Agboola, 16,James Turvey
<br  /><br  /><strong >Goalscorers</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Joe White (2), Harvey Brown, Jordy Mongoy
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-30 10:30:44 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>