<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3545185-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-post-tranmere-rovers-3545185.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Post Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Post Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Post Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts on Saturday’s trip to Prenton Park for the Daggers' game against Tranmere Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[John Still was pleased with Saturday's performance against promotion rivals Tranmere Rovers and is feeling confident for the future with players returning from injuries bolstering the Daggers squad once again.
<br  /><br  /><em >"It was always going to be a tough game because both teams are challenging for promotion. I thought we defended brilliantly the organisation in the team was very good, we always looked a threat going forward although the first goal might be classed as a bit fortunate, the second goal I thought was top class and finished a very good performance against a very good side."
<br /><br />
"We now have 17 games to go and I think we are in decent form, we have had lots of players out injured that are coming back which makes a massive difference and now it’s just a matter of every game that we play now is the biggest game we are going to play because that’s what it is like when you are trying to win promotion."
<br /><br />
"We said to the players before the game that they’re the home team, both teams haven’t played for a while, but the home team will try and take the ascendancy so the first thing we have got to do is defend well and we did as the back four performed excellently."
<br /><br />
"Another pleasing element was that Elliot only had to make one save right at the death, I don’t think he was challenged other than that. So after the first half where we’d kept the opposition at bay I thought we had done our job, we’d played some good football, we defended well and was holding the ball well."
<br /><br />
"We came out the second half and like good players do Hawkins came up with a great goal and although I’m not saying after that I thought we had won it but I did feel we were in a comfortable position because we looked so solid."
<br /><br />
"From a few weeks back not having enough players to pick from now we have selections on the bench such as Scott Doe and Luke Howell. Right back Sam Ling is not playing currently although Ling came in when he wasn’t really fit enough to be playing and we was worried about him getting injured. Bringing in Jake Sheppard really helped to add depth to the squad and he has come in and done really well. If we looked at the bench during the game we could make changes with Howell coming on, Scott Doe coming on so the squad is stronger now and we are going to need that towards the end of the season."</em><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//stilltranmere86292-3545163_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//stilltranmere169292-3545164_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-30 12:00:01 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>