<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3546792-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-craig-robson-post-tranmere-rovers-3546792.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Craig Robson Post Tranmere Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Craig Robson Post Tranmere Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Craig Robson Post Tranmere Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Defender Craig Robson gives his thoughts on the win over fellow promotion rivals Tranmere Rovers at Prenton Park on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Craig Robson thought that he and Shaun Donnellan coped well with the Tranmere attacks in what was their first game as a centre back partnership
<br  /><br  /><em >“I thought that we played really well, it was the first time that me and Donnellan had played together in a centre back partnership and I felt we coped with their attacking players well throughout the game. There has been quite a lot of centre back partnerships throughout the season with all the injuries and I have been injured for a while myself, I am just glad to be back out on the pitch again.”
<br /><br />
“We have kept three clean sheets in a row now and if you are keeping clean sheets it makes it easier to win games as we know that we can score goals. As a defender clean sheets is what you want and we hope to keep as many clean sheets as we can between now and the end of the season. “</em><br  /><br  />
The defender said that his injuries had been frustrating for him but is happy that he and fellow players are coming back into the fold after all of the injures that the team has suffered in recent months.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Since I started playing football I have hardly had any injuries and suddenly I have had a quite a few this season which has been frustrating for me but I hope to get fitter and stronger for the rest of the season.”
<br /><br />
“For the last couple of months we had been really suffering with injuries but now it is good as we have competition for places with the new signings we have brought in and players coming back from injury, so hopefully we can push on and be right up there come the end of the season.”
<br /></em><br  />
Robson is confident for the remainder of the season that the Daggers will continue to challenge at the top of the table.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We are not going to get ahead of ourselves and we will keep taking one game at a time and we are hoping that we will stay near the top of the table and if we can keep on our good run then we will be confident of at least finishing in the playoff places.”</em><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//craigrobson-86292-3511970_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//craigrobson-169292-3511973_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-01-31 12:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>