<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3553382-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-preview-dagenham-and-redbridge-v-chester-fc-3553382.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Preview: Dagenham and Redbridge v Chester FC</headline>
  <page_title>Match Preview: Dagenham and Redbridge v Chester FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Preview: Dagenham and Redbridge v Chester FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>A preview of the Daggers Vanarama National League home match against Chester FC on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >The Daggers will be looking to maintain their good form following three wins on the bounce including an impressive 2-0 away win at fellow promotion hopefuls Tranmere Rovers last weekend.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Chester currently sit 10th in the Vanarama National League, nine points below the playoffs following their 3-1 defeat away to Dover in their last outing.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Previous 5 Results </strong></div><div ><strong><br /></strong></div><div ><strong>Daggers</strong></div><div >Tranmere 0-2 Daggers</div><div >North Ferriby 0-4 Daggers</div><div >Daggers 3-0 Braintree </div><div >Braintree 3-2 Daggers </div><div >Daggers 4-4 Solihull Moors </div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Chester</strong></div><div >Dover 3-1 Chester</div><div >Chester 1-1 Wrexham </div><div >Chester 0-2 Forest Green (FA Trophy)</div><div >Braintree 1-2 Chester</div><div >Chester 0-3 Solihull</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Team News</strong></div><div >Sam Ling and Jake Howells could be available for Saturday’s game following their involvement in the Daggers' friendly against Gillingham on Tuesday. Robinson and Williams look set to miss out again.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Previous Meetings</strong></div><div >The two teams have met 13 times with the Daggers winning five times. The last time these two teams met in Dagenham was in 2008 with the Daggers winning 6-0 on that occasion.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Fixtures</strong></div><div >Due to the FA Trophy taking place this weekend there are six games taking place in the Vanarama National League on Saturday. All 3pm KO.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Bromley V Torquay</div><div >Dag &amp; Red V Chester</div><div >Gateshead V Southport</div><div >Maidstone V Aldershot</div><div >Woking V Solihull</div><div >Wrexham V Guiseley </div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Tickets</strong></div><div >Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-on-sale-dagenham-and-redbridge-v-chester-3522461.aspx">here</a>. </div><div > </div><div ><strong>Social Media &amp; Online</strong></div><div >Follow the Daggers on Twitter for live updates throughout the match (@Dag_RedFC). There will also be updates on our Facebook page (OfficialDaggers). After the match there will be a match report on the website.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><div><strong>Travel Information</strong></div><div>There will be problems on the District, Metline and Romford services this weekend. Please see below for full information. </div><div><strong><br /></strong></div><div><div><strong>District line </strong></div><div>Trains will not run between Embankment and West Ham. This is to allow testing on new signalling, replace drainage at Aldgate, carry out station improvement work at Stepney Green as well as Crossrail construction work at Whitechapel. </div><div><br /></div><div><strong>Hammersmith &amp; City line </strong></div><div>Trains will not run between Liverpool Street and Barking. This is to allow testing on new signalling, replace drainage at Aldgate, carry out station improvement work at Stepney Green as well as Crossrail construction work at Whitechapel.</div><div><br /></div><div><strong>Metropolitan line </strong></div><div>There will be no service between Aldgate and Wembley Park while testing is being made on signalling and replace drainage at Aldgate as well as track and drainage replacement work between Baker Street and Finchley Road.</div><div><br /></div><div><strong>London Overground </strong></div><div>All weekend there will be no service between the following stations: Romford and Upminster, due to Crossrail construction work and Network Rail track work.</div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//chesterhmatchpreview-861292-3554165_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//chesterhmatchpreview-1691292-3554166_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-03 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>