<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3554515-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-chester-preview-3554515.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Chester Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Chester Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Chester Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We speak to Daggers manager John Still looking ahead to Saturday's home fixture against Chester and we discuss the managers squad selection choices on the eve of the game</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After months of struggling for squad selection choices John Still is pleased to have plenty of competition back in the side.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I had problems when I had no players to choose from and I don’t have any problems now when we have lots of players fit. The players need to know that they are fighting for a place and now you need to be performing in training or any friendly games to make the bench and that is what we need. We have to have that competition for places and one of the ups that comes from the downs of not having enough players is that other players had a chance to show their worth. I have seen a big improvement in players that may not have been in the team at the start of the season so the competition now for places is a big plus for us.”</em><br  /><br  />
From experience John Still believes that no team in this league should be taken for granted, and with 17 games left in the league the Daggers will be looking to cement their chances for a promotion place.
<br  /><br  /><em >“If I look back on the games this season, we have drew with Forest Green away, we drew with Tranmere at home and beat them away. We have beat Lincoln at home and beat Dover twice this season as well. We lost away to Chester earlier in the season and I look around at the team and we have had a couple of games where people maybe expected us to win that didn’t go our way. This league is very tough and the strength of the league has got better and better over the years, from back when I won the league with Maidstone to doing it here with Dagenham and then with Luton, each year it has got tougher. I haven’t gone into a game this season thinking I know we can win this, I go into the games thinking I believe we can win this game if we perform as we know we can. I will not take anything for granted and from now until the end of the season if it’s against a team in the top six, but especially you can’t take anything for granted when you’re playing the teams that are not in that top six.”
<br /><br />
“When you start the season you have 46 games to play, whenever you play them; however you play them. In the first half of the season I always say that you have got to be in that top group, if you want to do well and we’ve been able to do that. When you get to the second half of the season, I believe that the league really starts from then onwards and we have just got to be in a position to give ourselves a chance, which we have done so far; the league has started and we have started the league very well.”
<br /></em><strong ><br />
Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><div ><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//stilltranmere86292-3545163_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//stilltranmere169292-3545164_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-03 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Premium Video,Team</Tags>
</News>