<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3559475-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-redbridge-southend-united-3559475.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Southend United</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Southend United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 0 - 0 Southend United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers and Southend played out a goalless draw yesterday in a behind closed doors match which saw both teams get some valuable game time in for players not regularly featuring.  </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >It also presented John Still with an opportunity to look at the trialists and saw ex-Dagger Zavon Hines return to the Chigwell Construction Stadium with his new side.
<div> </div><div>A largely uneventful first half was evident when the game’s first threat on goal didn’t arrive until 39 minutes on the clock. Frank Nouble broke into the box and took a shot from a difficult angle to force a save from Mark Cousins. Minutes later the Southend striker once again found himself in the box after muscling his way past Josh Staunton but didn’t force a save from The Daggers keeper.</div><div> </div><div>The Daggers began the second half in the ascendancy putting the Shrimpers' defence under pressure. On the hour Scott Heard intercepted the ball in midfield and put Mason Bloomfield through on goal. The youngster tried to beat the Southend keeper from 35-yards out but saw his shot canon off the crossbar. </div><div> </div><div>Moments later the bar was rattled again. Jake Howells found Joe White with a whipped in cross but the striker’s header beat the opposition keeper but came back off the woodwork.</div><div> </div><div>The game’s final chance came nine minutes from time when a free kick from Howells found an unmarked Staunton but the Southend Keeper pulled off a save to deny the Daggers defender.</div><br />
Short highlights of the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/highlights-dagenham-and-redbridge-southend-united-3559487.aspx">here</a>.
<br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3316004_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3316007_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-07 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Match,Reserves,Team</Tags>
</News>