<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3560710-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-contract-extension-update-3560710.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Contract Extension Update</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Contract Extension Update</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Contract Extension Update</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are delighted to announce that seven first team players have signed contract extensions with the club</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[With a number of players having contracts expiring at the end of the season, manager John Still has been keen to start talking to players about extending their stay at the Chigwell Construction Stadium.
<br  />
Those talks have now begun and a number of players have already put pen to paper.
<br  /><br  />
It’s not just the regular first teamers that have been offered new contracts with some progressing through the Club’s youth system also being offered new deals.
<br  /><br  />
We’re happy to report that seven players have now signed new contracts. Those seven are Fejiri Okenabirhie, Matt Robinson, Andre Boucaud, Corey Whitely, Elliot Justham, Tyrique Hyde and Joe White.
<br  /><br  />
In an exclusive interview with <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/" >Daggers Player</a> John talks about each contract extension individually here. Click <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news" >here</a> to watch the full interview on Daggers Player.     
<br  /><br  /><strong >Fejiri Okenabirhie</strong><br  /><em >"I think that it was evident early season for people to see that Fejiri was a threat and his work rate, work ethic and understanding of the game is much better than we even thought it would be. He trained with us for a little bit last year while he was still with his former club and we always knew that we would like to take him, and he hit the ground running straight away. We had some enquires about him early season from clubs above us and once the club was becoming stable in terms of new investors it was an obvious situation that we would like to keep him for a bit longer. Unfortunately injury has held him back a bit but in the last few games since he has come back I believe he has shown what a good player he is. I think that over the next five or six games that will get him back up to speed, and with his age and speed him signing a contract extension is something that we thought would be right for the club."</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Matt Robinson</strong><br  /><em >"Matt Robinson is a player that I knew well from my time at Luton and he played quite a lot of games for the Luton side that won the league to get back into the Football League. He was a young player then that lacked a little bit of knowledge and experience but he had good energy and his footballing skills were good. His attitude and desire to improve was something that caught my eye and I gave him a three year contract when I was with Luton and I said to him that I was not quite sure if you’re ready to push on in the Football League but I believe that you are going to be. When I came back to Dagenham and as soon as it became evident to me that Luton were not as keen on Matt as I was, I done everything that I could to bring him here. He is a better player now, he has pushed on and I think that he would be ready for the Football League now, he is a young player with lots of energy and has got the experience of winning the National League before. So giving Matt a contract extension was a no-brainer for me and I would never have let him leave if I was at Luton, and the fact that we have been able to extend his contract here for another year is good for us. And instead of him and Fejiri only having one year on their contract at the end of this season they now have two years left."</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Andre Boucaud</strong><br  /><em >"I knew Andre Boucaud very well as a player and when I came here it was really difficult as I felt that the side lacked the passion that you need. I didn’t see that in the team when I came here and maybe Andre had got sucked down with that and that is not an individual criticism. At the end of last season I made the decision that I would change as many players that I could and that was not based on how well they were doing as there was a couple players who left who I felt were doing quite well. I thought that was the right thing to do and Andre had another year on his contract which was fine and he has massively bought into what we want to do and he has become a leader on the pitch. I believe that he has become fitter and his energy levels and work rate are higher and because we are a reasonably young and inexperienced group his experience could be vital in the progression of the team. So Andre has been terrific and we have rewarded him by extending his contract by another year as his contract would have been over at the end of the season but we have extended that with two years now. I think that he has a big influence on the young players around him and I have seen the qualities that he has that maybe I didn’t see last year."
<br /></em><br  /><strong >Corey Whitely</strong><br  /><em >"Corey Whitely was a player that I tried really hard to get here form Enfield and was only able to do it at the start of the season, so brining him in was something that we wanted to do and he has progressed throughout the season. Sometimes you can bring young players in and they don’t progress straight away but this group have just progressed together. I am really surprised that they have progressed together and that is a good thing for the staff and coaches and everybody who has worked with this group of players. Corey has been in the Okenabirhie sort of mould where he has come from a lower level and has adapted to this level comfortably, and he is only going to get better so we wanted him to get better here."</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Elliot Justham</strong><br  /><em >"Elliot Justham was another Luton situation, I took him there from East Thurrock where he had performed really well and I believe that he learnt a lot while he was there as if he made a mistake he always learnt form it. Talking to previous goalkeeping coaches at Luton and here and also David James who had come to training a few times at Luton and here as well, they all felt that he was progressing really well. Goalkeepers are a position where they can mature at a later age and I was not sure if I would be able to get him from Luton but eventually I did and I think that he has been terrific. In the games that he has played, he has probably had a couple of games where he feels he could have done a bit better but his stature, distribution and ability are growing so we want him to grow here."</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Tyrique Hyde &amp; Joe White</strong><br  /><em >"Tyrique Hyde and Joe White are two young players who are progressing all the time, I had watched them in training with the Academy and we brought them into training with the first team and they have both handled that really well. I think that it is a tribute to Micah Hyde who is the Academy manager that we have managed to bring them into the team as we have had a lot of injuries this season so it was good to get them involved. In a way with the injuries as disappointing as they were it has helped us push on another couple of players in Joe and Tyrique."</em><br  /><br  /><em >"With football I have never changed how I do it or the way that I do it and that fits with some clubs and doesn’t fit with other clubs. I have always and particularly here, like to find and develop clubs and here I want players who can become Dagenham players. I look back now at players that were here before and I have spoken to Dwight Gayle and Matt Ritchie who both came back here recently and look back at their time here as where they got their grounding in football. That is what I like to create and I believe that doing that is something that can take a club Like Dagenham forward because we don’t have vast resources and we have to work with what we have got. Trying to find, young hungry and ambitious players that want to find their start in football here, I think that is the right thing for this football club and that’s what I have created here before, and is what I want to try and help create here again. I want to be able to look back in seven or eight years like I did when I was here before and we had two promotions, lots of players sold and the club had done its job on and off the pitch, and that it what I want to create once again."</em><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//johnstillsu86292-3560702_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//johnstillsu169292-3560703_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-07 15:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>