<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3562681-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-jordan-maguire-drew-post-chester-fc-3562681.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Jordan Maguire-Drew Post Chester FC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Jordan Maguire-Drew Post Chester FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Jordan Maguire-Drew Post Chester FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Jordan Maguire-Drew was happy to get the winner against Chester FC on Saturday and thanks the fans for their support so far this season</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Jordan Maguire-Drew was disappointed not to start against Chester but happy that he managed to help the team win the game on Saturday.
<br  /><br  /><em >"I was disappointed not to start on Saturday as well as the Tranmere game but I used it to fuel me, and when I came on I wanted to be able to get the winner for the team, which luckily I was able to do."
<br /><br />
"I used the frustration of not playing to make me be positive as I am going to go through times in my career when I am not starting. Hopefully I can get my place in the team next week away at Southport and then help the Club push on and get promotion, which would help me personally as well."
<br /></em><br  />
Maguire-Drew is confident in his abilities but says he has learnt a lot with his time with the Daggers so far this season.
<br  /><br  /><em >"The end product is a big part of my game and I find the shots, crosses and free kicks easy but what I am learning here is the defensive side of the game and how to grind out a win which is going to help me a lot."
<br /><br />
"I have been working hard in training and I know that this is a very good squad of players here now with players coming back from injury, and I thank the manager for trusting me in playing me regularly this season, but now we are just going to be looking forward to Saturday’s game at Southport."
<br /></em><br  />
The winger has thanked the fans for their support so far this season and wants to push on for the rest of the season and help the club back into the Football League
<br  /><br  /><em >"I can’t thank the fans and the staff at the club enough, they have taken to me like I am one of their own so I want to give as much as I can for the rest of the season to get this club back into the Football League which is where they deserve to be and what the fans deserve as they have been excellent this season at both home and away."</em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jordanmaguire-drewchester-86292-3562694_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jordanmaguire-drewchester-169292-3562695_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-07 08:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>