<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3562775-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-against-racism-day-ticket-giveaway-3562775.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Against Racism Day Ticket Giveaway</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Against Racism Day Ticket Giveaway</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Against Racism Day Ticket Giveaway</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We are giving away two free seated tickets for our annual Daggers Against Racism Day match against Guiseley AFC on Saturday 18th February on our Twitter page</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers will once again be hosting their award winning annual Daggers Against Racism Day for 2017, which this year will fall for their game against Guiseley AFC on Saturday 18th February, KO 3.00pm.
<br  /><br  />
In an effort to bring as many people together to celebrate this day which highlights the Club's commitment against all forms of racism and in particularly demonstrates that racism will never be acceptable within football. We will be running a variety of social media ticket competitons throughout the weeks leading up to the game.
<br  /><br  />
Head over to our twitter to be up for a chance of winning two free seated tickets for our annual Daggers Against Racism Day match against Guiseley AFC on Saturday 18th February.
<br  /><br  />
Winner will be picked midday on Thursday so head over to our twitter page now to enter, all you have to do is re-tweet our ticket competition tweet.
<br  /><br  />
Our twitter competition tweet is linked below, remember you only have until midday on Thursday day to enter!
<br  /><br  />
Click <a href="https://twitter.com/Dag_RedFC/status/828941200069623809" >here</a> to head over to our twitter.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//ticket-competition86292-3562834_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//ticket-competition169292-3562838_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-07 12:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>