<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3564685-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/vanarama-national-league-january-manager-of-the-month-3564685.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Vanarama National League January Manager Of The Month</headline>
  <page_title>Vanarama National League January Manager Of The Month</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Vanarama National League January Manager Of The Month</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are delighted to announce that manager John Still has won Vanarama National League manager of the month for January 2017 </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Dagenham and Redbridge manager John Still has been announced as the Vanarama National League manager of the month for January 2017. 
<div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers played three games in the National League in January winning all three games while also not conceding a goal. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers started the month in front of the BT cameras where they beat Braintree Town 3-0 at the Chigwell Construction Stadium on January 2nd, and on Saturday 7th January the Daggers beat North Ferrbiy United 4-0 for the second win on the bounce. </div><div ><br /></div><div >After our home fixture against Bromley on 21st January was postponed, the Daggers' final game of the month was away to play off rivals Tranmere Rovers where the Daggers ran out 2-0 winners to take the points home from Liverpool and complete a winning month. </div><div ><br /></div><div >John Still was delighted to be announced as the Vanarama National League manager of the month:</div><div ><br /></div><div >"When you get an award like the manager of the month, that is not just me winning the award, it is all my staff and everybody who has been involved with the team to be able to let us perform how we have managed to perform in January."
<br /><br />
"So this is just an award that we can give ourselves a pat on the back for and we will want to push on for the rest of the season to carry on our good form."
<br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//managerofthemonth-86292-3564705_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//managerofthemonth-169292-3564706_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-08 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>