<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3565786-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-luke-howell-on-his-comeback-from-injury-3565786.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Luke Howell On His Comeback From Injury</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Luke Howell On His Comeback From Injury</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Luke Howell On His Comeback From Injury</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to midfielder Luke Howell about his comeback from injury and looking ahead to the rest of the season</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Luke Howell made his 150th Daggers appearance in the win over Chester FC last Saturday and the midfielder was delighted to reach that landmark.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I didn’t actually know until after the game that it was my 150th appearance as I thought that I was still a few short but I am really pleased as it is a very good personal achievement.”</em><br  /><br  />
The midfielder has struggled with injuries this season and says that the injuries have been the worst of his career so far.
<br  /><br  /><em >“This season has been the most frustrating season of my career as I came back from injury after missing the start of the season with an injury to my right knee and then to come back and do the same to my left knew was really tough. Sometimes that happens in football and I am just concentrating on getting back fit as soon as possible.”</em><br  /><br  />
Howell believes that the Daggers will be able to push on for the last part of the season with players returning from injury.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have always managed to stay at the top or there abouts throughout the season even though we haven’t had a full squad for most of the season to choose from which shows the strength of our squad. We are coming to the end of the season where every point is vital, we hope to have as many players as possible to choose from with most of the team returning from injury, so we can all play our part in the team.”</em><br  /><br  />
Luke Howell has advised his team mates about what to expect at Haig Avenue for Saturday’s trip to Southport, having played there for the Daggers in the FA Cup two season ago.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Having been part of the team that played Southport away in the cup a couple of season ago I have told the other players that the facilities are not ideal and the pitch the pitch is not very good. We know that their players are going to be up for the game and it is a very difficult place to play, but we know that we have the quality to take all three points from the game.”</em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//lukehowellsouthport-86292-3566522_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//lukehowellsouthport-169292-3566524_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-09 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>