<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3566581-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-ahead-of-southport-fc-3566581.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Southport FC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Southport FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Southport FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still ahead of Saturday's away trip to Southport FC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[John Still spoke to the squad last week about what was needed in the second half of the season in order for the Daggers to achieve promotion
<br  /><br  /><em >“I said to the players last week that the first half of the season is where you see if you can get yourselves into a position to go for promotion and we have managed to do that. I said to them that with the second half of the season, it is now about winning games and whoever you play everyone has something to play for, wherever it is fighting to stay up, fighting for promotion or fighting to get a play-off spot.”
<br /><br />
“The only thing we have to do now is win, you are not going to play great every week and with the amount of games we have left we may only play really well in six or seven of those games, but in another six or seven games we could perform adequately. In some other games we may say we have been lucky, but they are all components that you have to find and on Saturday we managed to find a way to win the game, even without performing at our best.”</em><br  /><br  />
The manager believes the two recent friendly games away to Gillingham and at home to Southend have been important in giving game time to the players who have recently come back from injury and players who needed a rest.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have had a lot of players out injured and when they come back you have to be able to give them some game time somewhere. We were able to give Maguire-Drew a little rest and played him in our friendly against Gillingham last week and that helped him as he didn’t have the same intenseness of a first team game, it let him slow down a bit so he could have a break. Also Luke Howell who has just come back from injury managed to play in the friendly games and he came off the bench last Saturday and done really well as did Maguire-Drew. Paul Benson as well has played in both the friendly games and when he came on against Chester you know what you are going to get from him which he showed with his header that came off the crossbar which Jordan managed to finish well.”</em><br  /><br  />
John Still is pleased to have a strong squad again and says that Matt Robinson and Curtley Williams could be back in the squad again soon.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Earlier in the season we didn’t have enough players to make changes from the bench but with players back now the bench is strong with players who can make an impact in the game coming on as a sub. With players coming back from injury there can be little niggles but we have nothing long term at the moment, Matt Robinson will be back in training in the next few weeks and Curtley Williams has just got back into training so that is positive for us.”</em><br  /><br  />
The manager is expecting another tough game away to Southport after the club appointed a new manager in Andy Preece earlier in the week
<br  /><br  /><em >“I always believe that if you play well enough you will give yourself a chance to win, and we have to go to Southport on Saturday and however they play or whatever system they play we have to find our way to win the game. We know that it is going to be tough, and when a new manager comes into a team it can always make it a little bit tougher, but we will concentrate on ourselves and aim to perform as best as we can to get the three points.”</em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jstill2017-86292-3505110_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jstill2017-169292-3505111_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-10 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>