<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3572750-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-post-southport-fc-3572750.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Post Southport FC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Post Southport FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Post Southport FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Manager John Still gives his thoughts on the 4-1 away win over Southport FC on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA["It was a difficult game on Saturday as the pitch was poor and we started the game by trying to be too precise in our game and we couldn’t play the way that we wanted to play. We said to the payers before the game that if what we want to do isn’t working, then we may have to play longer. Once we went longer in the game we scored the three goals before half time and effectively that won us the game."
<br  />
 
<br  />
"Once we had the two goal lead we just had to be sensible and play on the break, as it was very difficult for us to get passing movements. Away from home to be able to score four goals is very good, but we always know that we are a team that is able to score goals. Maguire-Drew’s free kick was terrific and Okenabirhie’s strikes for the third goal was top drawer, so it was an efficient performance away from home for us."
<br  /><br  />
"The players said to me at half time that they didn’t think it was a penalty, but the referee gave it and thankfully we responded well to that. Once he has gave it there is nothing we can do about it, it is just about how you respond to situations like that, but we did respond and got our goals before half time."
<br  /><br  />
"Craig Robson was the captain for us on Saturday and I chose him as he is a leader in the team, and I look at players like him, Hawkins, Whitely and Okenabirhie and think about where they have come from it is fantastic how well they are doing for us so far this season."
<br  /><br  />
"Jake Howells made his debut for the club as well and we are just getting him fitter and fitter each week as he is a very good player and it is good for us to have players like him who we can bring on from the bench."
<br  /><br  />
"We have our Daggers Against Racism Day game next Saturday and it is always a big game for us, especially as it is a game to be played to show that football is a multi-cultural game, but there should be a big crowd and we look forward to the game and helpfully getting another win."
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jstill86292-3465308_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jstill169292-3465309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-13 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>