<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3572698-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/dagenham-and-redbridge-community-trust-project-futsal-3572698.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Trust Project: Futsal</headline>
  <page_title>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Trust Project: Futsal</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Trust Project: Futsal</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Throghout this week leading up to our annual Daggers Against Racism day fixture against Guiseley this Saturday, we will be showcasing some of the projects that are run by our Community Trust</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Our Community Trust run a variety of different projects to local residents of Barking and Dagenham, one of those projects is Futsal.
<br  /><br  />
Our futsal programme is the newest of our projects and our first project held in the Borough of Redbridge.
<br  /><br  />
Our new Futsal project at the Isaac Newton Academy, Cricklefield Pl, Ilford IG1 1FY is aimed at pupils in school years 3-6 and cost just £4 per week. Futsal remains an underrated game which is now becoming more popular in recent years, thanks to exposure via the internet and other social media platforms.
<br  /><br  />
Pros such as Cristiano Ronaldo and Messi have expressed their importance in the game, helping them learn and develop their football skills and techniques through the small sided game. Barcelona FC remains a very good example of how the futsal is an important part of development at grass roots level, alongside academy players’ football.
<br  /><br  />
The game is played on an indoor court, 5 v5, with a heavier size 4 balls that has no real bounce and encourages the ball to be played on the surface. The game is played at a quick pace, which allows young players to improve their decision making while under pressure in tight areas on the court.
<br  /><br  />
Our new Futsal programme will be headed up our lead Futsal Community Coach Josh Mugenyi who has a number of years’ experience in both playing and coaching this upcoming sport.
<br  /><br  />
If you would like to attend this new weekly Futsal session or require any further details please contact the Community Trust team on 0208-592-1579 ext 30 or email us on fitc@daggers.co.uk.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//futsalcommunityarticle-86292-3572702_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//futsalcommunityarticle-169292-3572703_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-13 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>