<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3574229-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-fejiri-okenabirhie-post-southport-fc-3574229.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie Post Southport FC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie Post Southport FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Fejiri Okenabirhie Post Southport FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Forward Fejiri Okenabirhie gives his thoughts on returning from injury and Saturday's 4-1 win away to Southport</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After conceding a goal early on Saturday, the Daggers knuckled down scoring four goals to finish the game with an impressive three goal lead over The Sandgrounders.
<br  /><br  /><em >"Saturday was tough to begin with they were very dominant early on, it took us 20 minutes to get to grips with their play but we made it through that tough period, and once we worked out our game plan I felt we dealt with them really well."</em><br  /><br  />
Fejiri has only recently returned to first team football after almost 3 months of suffering with severe bone bruising to his ankle, the forward is happy to be back and was glad with his contributions on Saturday to help the Daggers to a fifth straight win.
<br  /><br  /><em >"It is nice to be playing again, I have been out for a while so I’m glad to be back and help the team get the win. We all have a very good relationship with each other, we know how each other play and we are always trying to feed off each other’s strengths which I think worked really well today."
<br /><br />
"Each game I’m feeling fitter, it takes a while to get my fitness levels back to what they were but I am glad to be out there. Hopefully throughout the season I can get stronger and the team can get stronger and hopefully we can finish the season well."
<br /></em><br  />
The Daggers are currently 3 points off league leaders Lincoln City, Okenabirhie believes that the team should not focus on the leaders’ performances but focus on the Daggers’ performances and working hard in training.
<br  /><br  /><em >"We are on a good run, we are in the important part of the season now we just need to keep that run going and keep winning games. Now we look ahead to next week, work hard in training and hopefully duplicate what we done on Saturday. We just need to focus on our own performances at the moment, take each game at a time and try and get the wins that we valuably need to keep closing that gap on the league leaders."
<br /></em><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//okenabirhie86292-3574222_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//okenabirhie169292-3574225_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-14 11:30:33 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>