<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3579133-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/dagenham-and-redbridge-community-project-al-madina-mosque-programme-3579133.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Al-Madina Mosque Programme</headline>
  <page_title>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Al-Madina Mosque Programme</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Al-Madina Mosque Programme</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Leading up to our annual Daggers Against Racism day fixture against Guiseley AFC this Saturday 18th February, we will be showcasing some of the projects that are run by our Community Trust</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Our Community Trust run a variety of different projects to local residents of Barking and Dagenham, one of those projects is the Al-Madina Mosque Programme.
<br  /><br  />
This year the Community Trust coaches have teamed up with MSA sports who together with Al-Madina Mosque in Barking will be running sessions which are aiming to get more Muslim females playing football by providing a safe and secure environment which does not compromise any religious beliefs.
<br  /><br  />
Our new female project will run for 12 weeks and is free for participants to attend. This project has been made possible thanks to funding from The EFL Trust and Mayor of London as part of their Female Fitness and Exercise programme.
<br  /><br  />
Everyone at the trust is extremely excited about our new partnership with MSA sports and are looking forward to future projects that are currently being finalised.
<br  /><br  />
If you wish to attend this session please do not hesitate in contacting the Community Trust team on 0208-592-1579 ext 30 or email us on fitc@daggers.co.uk.
<br  /><br  />
For full details of our annual Daggers Against Racism Day please click <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/daggers-against-racism-day-2017-3522716.aspx" >here</a><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//mosquefootball-86292-3524756_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//mosquefootball-169292-3524758_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-16 15:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Community,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>