<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3579953-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>THIS WEEKEND: Daggers Against Racism Day</headline>
  <page_title>THIS WEEKEND: Daggers Against Racism Day</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>THIS WEEKEND: Daggers Against Racism Day</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers will once again be hosting our annual Daggers Against Racism Day, this year’s fixture is against Guiseley AFC on Saturday 18th February 2017</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Why not head down to the Chigwell Construction Stadium this Saturday celebrate our annual Daggers Against Racism Day where the Daggers will be taking on Guiseley AFC in their 2017 Daggers Against Racism Fixture.
<br  /><br  />
Not only are the tickets heavily reduced for this fixture when purchased in advance but there is plenty of fun to be had with our pre-match entertainment.
<br  /><br  />
Head down early to make the most of the entertainment!
<br  /><br  />
Once again we will have Shake Up My Party performing with their steel band instruments outside the club shop. If just watching isn’t enough why not have a go yourself on one of the range of mini steel instruments available you for to try!
<br  /><br  />
The face painters from DABD will once again be at the ground and weather permitting our inflatable target goal will be back where you can test your accuracy against friends, family and fans alike.
<br  /><br  />
We are also very pleased to be welcoming the Dagenham and Redbridge FC Ladies team, under 13 team, our Daggers walking footballers and participants from our PL Kicks programme and other community programmes to Saturdays fixture who will be taking part in our half time Daggers Against Racism photo.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Remember, to take advantage of the heavily reduced prices tickets must be purchased in advance. Prices will return to the usual price on the day of the fixture.</strong><br  /><br  /><strong >Advanced Ticket prices:</strong><br  /><br  /><strong >Terrace:</strong><br  />
Adults - £2.50
<br  />
Concessions - £0.50
<br  />
Junior (10-16) - £0.50
<br  />
Under 10 - FREE*
<br  /><br  /><strong >Seating:</strong><br  />
Adults - £9.99
<br  />
Concessions - £4.99
<br  />
Junior (10-16) - £4.99
<br  />
Under 10 - FREE*
<br  /><strong >*Under 10's are free if purchased in advance of matchday with an Adult equivalent.</strong><br  /><br  />
You can purchase you tickets by using one of the methods below
<br  />
Online:www.daggerstickets.co.uk
<br  />
Phone: 020 8592 1549 ext 21   
<br  />
Visit us in our Club Shop
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image />
  <featured_image />
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-17 12:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Community,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team,Tickets</Tags>
</News>