<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3581207-16</articleID>
  <articleURL />
  <headline>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Ladies and Girls FC</headline>
  <page_title>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Ladies and Girls FC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Dagenham and Redbridge Community Project: Ladies and Girls FC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Leading up to our annual Daggers Against Racism day fixture against Guiseley AFC tomorrow 3:00pm KO, we are showcasing some of the projects that are run by our Community Trust</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Our Community Trust run a variety of different projects to local residents of Barking and Dagenham, one of those projects is Ladies and Girls FC. 
<div ><br /></div><div ><div>Over the past 12 months the Dagenham and Redbridge FC Community Trust have been working hard to promote football to women and girls of all ages across the borough of Barking and Dagenham and the surrounding areas.</div><div><br /></div><div>Recent funding for the National League Trust has made it possible for us to further develop our playing pathway by establishing a girls youth section and a ladies first team. </div><div><br /></div><div>The 2017-18 season will see Dagenham and Redbridge’s first under 13 and under 14 girls team enter the Essex County Girls league and our Ladies into the Women’s league.</div><div><br /></div><div>With assistance for funding partners, Essex FA and sponsors we are looking to development new teams every year providing even more opportunities for females players of the community.</div></div><div ><br /></div><div >For full details of our annual Daggers Against Racism Day please click <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/daggers-against-racism-day-2017-3522716.aspx">here</a></div><div ><br /></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//newgen2-86292-3115258_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//newgen2-169292-3115259_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-17 16:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Community,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>