<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3581152-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-ahead-of-guiseley-afc-3581152.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Guiseley AFC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Guiseley AFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Ahead Of Guiseley AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to Darren Currie ahead of Saturday's annual Daggers Against Racism Day fixture against Guiseley AFC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[With players such as Matt Robinson and Curtley Williams returning from injuries that occurred earlier in the season, Darren Currie believes the wide selection of players the staff have got to pick from is vital to keep the Daggers in the running for the top spot. 
<br  /><br  /><em >“There’s a real positive attitude at the training ground at the moment created by the run we are on and the results we are getting. Matt Robinson has trained with the team today no unopposed training as we don’t want to include contact at this point in time. Curtley Williams is training quite regularly now, so it’s just about maintaining their fitness levels, giving them game time in reserve matches and hopefully we will have them both available for selection soon. For the first time this season Luke Pennell joined in training with the team and you can’t take the smile of his face, its great news for the team and indeed Luke as he has been working extremely hard with the physio and the fitness coach to get to this point so fingers crossed he can keep training with the squad and you never know come the end of the season he might get an opportunity.”
<br /></em><br  />
With Guiseley snatching a late winner to beat FA Cup heroes Sutton United 2-1, Darren Currie will not be underestimating the Lions when they visit the Chigwell Construction Stadium this weekend.
<br  /><br  /><em >“The manager has mentioned to the players and staff at the club that every team is going to have something to play for, there isn’t anyone in this league that hasn’t got something to play for. With Guiseley being in the position they are in they're scraping for their lives just outside of the relegation zone as well as that they’ll be lifted from their win on Tuesday evening. We don’t go into any game thinking that it is going to be anything other than a difficult game, you can look at the Southport game as a prime example as for the first 15/20 minutes we didn’t settle into the game as quick as we hoped and found ourselves a goal behind. We then found the ascendancy in the game that we needed and then once again showed that when we are ruthless in front of goal with the attacking players we have got we can have spells in games where we blow teams away.”</em><br  /><br  />
Darren Currie believes to be successful in this league it’s all about grasping the balance between Young hungry, energetic players with experienced pros.
<br  /><br  /><em >“You have got to get the balance right in the team, you have got to have the right amount of young energetic players paired up with the right balance of experience in which I think Dagenham have with the likes of Andre Boucaud, Luke Guttridge and Paul Benson who has been a fantastic pro all season, he may not be getting the minutes he would like but he’s been superb on the training pitch and has contributed to the team massively.”
<br /><br /></em> With Lincoln only 3 points and a game in hand above the Daggers, Darren Currie will be focusing all his efforts on the Daggers rather than worrying about opposition in and around the promotion positions.
<br  /><br  />
“We look at Lincoln City’s current position in different ways when we discuss it as staff, will they be lifted by the massive game they have at Burnley playing at a Premier League stadium, which can either give the side a huge amount of momentum or it could be very draining because they are playing the extra games and Burnley are as hard working as any other team in the country. We focus all our efforts on ourselves what more motivation do we need than winning this home match and putting us equal with Lincoln at the top and sending a message down the road to the league leaders that we are here and ready for the battle.”  
<br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><div><div class="copy-paste-block"><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong>  
<br /></div></div></div><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-17 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>