<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3581311-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/new-signing-daggers-sign-midfielder-ray-grant-3581311.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Ray Grant</headline>
  <page_title>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Ray Grant</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>New Signing: Daggers Sign Midfielder Ray Grant</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are pleased to announce the signing of midfielder Ray Grant on a youth loan.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Ray Grant has joined the Daggers on a 3-month deal from Norwich City. Son of Peter Grant, former player and manager of the Canaries, the young midfielder followed in his father’s footsteps as he has progressed through Norwich’s youth system.
<br  /><br  />
The Scottish youth international featured earlier this year at the Chigwell Construction Stadium when he represented Norwich City U23’s that played West Ham U23’s in a Premier League 2 fixture. The Canaries lost out to the Hammers on that occasion 1-2. Grant also featured in City’s first team in the FA Cup 3rd Round replay against Southampton, with the Saints winning 1-0.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Ray Grant will be squad number 26 and will be available for squad selection tomorrow for the Daggers National League fixture against Guiseley AFC.
<br  /><br  />
We spoke to Daggers Manager John Still to get his thoughts on the signing:
<br  /><br  /><em >“I’ve been aware of Ray for the last couple of years as I know his dad who was at West Ham for a few years as the assistant manager, so because of that I was already aware of him.”
<br /><br />
“I think this season when I have seen him he’s grown up, not always in this league do U23 football player’s suit but we have seen with Shaun Donnellan, Jake Sheppard and Jordan Maguire-Drew that we have picked the right young players to come into the squad. We think Ray is the right type of player to come in. It is a difficult time with Luke Howell not quite ready to return yet and Matt Robinson not quite ready yet we are bare in that area so he will be a good addition.”</em><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//raygrant86292-3581262_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//raygrant169292-3581263_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-17 16:00:33 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Signing,Team</Tags>
</News>