<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3582307-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-1-2-guiseley-afc-3582307.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Guiseley AFC</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Guiseley AFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 2 Guiseley AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge saw their five game winning streak come to an end with a 2-1 loss at home to Guiseley in the National League.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Daggers made just one change from the win at Southport, with Ray Grant coming in for a debut at the expense of Frankie Raymond.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers fell behind in the 12th minute when Guiseley forward Jordan Preston curled a low effort past Elliot Justham from 18 yards.
<br  /><br  />
Three minutes later, Daggers were reduced to 10 men after Corey Whitely was sent off for violent conduct.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers went close to fashioning a way back into the match, with Oliver Hawkins narrowly missing two chances inside 60 seconds 10 minutes later.
<br  /><br  />
In stoppage time at the end of the first half, Daggers were awarded a penalty after Marcus Williams handled in the box, but Jordan Maguire-Drew saw the resulting spot-kick saved.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers fell further behind in the 52nd minute when Preston powerfully struck his second of the match.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers pulled one back in stoppage time when striker Oliver Hawkins converted a Joe Widdowson cross.
<br  /><br  />
Attendance: 2055 (32 away fans)
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line Ups:</strong><br  />
Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Robson, Okenabirhie (Benson, 61 mins), Hawkins, Maguire-Drew (Howells, 67 mins), Boucaud, Whitely, Grant (Doe, 45 mins), Donnellan, Sheppard
<br  /><br  />
Guiseley: Maxted, Brown, Lowe, Lawlor, Hatfield, Rooney, Preston (Boyes, 82 mins), Williams, Walton, Cassidy (Rankine, 74 mins), Asamoah (Logan, 90 mins)
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-18 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>