<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3585268-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-redbridge-1-5-portsmouth-3585268.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 5 Portsmouth</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 5 Portsmouth</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Dagenham &amp; Redbridge 1 - 5 Portsmouth</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Defeated by Powerful Pompey</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Jordy Mongoy scored the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s’ only goal as Daggers youngsters suffered a 5-1 defeat at the hands of the Portsmouth FC Academy.
<br  /><br  />
The forward, who appeared in good form as he and full-back Liam Gordon regularly combined down the left, turned and drilled a shot under the visiting keeper to reduce the arrears with his side four goals down.
<br  /><br  />
Despite some early Pompey pressure, the Daggers enjoyed the majority of possession throughout, but were regularly thwarted on the break by a clinical Pompey.
<br  /><br  />
Initially, the hosts found themselves a goal down when the away number fourteen’s freekick from 40-yards bounced in following a Paul Symes hand-ball, and the visitors were two up when the Pompey full-back found the far corner goal seven minutes later.
<br  /><br  />
The visiting team tightened their grip on the game two minutes before the interval as the away number eight volleyed in, and the number twelve extended their lead with a header before Mongoy struck.
<br  /><br  />
With ten minutes remaining, Pompey added a fifth as the away number two’s low cross was deflected past Louie Chapman from close-range as the Daggers were left to reflect on a harsh scoreline.
<br  /><br  />
The conditions of the pitch were not ideal for the way the east London outfit play.Although the hosts enjoyed more time on the ball they, at times, lacked creativity going forward, and appeared nervy in defence against a tall and physical Portsmouth side that used their height and strength to their advantage.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers again featured a number U16 players, looking to impress the Academy headcoach Micah Hyde, taking on an established Pompey side may have come as a shock to the system of the Daggers youngsters, whose performance did gradually improve as the
<br  />
encounter progressed, particularly in an encouraging and energetic second half.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers were seeking an equaliser after the away number fourteen’s free-kick sailed over a crowd of players and bounced in above the goalkeepers gloves after Symes had handled in midfield, and a pacey pursuit down the left from Liam Gordon nearly resulted in Mekhi Hyde finding the top corner with a side-footed finish after Blue Gallagher collect from the left-back and laid off the midfielder.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers persistence eventually reaped its rewards with nineteen minutes remaining, as Jordy Mongoy worked space deep inside the box to bury a low shot under the Pompey stopper to reduce the deposit back to three goals after the away number twelve had previously broken down the right, cut back and crossed for the number seven to head his side four goals up.
<br  /><br  />
After the encounter, Academy Manager Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the performance:
<br  /><br  />
“We had a number of our U16s playing today, which was good for them and their experience. Our objective was to see how these younger players cope and see if they possess qualities that we are looking for and also challenge the current U18s that were playing, against a mature Portsmouth team. So the result should be important to the players but today less significant for me, I'm interested in the development of players, and I thought our forward thinking players did alright today, in their endeavour and attitude," said a content Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“We didn't show enough quality as a team to win, but I’m not disappointed with how the game went because there were positives to be taken from it, however I am disappointed in our defensive performance, we had young and inexperienced players, but the team was built on an U18 defensive unit, which performed poorly, so again this gives me information on their development,"continued the U18s coach.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 1. Liam Tuitt (U16), 2. David Agboola, 3. Liam Gordon, 4.Dominic Odusanya, 5. Jack Lee, 6. Paul Symes, 7. Emmanuel Ogunride (U16), 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Jordy Mongoy, 10. Blue Gallagher, 11. Luke Hirst(U16) 12. Charlie Holmes, 14.Mekhi Hyde (U16), 15. Deniz Alici, 16. Dylan Florence
<br  /><br  /><strong >Goalscorers</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Jordy Mongoy 71’
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-20 10:00:43 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Fans,Home,Match</Tags>
</News>