<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3586027-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-post-guiseley-afc-3586027.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Post Guiseley AFC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Post Guiseley AFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Post Guiseley AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still after Saturday's 2-1 home defeat to Guiseley AFC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Manager John Still sees Saturday’s result as a chance missed for the Daggers but has no complaints about the result.
<br  /><br  /><em >“It was a chance missed for us on Saturday but the best team won on the day, we was down to ten men for a while in the game but we missed too many opportunities in the first half and the penalty as well and we didn’t play well enough in the game to get anything from the game.”</em><br  /><br  /><em >“I felt that we never really got into our stride in the game, there was a while leading up to half time where I thought that we were getting there and then we had the penalty that we missed. That could have changed the game as it would have changed the way we approached the second half if we had scored the penalty, as we could have afforded to break it down a little better than we did.”</em><br  /><br  />
John Still did not see the incident with Corey Whitely clearly during the game but will have words with the forward about what happened.
<br  /><br  /><em >“With the incident involving Corey Whitely, I didn’t see the incident during the game as there as a lot of players around him but he was aggrieved that he did not win a penalty. When a referee does not give you a penalty, you have to get up and get on with it and unfortunately he didn’t do that, so I will have words with him about that.”</em><br  /><br  />
With John Still’s players returning to form in recent months after starting the year with a 5 game win streak, John believes that he will have to look into the way the team plays at home after Saturday’s result.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We may have to change the way that we play at home as our pitch at the moment is not allowing us to play how we want to play at home. Our best performances have been away from home, as when you are playing away you are able to be a little bit deeper and play a little bit longer as we are not worried about entertaining people.”</em><br  /><br  /><em >“We have had a fantastic run all season and to be where we are and to overcome all the injuries that we have had has been fantastic, but we have got to stick at it and keep working hard. We were really pleased last week, this week we have had two little injuries in Guttridge and Raymond and we found out that Luke Howell, who was just getting ready to play again has just injured his thigh and Matt Robinson is still not quite ready yet. So we are still having to make little changes, but that is not why we lost the game on Saturday, I think we lacked the energy and the quality that we needed to win the game.” </em><br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong ><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//johninterview86292-3537357_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//johninterview169292-3537362_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-20 15:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>