<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3586336-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-doe-post-guiseley-afc-3586336.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Doe Post Guiseley AFC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Doe Post Guiseley AFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Doe Post Guiseley AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to captain Scott Doe after Saturday's 2-1 home defeat to Guiseley AFC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After going 5 matches unbeaten the Daggers lose an impressive streak to 20th in the league Guiseley, although Scott Doe does not believe that people should dwell on the defeat too much especially after the games prior to Saturday’s defeat.
<br  /><br  /><em >“The changing room was deflated after Saturday’s game as we do believe we should have won especially at home so it is disappointing but you also have to remind people that we have just won five games in a row prior to Saturday’s game. It is disappointing to lose the streak but we can’t dwell on Saturday’s result too much.”</em><br  /><br  /><em >“Before the game the manager did say if we win today we go joint top and if that can’t get you pumped for a game then nothing can as this is a massive incentive, if you do go top you don’t want to come off the top for the rest of the season. The defeat was hard to take but there was a lot of points taken from Saturday’s game which wasn’t how we usually play which we are disappointed in.”
<br /></em><br  />
With the Daggers receiving a red card early on and missing a penalty on the stroke of half time, Scott reflects that on another day the result would have been different.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Before I came on to the pitch I was speaking to Paul Benson on the side lines and we both said it was ‘one of those days’ where nothing was going right for us, we had a player sent off, we had chances, missed a penalty on the stroke of half time but obviously in football you have got to dig in and keep going until the end. We did manage to get one goal back at the end of the game but it is just a shame we didn’t get back into it.”</em><br  /><br  />
After Scott Doe returned from his two match game ban after his sending off away to Braintree, Doe has struggled with the lack of first team football he has been getting but understands it’s about the team winning games not himself.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I’d be lying if I didn’t say I was disappointed to not been getting as much game time as I have been recently, it has been tough as I live for games but at the end of the day it’s not about me it’s about the team and winning games. We’d won five in a row prior to this result, we haven’t always played great but we have still won games, today on the other hand ideally we didn’t want to concede again in the second half we wanted to keep it 1-0 and try get back into the game. Personally it was nice to play 45 minutes and get back out on the pitch, it is never easy coming on as a sub especially as a defender, it has been tough not starting games but as I said before it’s about winning games, it’s not about me.”           </em><br  /><br  />
Doe believes that tomorrow and next week’s games are now more important than ever to keep up the title race.
<br  /><br  /><em >“After Saturday’s result I have said to the players that these two games are more important as ever, we have to get back to winning ways and put pressure on the teams around us again, there will be other teams slipping up but we have to focus on our game and concentrate on getting back to winning ways on Tuesday.”</em>  
<br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong ><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//scottdoe86292-3535896_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//scottdoe169292-3535897_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-20 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>