<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3589489-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-post-bromley-3589489.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Post Bromley </headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Post Bromley </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Post Bromley </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to assistant manager Darren Currie after Tuesday's 2-1 home win over local rivals Bromley FC </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >The Daggers managed to scrape a 2-1 win over Bromley last night after defender Jake Sheppard scored an impressive 40 yard goal in the 88th minute of the game to seal the second win over The Ravens this season.
<br /><br /><em>“It was a fantastic goal to win the game for us although the performance wasn’t as good as how we have been playing in recent weeks. We did lack a bit of intensity but the manager has been speaking about it a lot of late about finding a way and that was what was asked of the boys at half time. We wasn’t playing as fluid as we would of liked to play, the game tonight was all about getting the ball forward quicker, not playing so many shorter passes and just finding a way of winning. Sheppard got moved from right back up to right wing as we were trying to manoeuvre the team to find that final goal that would win us the game and he’s come up with a belter of a finish to win the game for us so that was really pleasing.”</em><br /><br />
The Daggers have now come back from one nil to win the game for the third time in their last four games, although Darren admires the team’s admiration to get back into the game he believes that this is something the team must work on.
<br /><br /><em>“It has been something we have spoken about in recent weeks, we have asked the boys to play a certain way early on to eradicate early chances from the opponents but again we started really slowly again tonight and it is a small concern. Although we did win the game from very good goals the first a direct ball up the field to Hawkins whic we are able to do because Hawkins is brilliant upfront for us finished with a great controlled shot from Fejiri, the second as we mentioned was a fantastic goal to win the game.”</em><br /><br />
Darren Currie expresses that although the Daggers equalised before the half the performance of the players in the first half was disappointing and there was a lot still be done to rescue the points from Bromley.
<br /><br /><em>“The equaliser before the half changed the team talk ever so slightly but not a great deal as we were still disappointed with the performance that we displayed in the first half. What the equaliser did do and what it might have done on Saturday with the penalty is give us the platform to go into the second half. There was a spell in the game after Fejiri scored where our energy levels started to go up a little bit and I can understand there is tension at the minute as there is a big prize at the end but we have got to realise what got us in this position, our energy levels, and our fitness levels and our sharpness which are big parts of how we got to where we are in the season so far and we have got to remember that. We did have a moment of that after our first goal and we also saw a bit more into the second half, although it wasn’t pretty tonight we asked them to find a way and they done that.”
<br /></em><br />
With Lincoln City progressing into the next round of the FA Trophy after their win against National League South side Welling United, the Daggers' game against the Imps will not be played this weekend and has been rescheduled until the 4th April, meaning the Daggers will have a rest from League football this weekend; returning to League action on Tuesday for their game against Maidstone United.
<br /><br /><em>“It is good that we have got this break as we do have players getting very close to match fitness. Curtley Williams and Matt Robinson are both back in training now so they are edging closer to returning to first team football. These extra few days will help as we will be able to get some training into the boys over the weekend to prepare for another big game here on Tuesday. Hopefully the rest will relax the boys they have earned the right to win their three points tonight and we will be able to get them out training again at the back end of the week and get them prepared for the Maidstone game.”
<br /></em><br /><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-22 16:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>