<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3589741-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/culverhouse-takes-up-a-new-challenge-3589741.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Culverhouse takes up a new Challenge</headline>
  <page_title>Culverhouse takes up a new Challenge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Culverhouse takes up a new Challenge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge assistant manager Ian Culverhouse has decided to take up the offer of becoming the new manager of Kings Lynn Town in the Southern League with immediate effect. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Ian was John Still’s first addition to his team management when returning to the Daggers just over a year ago but the former Norwich City defender has always expressed his ambition of managing a club.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Although not wanting him to leave, the Club will not stand in his way and would like to place on record a big thank you for the service he has given to Dagenham &amp; Redbridge FC and to wish him every success with the Linnets.
<br  />
 
<br  />
As a player Ian was a defender with Tottenham Hotspur and was an unused substitute in the 1984 UEFA final victory against Anderlecht. He moved to Norwich City where he spent ten seasons and was part of some of the greatest moments in the club's history. After 369 appearances he moved to Swindon Town then on to Kingstonian and Brighton. It was with the Seagulls that he began his coaching career that led to him coaching the youth teams of Barnet, Leyton Orient and Wycombe Wanderers. Culverhouse was named Colchester United assistant manager under Paul Lambert and followed him to Norwich City then Aston Villa before linking up with John Still.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Ian’s assistant manager duties will be covered in the interim by Terry Harris whilst John Still looks to the future and the options available to him.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//culverhouse86292-3589722_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//culverhouse169292-3589723_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-22 17:16:33 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>