<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3589493-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-jake-howells-post-bromley-3589493.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Jake Howells Post Bromley</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Jake Howells Post Bromley</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Jake Howells Post Bromley</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We catch up with Jake Howells after the Bromley game to discuss the wingers first start for the Daggers in Tuesday's 2-1 home win</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >With Jake Howells starting his first game for the Daggers Tuesday night, Howells is happy to be getting first team game time but admits he is still not fully playing to his full potential due to the knee operation he had earlier in the season.
<br /><br /><em>“It was a tough game Bromley are a good side, we didn’t start very well very much like Saturday but it was one of them games where you have to grind for a result and we did. We do need to start games better the teams knows that now. I am delighted to get my first start for the club as I am not fully fit yet which isn’t great but with Corey Whitely being sent off on Saturday the options wasn’t great for the Manager, so for him to put me in I was very happy to get out there but I’m still trying to get sharp as it is but we got the win and that’s the most important thing.”</em><br /><br /><em>“All I'm concentrating on at the minute is getting myself back up to match fitness and getting sharper on the pitch and you can’t improve these without playing games so for me to get 60 minute out their today I’m very happy with.”</em><br /><br />
Howells won promotion from the Conference under John Still at his time at Luton Town and believes that the Daggers have the perfect opportunity with the squad that John has built to do that once again.
<br /><br /><em>“I know how the manager works and I know how he can get success in this league, I did enjoy my time playing for him at Luton and I know what he wants from me as he knows what I can give him when I’m fully fit. It is nice to have that confidence from the Manager to bring me in and give me a good contract, it’s my job now to show him and everyone at the club including the supporters what I can do, hopefully giving a boost to this squad and get us out of this league.”</em><br /><br />
The Daggers currently sit three points behind league leaders Lincoln City, although Howells does not believe it will be easy for the Imps to keep up this lead due to the amount of games they are set to play leading up to the end of the season.
<br /><br /><em>“Lincoln have got a lot of games to play and that’s not easy, I’ve been in their position and you’re playing Saturday’s and Tuesday’s, you get injuries and suspensions, it’s never easy to stay up there when you are at the top. It’s a lot easier for us chasing the league leaders and the three points here tonight was massive in keeping up that chase.”   
<br /></em><strong><br />
Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//howells86292-3590427_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//howells169292-3590429_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-23 12:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>