<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3592114-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-jake-sheppard-on-his-form-at-the-daggers-3592114.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Jake Sheppard On His Form At The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Jake Sheppard On His Form At The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Jake Sheppard On His Form At The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to defender Jake Sheppard about Tuesday's winning goal against Bromley and signing for the Daggers back in January</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Jake Sheppard feels he wasn’t playing at his best on Tuesday night but was delighted that he managed to get the winner for the Daggers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“It was almost a sense of relief when the goal went in on Tuesday for the team, and if I am being honest I wasn’t playing as well as I can and it wasn’t looking like it was going to go our way, but it is always nice to make amends for not playing well and managing to grab the winning goal for the team late on in the game.”</em><br  /><br  />
Jake is happy that he has managed to get two important goals for the team since signing for the club on loan.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I believe that going forward is one of my strong points as I have played a season on the wing before, so it is definitely the main part of my game as a full back which is the modern trend for a full back now. I like to get forward and get crosses into the box, but I don’t usually get myself into positions where I am able to score goals so it is nice for me that I have managed to get myself two goals already since signing here.”</em><br  /><br  />
The defender was delighted to be given the chance to sign here on loan and is confident that we will stay near the top of the table for the rest of the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I was aware that a few people from here had come to watch me play and it was nice for me that a team wanted me to join them on loan. When I signed here we was in the play-off position’s and that was a great position for the club to be in and I wanted to be able to help them stay in the play-offs and if not win the league.  We have won six of our last seven games now and that is the form that we need to keep in order to stay near the top of the table which is where we want to be.”</em><br  /><br  />
Sheppard has had no problems in fitting into the squad and thinks the competition in the squad will make everybody better.
<br  /><br  /><em >“There is a really good bunch of players here and they are all easy to get on with, so I had no problems at all in making myself part of the squad and part of the team. There is healthy competition in the team and having many players who can play in one position adds pressure to make you perform better and do more for the team when you play.”</em><br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jakesheppard-86292-3592474_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jakesheppard-169292-3592475_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-24 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>