<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3596966-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-barnet-2-5-dagenham-redbridge-3596966.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Barnet 2 - 5 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Barnet 2 - 5 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Barnet 2 - 5 Dagenham &amp; Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Defeat Barnet</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A seven goal thriller in North London saw the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s dismiss the Barnet FC Academy for a second time in the space of a month following their 4-1 thrashing of the Bees three weeks ago.
<br  /><br  />
In a Daggers-dominated tie, Jordy Mongoy shone brightly as part of an unforgiving Daggers attack, assisting twice and scoring once in the east London side’s 5-2 rout.
<br  /><br  />
However, it was Barnet that got the opener with a tap-in from the home number nine, but Dylan Florence drew the visitors level with a smart finish, before Elliot Bonds side-footed the Daggers into 58th minute lead.
<br  /><br  />
Jordy Mongoy rounded the Bees keeper to open up a two-goal cushion for his side, and Florence gave the Daggers their fourth with his second of the game, completing his hat-trick shortly after the Bees number eleven broke free and slid home to reduce the deposit.
<br  /><br  />
The encounter endured a relatively cagey opening – although the Daggers enjoyed more possession and demonstrated good endeavour to break forward and create problems for the Barnet defence, the quality of the end product occasionally lacked when it mattered, and goalscoring opportunities came few and far between as a result.
<br  /><br  />
However, a much-improved second half from the Daggers was more than enough to thwart the Bees resilience as the visitors upped the tempo and were clinical in possession, producing a host of opportunities from their quick, incisive passing and relentless forward movement.
<br  /><br  />
The opening fifteen minutes laid a promising foundation for the away side as they came close to netting the opener on two occasions.
<br  /><br  />
But the visitors were unexpectedly pegged back when the Bees number nine touched in at the far post from a left-wing cross to give the hosts the lead against the run of play.
<br  /><br  />
Although the visitors were yet to fully warm to the game, they demonstrated good perseverance, committing men forward as they edged closer to an equaliser.
<br  /><br  />
And it was the familiar face of Dylan Florence who popped up with the leveller on the stroke of half time with a brilliant finish, working his way into the box ahead of cutting back and stroking past the outstretched glove of the Bees number one.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers’ form drastically improved in an entertaining second half, producing more moments of adversity for busy Bees backline as the away side battled on to acquire the game’s next goal.
<br  /><br  />
It was a stylish move down the left involving Liam Gordon and Jordy Mongoy that awarded the visitors their next chance, which was coolly dispatched by Elliot Bonds with a side-footed finish low into the corner from left-back Gordon’s inviting cross, before Mongoy himself got on the scoresheet, rounding a helpless Bees stopper and rolling in for 3-1.
<br  /><br  />
And their intense pressure once again paid dividends, with Dylan Florence grabbing his second of the game, slamming in the rebound after the Bees stopper parried Elliot Bonds’ drilled volley.
<br  /><br  />
By this point, the hosts were firmly in control of the tie as they looked to see out the final 20 minutes of the encounter.
<br  /><br  />
They were however, provided with a harsh reminder to guard against all complacency by the home number eleven who, in a rare moment of defensive slacking from the away side, ran clear and slid beneath the Daggers stopper for 4-2.
<br  /><br  />
Mercifully for the Daggers, Dylan Florence’s third strike of the game rendered the Bees’ second a mere consolation as striker Florence latched on to an exquisite Elliot Bonds through ball to slot into the corner as the hosts emerged from North London as the victors for the second time in a month.
<br  /><br  />
Academy Manager Micah Hyde's thoughts, "It was an improved performance defensively, and      the positive game understanding required and quality in the final third when it mattered, which wasn't enough in the first half. Overall it was dominant performance with aspects to improve on, defensively and attacking." said Hyde.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 13. Louie Chapman, 2. Kieran Walker-Browne, 3. Liam Gordon, 4. Paul Symes, 5. David Agboola, 6. Jack Lee, 7. Micah Archer, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Dylan Florence, 10. Jordy Mongoy, 11. Mustaphe Ali, 12. Charlie Holmes, 14. Blue Gallagher, 15. Dominic Odusanya
<br  /><br  /><strong >Goalscorers</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Dylan Florence 44’, 70', 75’, Elliot Bonds 58’, Jordy Mongoy 63’
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-27 11:30:17 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>