<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3596789-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-player-commentary-dagenham-and-redbridge-v-maidstone-united-3596789.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Dagenham and Redbridge v Maidstone United</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Dagenham and Redbridge v Maidstone United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Player Commentary: Dagenham and Redbridge v Maidstone United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>If you are unable to make it to Tuesday's home fixture against Maidstone United, tune in to Daggers Player for live commentary and updates from the Chigwell Construction Stadium</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Jake Sheppard’s last minute winner had Mick and I out of our seats such was the quality of his strike against Bromley last Tuesday. You always hope as a commentator you do the goal justice and describe it with appropriate detail and hopefully we did.
<br  /><br  />
Tomorrow Mick Payne and I will take our usual seats in the Carling Stand and will once again be on air from 7.25 as the Daggers host Maidstone United. Home hasn’t always been the happiest place for the Daggers and John will be hoping for a much improved performance from his side and a successive win.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The team frequently show week after week they have fight and belief as they came from behind for the second time in three games to bag all three points. This is our last game before what is likely to be a season defining month in March and is another chance to put the pressure on Lincoln at the top.
<br  />
 
<br  />
If you can’t get to the game tune in for full live match coverage with James Glass with features including ‘Mick Payne’s Top Corner Challenge’ and all the news surrounding the club.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-86292-3398049_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-169292-3398050_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-02-27 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>