<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3601407-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-on-tuesdays-defeat-to-maidstone-united-3601407.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still On Tuesday's Defeat To Maidstone United</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still On Tuesday's Defeat To Maidstone United</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still On Tuesday's Defeat To Maidstone United</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still after Tuesday's 2-0 home defeat to his former club Maidstone United</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Maidstone took the lead within the first six minutes in the game after a speculative volley from the edge of the box from Stones midfielder Joe Pigott. John believes that although it was a good goal the defending leading up to the strike should have been better.
<br /><br /><em>“Maidstone started with a good goal although our defending leading up to that goal was poor, we had several chances to clear our lines and didn’t do so and from that he struck a good goal. From that moment on in the first half I thought they looked the more likely to score again. In the second half we had more than enough of the ball but nowhere near enough quality, it was a long way off what we are capable of and what we have produced over the season. To win games you have got to have some kind of quality in which we didn’t have on Tuesday.”
<br /></em><br />
Throughout the season the Daggers have struggled with countless first team injuries and with key midfielders such as Guttridge and Robinson still out with injuries the manager believes it is a position the team is struggling with options.
<br /><br /><em>“</em><em>With Robinson, Guttridge, Howell and Howells out with injuries w</em><em>e haven’t got a great amount of midfield players at the moment, we have had this porblem all season; a lack of enough players in certain areas, we were struggling in midfield and we would have liked to make a change. Neither of our wide players produced what they are capable of, Okenabirhie has been out with an injury so his form will drop but we never really got anything out of Maguire-Drew tonight his quality was poor. We never provided enough service for the front two with a scoring opportunity.”</em><br /><br />
Mark Cousins started his first league fixture on Tuesday evening, Still stated that he felt this was the right time to give Mark his opportunity after Elliot Justham’s performance last week against Bromley.
<br /><br /><em>“Justham has done brilliant this season, although I thought he was a bit off his game last week and I felt it was the right time to let Cousins have an opportunity. This decision doesn’t mean that Elliot won’t play the next game I just felt it was the right thing to do. The reason that we decided to put Doe in the full back position is because he is our captain and we felt today we would need another leader on the pitch.”</em><br /><br />
With twelve fixtures left, John Still will not let the defeat to Maidstone affect him or his players, the manager accepted the defeat but now will be looking to repair the form on Saturday for the Daggers’ away fixture to Gateshead.
<br /><br /><em>“This is football there will be highs and lows, I’ve been in this game for 40 years and you can’t be affected by one game you’ve got to be affected by a season and the season has told us up to this point we are second in the league which is unbelievable to what we would of hoped at the beginning of the season. I have to accept that sometimes players aren’t going to play well but we will have to respond to that on Saturday.”</em><br /><br /></div><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jstillmaidstone-86292-3601635_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jstillmaidstone-169292-3601637_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-01 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>