<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3603855-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-gateshead-fc-vs-dagenham-and-redbridge-3603855.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Gateshead FC vs Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Gateshead FC vs Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Gateshead FC vs Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Daggers' Vanarama National League away fixture at Gateshead on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Originally constructed in 1955 and the home of Gateshead FC since 1970, the Gateshead International Stadium has a capacity to hold 11,800 spectators and is a multi-purpose all-seater arena. Unsurprisingly given the stadium’s status as a home of athletics, all four stands are set-back from the pitch making it difficult for an atmosphere to be created on matchday. Gateshead generally only make use of the two all-seater covered stands running along both sides of the pitch, both of which are unrestricted with a combined capacity of 7,271. The stadium also serves as a home for the Gateshead Thunder Rugby League Club.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
Although there isn’t a great deal of eating establishments on the streets surrounding the stadium, if you walk five minutes along Park Road towards Newcastle, you will come across a McDonalds on your right. If you have some time pre-match or are travelling by train, it is best advised to head into Newcastle City Centre which has a wide variety of food outlets and pubs. Pubs in Newcastle include The Town Wall, BrewDog Newcastle which specialises in Scottish craft beers, and the Quayside Bar which is a JD Wetherspoon located on the banks of the Tyne by Javel Groupe roundabout. Closer to Gateshead Metro Station, however, you also have The Black Bull and The Tilley Stone, both of which are within a five minute walk from the station.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-gateshead-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3577188.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />
An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-gateshead-fc-3599572.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-02 11:30:30 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>