<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3604528-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/dagenham-and-redbridge-golf-day-2017-3604528.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Dagenham and Redbridge Golf Day 2017 </headline>
  <page_title>Dagenham and Redbridge Golf Day 2017 </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Dagenham and Redbridge Golf Day 2017 </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Ever fancied having a round of golf with a member of the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge playing or management staff? Well now is your chance! </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[There are now places available for the annual Daggers Golf Day which will take place on Monday 24th April at Maylands Golf Club in Romford.
<br  /><br  />
The beautifully constructed 18 hole, par 71 championship golf course provides the perfect setting for a day of competition and fun with the Daggers players and management.
<br  /><br  />
Golfers will go around in groups of four including a member of the first team playing squad or coaching staff getting involved in the action.
<br  /><br  />
A full day’s programme of entertainment is on offer commencing with bacon rolls and tea or coffee in the clubhouse before the tee off.
<br  /><br  />
Teams will then be invited to play 18-holes and on completion all players can return to the club house to enjoy a well-deserved pre-dinner drink, followed by a two course meal and the all-important awards ceremony.
<br  /><br  />
Tee off times will begin at 1.30pm and teams of 3 are available for just £195.00 with individual places only £65.00.
<br  /><br  />
If you are not a golfer, you can attend the evening two course meal and Q&amp;A session with John Still for only £25.
<br  /><br  />
For further information or to make a booking please contact the commercial department on 0208 592 1549 ext 33 or email commercial@daggers.co.uk
<br  /><br  />
Alternatively download your booking form <a xlink:href="tcm:0-3605022" title="Daggers Golf Day Booking Form 2017"   xlink:title="Daggers Golf Day Booking Form 2017">here</a> and email to commercial@daggers.co.uk or post to Commercial Department, Dagenham &amp; Redbridge FC, Victoria Road, Dagenham, Essex, RM10 7XL.
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//golfday201786292-3604520_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//golfday2017169292-3604521_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-21 17:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>