<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3605580-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-player-live-commentary-gateshead-fc-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3605580.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Gateshead FC v Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Gateshead FC v Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Gateshead FC v Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>If you are unable to make it to Saturday's away fixture against Gateshead FC, tune in to Daggers Player for live commentary and updates from the Gateshead International Stadium</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The first game of March sees us taking the train to Gateshead for one of the longest trips of the season. If you cannot make the journey do not worry as James Glass from the Daggers player will be there to bring you full match commentary.
<br  /><br  />
James will be joined by a member of squad who is not involved in the day. He will give a unique insight into the teams thought and performance on the day as the Daggers look to bounce back from their defeat against Maidstone.
<br  /><br  />
As is now the norm the show will begin 20 minutes before kick-off at 2.40. Mick Payne’s Top Corner Challenge and One to Watch will continue as features with Mick providing thoughts on the phone.
<br  /><br  />
March is a big month for the Daggers as we play teams all vying for promotion with the exception of York. Gateshead is the first of these matches and promises to be an exciting game.
<br  /><br  />
The last few games for Dagenham have had it all with goals, penalties, red cards,  goals ruled out, stunning finishes and last minute winners. Join the team on Saturday for more of this exciting and entertaining football from the boys in red and blue.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-86292-3398049_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-169292-3398050_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-03 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>