<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3606040-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-ahead-of-gateshead-3606040.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie On The Season Run In</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie On The Season Run In</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie On The Season Run In</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to Darren Currie on the last few home games and got his thoughts on the last twelve games of the season </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Darren Currie was disappointed with the performance from the Daggers in Tuesday’s 2-0 home defeat to local rivals Maidstone United.
<br  /><br  /><em >“It was another bad start and we keep giving ourselves a mountain to climb, we are playing a little bit out of sorts at the minute and we are not playing as freely as we have done throughout the season up to now. We never really looked like we were going to get back into the game, we had a go and Hawkins had an opportunity in the first half that could have got us level but we are not playing with confidence that we have previously displayed which is frustrating.”</em><br  /><br  />
Currie says that the team has been making too many mistakes recently but that the players are showing the hard work in training that is needed for the last set of games this season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have to look at how we are contributing to our own downfall at the minute and at the minute we are making too many mistakes, when we was playing well we was making mistakes then as well but we were overcoming them mistakes and now at the minute when we make a mistake we seem to close up a little bit. We are a good team and we have very good players, recently we have just been playing below the standards that we have set ourselves this season but the effort and determination that they have been showing in training is telling me that we are going to cover come thus and we have to remain as positive as we can.”</em><br  /><br  />
Darren Currie is not expecting any easy games between now and the end of the season with most teams having something to play for between now and the end of the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have twelve games left until the end of the season now and we have to play at the levels which we know we are capable of and we have had a talk with the squad this week and hopefully that with be a positive for us. These last twelve games some of them are not going to be where there is good football being played, there is going to be games that we fall behind again, there will be some games where we will dominate the ball, and others are going to be a scrap or a fight. So there is going to be a mix of different types of games that we are going to come up against and we have shown already that whatever sort of games is thrown at us, we can cope with it.”</em><br  /><br  />
Mark Cousins made his first league start for the Daggers this season against Maidstone United on Tuesday and Darren says the goalkeeper deserved his chance.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Mark is a terrific professional and he has been outstanding this season, I know that he has not played as much football this year that he would have wanted but he conducts himself superbly in training and he is a great lad who has pushed Elliot Justham all season. Mark rightly deserved his opportunity on Tuesday and the manager just thought that because of recent performances Mark deserved an opportunity to show his worth.”</em><br  /><br  />
With first team players such as Robinson, Howell, Guttridge and Howells missing the team has lacked a little bit of experience in recent weeks.
<br  /><br  /><em >“They are all experienced pros and maybe we have a lacked a little bit of knowledge and experience in the last few games but that can be easy to say when you lose. We have had times in the season where we have had to have players out injured or missing and we have overcome that, but unfortunately we just having been able to overcome it in two of our last three home games. They are crucial players for us and we want them all fit and available for the last few games so that we have a nice selection dilemma until the end of the season.”</em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-03 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>