<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3610466-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-0-0-cheltenham-town-3610466.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 Cheltenham Town</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 Cheltenham Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 0 - 0 Cheltenham Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>A goalless draw at Parkonians deprived the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s a much-warranted victory as the Cheltenham Town academy held on for a point.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers were the dominant side throughout and appeared creative and ambitious, but surprisingly on this occasion lacked composure in front of goal.
<br  /><br  />
Two of the game’s best chances fell to forward Jordy Mongoy, but the Robins stopper denied the wideman on both occasions after two good saves from substitute goalkeeper Louie Chapman prevented the visitors taking a second-half lead.
<br  /><br  />
Going into the game, the Daggers were in good goalscoring form, with last week’s sensational victory away at Barnet to reflect on for attacking inspiration having netted five times against the Bees.
<br  /><br  />
Their victory in north London was the fourth time in five games Micah Hyde’s side had scored four or more goals in a single fixture, and were looking to extend that run with a convincing victory against the Robins.
<br  /><br  />
The opportunities to do so were unequivocally present from an early stage with Jordy Mongoy and Kieron Walker Brown close to providing an opener after the former touched towards goal from Liam Gordon’s cross following a powerful run from the wingback before the latter curled inches wide after outwitting his man with a neat step-over.
<br  /><br  />
Mustaphe Ali was involved in the Daggers’ next two chances, blasting over after collecting from Liam Gordon’s silky run, before supplying Jordy Mongoy to cross for a well-positioned Dylan Florence, who placed wide.
<br  /><br  />
An entertaining second half produced an even bigger array of opportunities for the home side, most of which fell to the goal-hungry figures of Jordy Mongoy and Dylan Florence.
<br  /><br  />
But on a number of occasions, Liam Gordon cleverly exploited space on the inside left channel and found himself with a clear shot at goal.
<br  /><br  />
However, the left-back was denied at the near post by a miserly Robins stopper shortly before dragging his second chance of the game from similar territory wide as the superior Daggers increased their intensity.
<br  /><br  />
Both chances occurred either side of a clean-through Dylan Florence ballooning an effort over the Robins crossbar and Jordy Mongoy, with the goal at his mercy, seeing his effort from a one-on-one deep inside the Robins box miraculously saved by the away keeper to the disbelief of the Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
As the encounter entered the final ten minutes, both Jordy Mongoy and Dylan Florence had good chances to atone for their earlier misses.
<br  /><br  />
But to the misfortune of the hosts, recent history was to repeat itself as Mongoy, running clear at goal for a second time, failed to generate sufficient power on his finish to beat the keeper, before Florence, with time and space in the opposition box, fired over the bar after collecting from midfield and turning at goal, leaving the Daggers to settle for a point.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Academy Manager Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the tie:</strong><br  /><br  />
“Pleased with the team performance today, superior in almost every department, except the important one, we created so many chances, particularly one-on-ones, especially in 2nd half, they normally take some,” said Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“Defensively extremely pleased for the defensive unit a clean sheet is their main objective. As a team I asked them to give the same performance as last week, and they did, they were just unable to get the three points to match their endeavour but everything else was there and all I can ask for,” the Headcoach continued.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Line Up:</strong> Joe Carter, David Agboola, Liam Gordon, Jack Lee, Kieron Walker-Browne, Paul Symes, Elliot Bonds, Micah Archer, Jordy Mongoy, Dylan Florence, Mustaphe Ali, Charlie Holmes, Blue Gallagher, Louie Chapman, Dominic Odusanya
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-06 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>