<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3613224-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/friendly-match-report-barnet-fc-1-2-dagenham-and-redbridge-3613224.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Friendly Match Report: Barnet FC 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Friendly Match Report: Barnet FC 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Friendly Match Report: Barnet FC 1 - 2 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers travelled to North London yesterday for a behind closed doors friendly against League Two side Barnet FC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[With players such as Curtley Williams and Matt Robinson featuring in the squad, this game allowing players the game time they need to return to full match fitness.
<br  /><br  />
The first chance in the game came in the 7th minute after a clever one two pass between forwards Sam Akinde and Fumnaya Shomotun which left the Barnet striker Shomotun one-on-one with Cousins, although the Daggers keeper got down well to his left and parried the ball past the post.
<br  /><br  />
After 10 minutes of dominant football from the League Two side the Daggers bounced back in the 16th minute with a looping corner ball from Howells which was met by Paul Benson’s head at the back post, the Barnet keeper quickly reacted pushing the ball off the line and back into the box finally being cleared by the defending team.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers tested the keeper once again in the 22nd minute after a clearance from Sam Ling was cleverly headed on by Paul Benson into the path Corey Whitely who beat his marker which left him with a tough angle and the forward could only slice the ball the wrong side of the post.
<br  /><br  />
Barnet once again came close to scoring in the 37th minute after Barnet forward Shomotun turned Liam Gordon and found a gap through the Daggers defence to find himself in front of the Daggers goalkeeper the forward slotted his shot through Cousins’ legs only to be cleared off the line by Sam Ling and collected by Cousins.
<br  /><br  />
The final chance of the half came from a corner deep into stoppage time, after a Howells’ cross found an arriving Benson who knocked the ball down to find Whitely who striked the ball acrobatically only narrowly missing the goal mouth.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers started the second half with an ascendancy and with 5 minutes gone young scholar Jordi Mongoy gave the Daggers the lead after a corner from Howells was only cleared as far as the edge of the penalty box to find the young forward who placed the ball in the bottom right hand corner.
<br  /><br  />
Two minutes later the hosts answered with a swift reply after winning a corner, Barnet defender Dan Sweeney rose above his marker to head the ball past the reach of Cousins.
<br  /><br  />
The final goal came in the 74th minute after the Daggers broke quickly after a clearance from full back Sam Ling, Jordi Mongoy cleverly brought the ball down beating his marker and slotting the ball past the Barnet keeper completing his brace.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-08 10:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Reserves,Team</Tags>
</News>