<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3616708-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-joe-widdowson-ahead-of-forest-green-rovers-3616708.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Joe Widdowson Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Joe Widdowson Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Joe Widdowson Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to defender Joe Widdowson ahead of the big clash against promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers on Saturday. </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<br  />
After the Daggers have lost their last 3 games out 4, Widdowson is determined to get back to winning ways after the Gateshead defeat on Saturday.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I think that everyone is looking forward to this weekend’s game at home and put it right after last weekend’s defeat and that is our focus at the minute. The boys are always talking with one another about what we can work and improve on so everyone is aware of what we need to improve on it is just about putting it into practice on Saturday.”</em><br  /><br  />
The defender is expecting a good game of football between two teams at the top of the table when the Daggers meet Forest green on Saturday.
<br  /><br  /><em >“This Saturday is a very big game and when we played them away earlier in the season I think that it was one of the best footballing games that we have played in this season, so we know that they like to play and we do as well so hopefully we will be at our best on Saturday. They have a lot of talented players in their squad and have invested a lot more than us so they are expecting to be challenging at the top which we are as well.”</em><br  /><br  />
Christian Doidge will be returning to the Daggers this Saturday and Widdowson is not surprised by how well the forward has been doing since his summer move to Forest Green Rovers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Christin Doidge is a very good player and his last six months here I believe that he showed that for us, I am pleased to see him doing well as he is a good friend of mine. I am not surprised by how well he has done this season as he is a striker that if you give him a good supply he will score goals.”</em><br  /><br  />
The Daggers have currently not been beaten by any of the top six teams in the National League, with the Likes of Forest Green, Aldershot and Lincoln all still to play Widdowson believes although there has been a drop in form the Daggers can still win all of these top flight games.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Maybe we raise our game a little bit more against the big teams but that shouldn’t be the case as we should be as focused when we face someone like Guiseley and Maidstone as when we play someone like Forest Green. We haven’t picked up the amount of points that we would have expected too against the lower teams but we can’t dwell on that we need to rectify that and put it right starting on Saturday.”</em><br  /><br  />
Widdowson says that the play-offs will be the minimum that the Daggers are hoping for and will still be looking to try to knock lead leaders Lincoln off the top spot.
<br  /><br  /><em >“The play-offs need to be the minimum for us and we are still looking at the top of the table and we need to get as many points as possible between now and the end of the season.”
<br /></em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//joewiddowsonnew-86292-3616734_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//joewiddowsonnew-169292-3616735_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-09 16:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>