<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3616181-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-player-live-commentary-daggers-v-forest-green-rovers-3616181.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Dagenham and Redbridge v Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Dagenham and Redbridge v Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Player Live Commentary: Daggers v Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>If you are unable to make it to Saturday's home fixture against promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers, tune in to Daggers Player for live commentary and updates from the Chigwell Construction Stadium</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Forest Green Rovers head to the Chigwell Construction this Saturday. The Daggers have had a dramatic turnaround in form. After winning the first five in 2017 they have followed that up with 3 defeats in the last four. The absence of Corey Whitley has coincided with the dip in form and he will be available for selection on Saturday having served a three game ban.</div><div > </div><div >The game is the second of the four big games the Daggers have in March. After this top of the table clash a trip to Barrow and Aldershot follow. A bit of advanced warning that at present no commentary will be available for the game at Barrow AFC next Saturday.  </div><div > </div><div >James Glass who traveled to Gateshead last week will be back in his usual seat in the main stand giving live commentary of the game. The show starts at the usual time of 2.40 pm. James will be joined by a co-commentator and Mick Payne will offer his thoughts on the phone. Features including Ned's News and Mick Payne's one to watch along with all the big stories affecting the Daggers.</div><div > </div><div >Join James from 2.40pm on Saturday to catch the full coverage of the game. </div><div > </div><div >If you want to join Daggers Player follow the link <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/Buy">here</a>.</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-86292-3398049_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//daggersplayer-169292-3398050_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-09 12:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>