<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3617756-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-ahead-of-forest-green-rovers-3617756.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still ahead of tomorrow's promotion clash against Forest Green Rovers</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[John Still was disappointed with the result away to Gateshead on Saturday after keeping up such a good away record prior to the game.
<br  /><br  />
“I don’t get any problems in training, the boys are very good and everybody works hard. It was a tough game last week against Gateshead but they are on a bit of a good run and they beat Forest Green a couple of week earlier 3-1 and we lost by the odd goal. They had a lot of the ball in the first half and had quite a few chances, but I thought that our defending for their goal was poor. Once they scored the goal I thought that we were the better team and we had forced them to change their system by a little adjustment that they had made. Our away record is very good and I don’t have any problems with our away performances as it is our home form that has not been as good as we would have liked it to be.”
<br  /><br  />
Matt Robinson and Curtley Williams both played in a friendly midweek and the manager hopes to get another friendly sorted for next week to keep the squad fully fit.
<br  />
 
<br  />
“Matt Robinson and Curtley Williams both played in a behind closed doors friendly on Tuesday and they were a bit sore after the game so we will know more next week. Matt Robinson seems to have recovered well and Curtley Williams is aching a little bit because he has been out for a long time. Luke Howell was also back in training this week and he is ahead of schedule, and we hope to get another friendly sorted for next Tuesday which hopefully he can play in along with Robinson and Williams. These friendly games are really important for us as the one on Tuesday was a good opportunity to get minutes into Sam Ling, Paul Benson, Corey Whitely and Josh Staunton, and also gave us another opportunity to see the younger lads playing a game like Liam Gordon and Jordan Mongoy.”
<br  /><br  />
John Still believes that the Daggers have struggled with midfield options in recent months with injuries to Matt Robinson, Luke Howell and Luke Guttridge.
<br  />
 
<br  />
“Midfield is an area for us that we have a lot of continuity in this season with Guttridge, Howell and Robinson all having problems throughout the season. When we play at home we need to take the game more to the opposition and I think that sometimes when we have played at home we haven’t had the players we have needed to be able to take the game and play our football. Away from home you are able to sit a little deeper and the home team will bring the game to us.”
<br  /><br  />
The manager is expecting a tough battle on Saturday especially from former Daggers Christian Doidge.
<br  /><br  />
“Christian Doidge is a player that I liked and we wanted to keep him here but he has done very well for Forest Green this year. He didn’t score as many goals for us last year as he has done this year for Forest Green but last year he was playing in a struggling team and this season he is playing for a team that is near the top of the table. We will have to be ready for the challenge on Saturday as he is a 100% player and I always say that players like that are always dangerous as they will never stop working and running.”
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//johninterview86292-3537357_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//johninterview169292-3537362_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-10 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>