<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3617200-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/charity-auction-signed-1516-season-frame-signed-shirt-3617200.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>CHARITY AUCTION: 15/16 Season Frame Signed Shirt</headline>
  <page_title>CHARITY AUCTION: 15/16 Season Frame Signed Shirt</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>CHARITY AUCTION: 15/16 Season Frame Signed Shirt</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Stammers family have kindly donated a framed signed shirt to be be auctioned off with all money raised going towards supporting the St Francis Hospice </short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Four of Dagenham &amp; Redbridge's most ardent supporters, David, Christine, Caroline and Michael Stammers have once again approached the Club to support St Francis Hospice, a charity close to the heart of the Club.
<br  /><br  />
As well as season ticket holders and attending all our away games the "Stammers Family", as they are affectionately known, also sponsor a number of matchballs each season, giving away tickets and signed balls to local charities.
<br  /><br  />
Recently the family had a shirt, signed by the 2015/16 squad framed and now wish to auction it with all the proceeds going to St Francis Hospice.
<br  /><br  />
The shirt is currently on the Clubs eBay site and anyone wishing to bid have a week to do so, the listing will end next Thursday at 4:30pm.
<br  /><br  />
This is a fantastic gesture by the "Stammers Family" and we hope that there are some individuals or companies out there willing to support St Francis Hospice and at the same time acquire this fine piece of Dagenham and Redbridge memorabilia.
<br  /><br  />
Click <a href="http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/CHARITY-AUCTION-Dagenham-and-Redbridge-15-16-Season-Framed-Signed-Shirt-/322447017402?hash=item4b135705ba:g:e0gAAOSw4CFYwX%7EH" >here</a> to go the Clubs eBay account where you can bid on the signed shirt.
<br  /><br  />
If you want to find out more about Saint Francis Hospice please click <a href="https://www.sfh.org.uk/" >here</a> to go to the Hospice's website.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//hospice86292-3617791_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//hospice169-1292-3617792_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-16 11:30:23 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>