<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3619129-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/manager-john-still-signs-contract-extension-3619129.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Manager John Still Signs Contract Extension</headline>
  <page_title>Manager John Still Signs Contract Extension</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Manager John Still Signs Contract Extension</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Football Club are pleased to announce that manager John Still has signed a two-year extension to his contract</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The new contract for John Still will see him remain in charge at the Chigwell Construction Stadium until the end of the 2018/19 season.
<br  /><br  />
John was appointed for his third spell in charge of The Daggers on 1st January 2016, having also been in charge of the Club for two years from July 1992 and nine years from April 2004.
<br  /><br  />
Since his most recent return he has totally rebuilt the squad with young, hungry players and managed to gel them together to mount a promotion bid this season.
<br  /><br  />
John has had a long career in the game that has seen unprecedented success. Leading three teams Maidstone United, Dagenham &amp; Redbridge and Luton Town into the Football League.
<br  /><br  />
His playing career was cut short by a knee injury having played for Orient, Dagenham and Bishops Stortford, where he won an Amateur Cup winners medal in the last ever final and he turned to management with Leytonstone Ilford and Dartford where he won a Southern League and Isthmian League title. He then took Maidstone United to the Conference title but decided against going full time and joined Redbridge Forest whom he won the Isthmian League with.
<br  /><br  />
The lure of a Football League management job took him to Peterborough in 1994 then on to Barnet via a coaching spell at Lincoln City.  Still took Barnet into the Division Three play-offs on two occasions. When Tony Cottee was appointed manager, he became director of football but was reinstated two years later after a slump in form. This was then followed by a spell as assistant manager with Bristol Rovers before his second spell at the Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
Not only did John take the Daggers into the Football League, but he guided the club to the 2010 League Two play-offs where they beat Morecambe 7-2 on aggregate in the semi-final after a remarkable 6-0 first leg triumph. He went onto lead the team out at Wembley and a memorable season was complete, with a 3-2 win over Rotherham United. He was later recognised for this success by being awarded the BBC London's Sports Personality of the Year (2010-11).
<br  /><br  />
In search of a new challenge he took over the reigns at Luton Town in February 2013 and in his first full season at Kenilworth Road, he ended The Hatters s five-year exile from the Football League.
<br  /><br  />
John is a Freeman of the Town of Luton and the Borough of Barking &amp; Dagenham.
<br  /><br  />
We caught up with Manager John Still to get his thoughts behind the extension:
<br  /><br  />
“I think that I was quite open when I came back to the Daggers that this season could be my last year, and if I am being honest it has been a funny season this year because we brought a lot of young players in this season and we was not sure how they would all do. The players we did bring in have done great for us and I believe that they will keep on growing, we have had the difficulties with the club situation in terms of a new owner.”
<br  /><br  />
“I just felt that when the club spoke to me that the club has been stabilised this year on and off the pitch. Hopefully as a club we can all push on and I felt that having spoken to the club about it the situation that we are in, where I feel that the club is growing I feel that it is right that I stay initially to make sure that everything that we do is leading us in the right path.”
<br  /><br  />
“Dagenham &amp; Redbridge is my club and when I do go, whether we are in this league or in League Two I would like to look back when I go that I have left all of the foundations for this club to grow again and that is how I feel.” 
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//contract86292-3619350_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//contract169292-3619351_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-11 14:45:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>