<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3622497-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-afc-wimbledon-1-0-dagenham-and-redbridge-3622497.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: AFC Wimbledon 1 - 0 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: AFC Wimbledon 1 - 0 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: AFC Wimbledon 1 - 0 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Suffer Narrow Dons Defeat</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[An early goal from the Dons number eleven resigned the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s to a narrow defeat despite a display of good resilience against the AFC Wimbledon academy.
<br  /><br  />
Up against a strong and physical Dons side, the visitors occasionally struggled to maintain regular bouts of possession, and clear-cut chances came few and far between as a result.
<br  /><br  />
The closest they came was a ferocious Elliot Bonds volley that slammed against the upright deep into the first 45.
<br  /><br  />
Going into the game, the hosts arrived in south-west London looking to return to winning ways following last week’s goalless home draw against Cheltenham Town, an encounter that saw Micah Hyde’s side dominate, but fail to capitalise on their creativity with that all-important winning goal in a tie that could have witnessed the Daggers score three or four.
<br  /><br  />
The endeavour to do so in their meeting with the Dons was undoubtedly present, but the hosts made it difficult for the Daggers to gain a momentous start.
<br  /><br  />
The hosts started on the front foot, pressing high and seeking to break down a Daggers defence that did consistently well to stand up to an unforgiving Dons attack that could only muster two attempts in the opening stages of the game.
<br  /><br  />
The visitors were let off early after a Dons man was brought down in the box, with the number seven firing the resulting penalty wide, but were punished later when they failed to bring the home number eleven’s run to a halt, leaving the forward to back heel in from the tightest of angles.
<br  /><br  />
But the game soon turned on the home side as the Daggers began to gain some authority of the tie.
<br  /><br  />
When left-back Deniz Alici’s ball landed at the feet of Tyrique Hyde, the midfielder shot at goal but saw his effort blocked, before another goal bound effort from the Daggers man was once again charged down by a home defender.
<br  /><br  />
However, it was Elliot Bonds who came closest to a reply with a sensational right-footed volley that left the frame of the goal shaking after the ball fell to the midfielder eighteen yards out.
<br  /><br  />
With half time beckoning, a goal would have added a completely new complexion to the game, but to the relief of AFC Wimbledon, who so easily could have been level going into the interval, the Daggers’ acclimatisation to the game could not be capped with an equaliser.
<br  /><br  />
The second half saw the away side play with more positivity and confidence as they set out to thwart the Dons with an energetic display.
<br  /><br  />
Blue Gallagher was the architect of the Daggers’ next chance as the midfielder’s persistent
<br  />
run down the right saw him evade two challenges and send in a superb low cross that narrowly escaped several Daggers boots, before a Deniz Alici cross from the opposite flank flew across the face of goal.
<br  /><br  />
After the game, the Academy Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on the game:
<br  /><br  />
“I didn’t think there were many clear-cut chances for Wimbledon today, and that shows we did well defensively, but we just weren’t creating enough going the other way, perhaps we didn’t have enough power, which is fine as we rested several second years and involved
<br  />
U16s again. ” explained Hyde.
<br  /><br  />
“Quality-wise, I thought we could have done better at times, but they did very well today.
<br  />
I saw areas in which we were good, areas I felt there could be room for improvement and that was primarily what today was about for me, watching the players that are showing development and the potential of others,” continued the coach.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line-up</strong><br  />
Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: 19. Louie Chapman, 2. Charlie Holmes, 3. Deniz Alici, 4. Paul
<br  />
Symes, 5. Jack Lee, 15. David Agboola, 7. Harvey Brown, 8. Elliot Bonds, 9. Dylan
<br  />
Florence, 10. Blue Gallagher, 11. Tyrique Hyde 12. Didi Ndombe, 14. Mekhi Hyde, 16. Luke
<br  />
Hirst, 1. Joe Carter
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-13 11:00:29 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>