<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3622764-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-sign-forward-from-eastbourne-borough-3622764.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Sign Forward from Eastbourne Borough</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Sign Forward from Eastbourne Borough</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Sign Forward from Eastbourne Borough</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are delighted to announce the signing of Elliot Romain from Eastbourne Borough</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Football Club have moved fast to fend off rival bids and sign striker Elliott Romain from National South Eastbourne Borough for an undisclosed fee.
<br  /><br  />
The National League South’s third top scorer has already notched 20 league goals this season as well as two more last Tuesday as Eastbourne were beaten by the odd goal in seven by Brighton Under 23’s in the Sussex Senior semi-final.
<br  /><br  />
A quick and direct frontman with the ability to be in the right place at the right time, Romain played youth football at both Brighton &amp; Hove Albion and Millwall but broke into senior football with Three Bridges where he was their main goal threat for four seasons.
<br  /><br  />
He finished the 2013/14 season with 16 goals for the Crawley-based club and joined Ryman League Premier Division side Lewes in July 2014. He also spent time on loan with Horsham YMCA during the 2014/5 season.
<br  /><br  />
He joined Eastbourne Borough in July 2015 and has spent two seasons with The Sports where he has played alongside former Dagger Jamie Taylor.
<br  /><br  />
Elliot Romain will wear squad number 9 and be available for squad selection on Saturday for our away fixture against Barrow AFC.
<br  /><br  />
We spoke to Manger John Still about the signing of Elliot Romain ahead of Dagenham and Redbridge’s away fixture against Barrow this weekend:
<br  /><br  />
“We highlighted Elliot earlier on this season as he’s been watched by our scouts. We’ve always been trying to find the right time for us and the right time for Eastbourne Borough because they wanted to hold onto the forward, fortunately they got to a stage that they thought it was the right time to let him go and we are absolutely delighted to bring him in.” 
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//romain86292-3625066_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//romain169292-3625067_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-14 15:00:58 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team,Transfer</Tags>
</News>