<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3623196-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-doe-post-forest-green-rovers-3623196.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Doe Post Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Doe Post Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Doe Post Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to captain Scott Doe after Saturday's 2-1 win over promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers where the defender got the winning goal</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After a drop in form in recent weeks the Daggers returned to winning ways on the weekend after a dominant performance over promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I would say the team was back to their best today, it was a good performance both first and second half against a good side, which I felt we made look average through our performance. With our first half chances I think that is what shows our performance better as in the past we have sometimes felt sorry for ourselves and dropped our heads and conceded a goal but today we pushed on and got the win.”
<br /></em><br  />
Doe believes that winning this game today is crucial to bringing confidence back into the squad as John Still’s men go into their final ten games of the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I would say it was one of the most important goals I have scored for the club, all credit to Christian Doidge scoring a great header, but I was well overdue a goal so to get it at home to Forest Green is massive. Saturday’s result will bring so much confidence into the team, we had won five in a row to start the year then dropped form in recent weeks but we always bounce back from defeats, to bounce back at home where our form has been less impressive and to get the win against the team who was above us in the league will bring a lot of confidence into the side.” </em>  
<br  /><br  />
Before Saturday’s game John Still signed a two year contract extension with the Club, Scott was delighted with the decision for the manager to extend his contract and continue building the current squad.
<br  /><br  /><em >“John Still had a major part in me returning to the club and me coming here in the first place. The two extra years he will be able to carry on the great work he has been doing while at the Club, bringing in young, hungry players from Non-League clubs and achieving greatness from those players like we have seen this season. John staying means he can build on what he has created this season by developing these players and hopefully taking them into the Football League.”</em><br  /><br  /><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><strong><br />
Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//doey86292-3623263_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//doey169292-3623264_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-13 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>