<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3623859-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/loan-update-13th-march-2017-3623859.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Loan Update 13th March 2017</headline>
  <page_title>Loan Update 13th March 2017</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Loan Update 13th March 2017</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Scott Heard and Joe White have both extended their deals at their loan clubs while Shomari Barnwell has joined Hastings United on loan until the end of the season</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<strong >Joe White (Wealdstone FC)</strong><br  />
Wealdstone have extended Joe White’s loan at the club for another month after the forward put in several good performances over his month stay with the National League South side. The young forward bagged himself a goal in Saturday’s 2-1 win when the Stones faced Truro. We spoke to manager John Still about White’s spell at Wealdstone:
<br  /><br  />
“Joe has done very well at Wealdstone, we like him a lot and I think him playing games at the level he is currently playing at rather than youth team level is helping him progress, although we are not apposed now because this is his second month we can bring back at any time we want. If we do feel need him back in the squad we will bring him back as I said we do really like him and I think he is a player we will be working with a lot next year, if not then between now and then end of the season we will see.”
<br  /><br  /><strong >Scott Heard (East Thurrock United)</strong><br  />
East Thurrock United have also extended Scott Heard’s loan for another month, Scott is another player who has impressed while at his loan club, helping the Essex side to a comfortable 4-0 win over Bishop’s Stortford on the weekend. John has been very impressed with the young midfielder at his time at the National League South side:
<br  /><br  />
“Heard has done very well at Thurrock, when part time players come into the side it is difficult sometimes which I felt that Heard struggled with it slightly but he has now pushed on enough that we want to give him some games. With Scott again if we needed to bring him back we can because he is now into his second loan spell.”
<br  /><br  /><strong >Shomari Barnwell (Hastings United)</strong><br  />
After completing a loan spell at Bishop’s Stortford the young forward Shomari Barnwell will now be heading out to Ryman South side Hastings United who have loaned Shomari for the remainder of the season. Hastings United currently sit in sixth position in the Ryman South Division.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//loanupdate-86292-3490074_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//loanupdate-169292-3490075_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-13 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword>Loan Watch</userdefined_keyword>
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home</Tags>
</News>