<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3624803-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-post-forest-green-rovers-3624803.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Post Forest Green Rovers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Post Forest Green Rovers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Post Forest Green Rovers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We caught up with Assistant Manager Darren Currie after the 2-1 win over promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers to discuss the team performance</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Before Saturday’s game Manager John Still signed a two year contract extension with the Club, Darren was delighted with John’s commitment to the Club and was glad the team could complete the day with a crucial three points against promotion rivals Forest Green Rovers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Saturday was a very good day it is very pleasing to see that John has committed himself for another 2 years and we backed it up with a performance which was a proper Dagenham performance. After signing a few players this season you can start to tell the Club is going in the right direction, we all know the relationship John has with this Club so it is great for everyone here at the club.”</em><br  /><br  />
Prior to Saturday’s game the Daggers had lost their last three out of four games, with ten games left Darren believes that they will need to keep up the standard of football the team displayed on Saturday to keep up their promotion battle. 
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have had a dip in form in recent weeks but we knew we was going to come out the back of this dip and start climbing again which we have done today, we have worked incredibly hard today putting bodies on the line. All credit to Josh Staunton today throwing himself in front of everything to protect his goal and that is what is required now, we have ten huge games left and we need to play to the levels we were playing at on Saturday.”    </em><br  /><br  /><em >“We did have a couple of chances, hit the bar and we did feel like is it going to be one of those days where we have seen in recent weeks where we do not take the chances gifted to us. We kept going we was very positive at half time you could sense the positivity in the way the boys were playing and we asked the players to go back out there and keep doing what they showed in the first half.” </em><br  /><br  />
After suffering from an injury earlier in the season Okenabirhie has been returning to form with each game he plays in, after signing from Harrow Borough in the summer the young forward has impressed the management staff while featuring in the first team. 
<br  /><br  /><em >“Okenabirhie has been brilliant all season, he has had a slight dip due to his injury earlier in the season but you have to remember where these young boys come from and for them to come in and play consistent good levels of football week in week out is nothing shy of impressive. Fejiri was back to his sharp electric self today and it was a great bit of skill to beat his marker and get the ball in, to assist Maguire-Drew to get the goal.”</em><br  /><strong ><br />
Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br  /><div ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>
 
<br  /><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrietorquay-86292-3444707_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrietorquay-169292-3444708_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-14 12:30:44 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>