<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3625294-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-barrow-afc-3625294.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Barrow AFC </headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Barrow AFC </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Barrow AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Daggers' Vanarama National League away fixture at Barrow AFC on Saturday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Barrow’s stadium since 1909, Holker Street – or the Furness Building Society Stadium as it is known for sponsorship reasons – has a capacity of 4,414 and is the seventh smallest ground in the National League. The stadium in its current guise is comprised predominantly of terracing, the only exception being the 1,000 seater main stand which was redeveloped during the mid-1990s. The stadium retains the charm of a traditional non-league ground, with only one third of the remaining terracing under cover from the elements. The terracing is made up of the uncovered Holker Street End and Crossbar End behind the goals and the partially covered Ray Wilkie Popular Stand which runs part-way alongside the pitch.
<br  /><br  /><strong >DAGGERS FANS:</strong><br  />
Barrow tend to implement segregation at home fixtures, meaning Daggers fans will be housed on one side of the Holker Street terrace. The stand, which is shared with home supporters who are separated by a scaffold structure, is completely uncovered and as such is open to the elements. Away supporters are also offered a limited number of seats in the main stand which is located centrally alongside the pitch. This stand is restricted by three pillars, but does offer protection from the elements.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
Holker Street has a small sized clubhouse called, ‘The Crossbar’, which admits away supporters on matchday and also shows Sky TV for the early kick-off. There is also a pub located adjacent to the stadium called the Soccer Bar, which is independent from the club and also allows in away fans. Otherwise, head along Walney Road and turn left into Duke Street where you will find the Ambrose Hotel which serves a selection of real ale. If you continue along Walney Road, however, you will find a McDonalds, KFC and a further pub, ‘The Owl and the Pussycat.’ The town centre also has a selection of public houses, including ‘The Furness Railway’, which is a JD Wetherspoons outlet listed in the CAMRA Good Beer Guide.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-barrow-afc-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3612861.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />
An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-barrow-afc-3624791.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-16 13:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>