<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3627321-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/daggers-sign-forward-mason-bloomfield-3627321.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Daggers Sign Forward Mason Bloomfield</headline>
  <page_title>Daggers Sign Forward Mason Bloomfield</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Daggers Sign Forward Mason Bloomfield</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We are delighted to announce the signing of forward Mason Bloomfield from Aveley FC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Mason came through the Daggers youth system on a two-year scholarship in 2013 after leaving the Ase Academy.
<br  /><br  />
The forward made his Football League debut for Dagenham and Redbridge when he replaced Matt Partridge in the League Two fixture against Northampton Town in September 2014 after playing a youth match that same morning.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Loan spells at Isthmian League Division One North Side Chatham Town, where he made five appearances, and Southern Counties East side Erith &amp; Belvedere, scoring in his match for the side Maldon &amp; Tiptree, racking up 18 appearances and 5 goals.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Last season the forward signed for Chelmsford City, also featuring in Isthmian Premier Division sides Billericay Town and Grays Athletic. He joined Aveley in December of last year and has featured in several behind closed door friendlies this year for the Daggers impressing John Still and the rest of the Daggers management team, The Daggers are currently in review of loaning Bloomfield back out to Ryman North side till the end of the season.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers manager John Still gave his thoughts on signing the young forward:   
<br  />
 
<br  />
“Mason has been playing locally at Aveley FC and got recommended to us by Aveley’s manager, initially I didn’t know him but he is known by the Club because he was here as a youth. So we’ve been watching him and brought him in and he has done ever so well, he also played in a first team match when he was 16 years old although I think he picked up an injury while he was at the club and the Club didn’t hold onto him.”
<br  />
 
<br  />
“The person who recommended him to the Club was actually the person who told us about Dwight Gayle and we brought Dwight in the same way as Mason. We won’t be involving him right now, we will be loaning him back out to Aveley, but we will look to him as one for the future.”
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//bloomfield86292-3628833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//bloomfield169292-3628834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-16 10:00:38 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Signing,Team,Transfer</Tags>
</News>