<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3630535-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-guide-aldershot-town-3630535.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Guide: Aldershot Town</headline>
  <page_title>Away Guide: Aldershot Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Guide: Aldershot Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>An away guide for the Daggers' Vanarama National League away fixture at Aldershot Town on Tuesday</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Aldershot Town have the seventh largest ground in the Vanarama National League this season with an overall capacity of 7,100. On one side is the North Stand. This was built by the supporters club in 1932, in preparation for the old Aldershot FC joining the league. It was built on top of some much older stone terracing, and is raised slightly above pitch level where the stone base of the terracing can still be seen. It originally had bench seating only in the front, central sections, but this was replaced with individual seats when new dressing rooms and offices and the Directors box were added in 1980.
<br  /><br  />
Further seating was also added in 2008 on Aldershot town’s promotion to the League to bring the total seats in the ground close to 2,000. However both ends and a small section behind the seats are still standing. At one end is the East Bank covered terrace. This stand has a classic looking barrel shaped roof and has a number of supporting pillars running across the front of it. Opposite is the High Street End. Called the Community Stand it comprises just four rows of seats and only runs from the corner flag to the goal area. It has a total seating capacity of 250. On the other side of this end is a two storey green portakabin that serves as a Police Control Box, otherwise this end is unused for spectators. The ground benefits from an impressive set of floodlights.
<br  /><br  /><strong >DAGGERS FANS:</strong><br  />
Away fans are housed in the South East corner of the ground. This comprises 212 covered seated places which are available in the South Stand and space for a further 1,320 standing supporters in the East Bank Terrace and a portion of open terrace extending around to the South Stand. The East Bank is shared with home supporters and there are a number of supporting pillars, which could obstruct your view. Although the East Bank is showing its age, at least it does allow a good atmosphere to be created and it does have that interesting barrel shaped roof.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Please note that</strong> All AWAY Supporters will enter the ground from the High Street end and access the stands through turnstile 4. Disabled /Carer tickets should be booked in advance via the Aldershot Town ticket office but if they arrive on the day those people need to purchase their ticket from the ticket office. Aldershot have limited wheelchair spaces in the Away section and away supporters are advised to reserve them prior to the game.
<br  /><br  /><strong >FOOD &amp; DRINK:</strong><br  />
Refreshments are provided via a mobile catering unit, selling the usual fayre of Cheeseburgers (£4), Jumbo Hot Dogs (£3.50) and Chips (£2).
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-aldershot-town-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3612903.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  /><br  />
An away travel guide for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-aldershot-town-3630515.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-86292-3225841_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awayguide16-17-169292-3225843_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-19 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>