<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3630101-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-elliot-romain-on-signing-for-the-daggers-3630101.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Elliot Romain on Signing For The Daggers</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Elliot Romain on Signing For The Daggers</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Elliot Romain on Signing For The Daggers</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers Player caught up with new signing Elliot Romain to get his thoughts on signing for the Club</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Earlier this week the Daggers signed striker Elliot Romain from National League South side Eastbourne Borough, Elliot was delighted to make the change to the Essex side and looks forward to help the Daggers push for promotion back into the Football League.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I’ve always heard good things about this Club, the team is doing very well in the league currently and I would like to come in and hopefully help push for promotion. John has a lot of experience in bringing in players and progressing them onto bigger Clubs with the likes of Dwight Gayle and I would like to push on eventually if I am good enough.”</em><br  /><br  />
With Elliot coming up against forwards such as Hawkins and Benson for competition for the striker position, Romain believes the competition will help him play to his full ability on the pitch.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I know the position I play in currently has competition with the likes of Hawkins and Benson but I look forward to it, competition is good at any level I wouldn’t want to be at a Club where I’m not fighting for my place; I’m ready to get out there and earn my place. I’ve come into a really strong team with a good chance of getting promoted, I want to assist the team in any way I can and hopefully get some goals for the Club.”</em><br  /><br  />
Elliot is more than confident coming into the team that the switch from part time to full time training will not affect him and will only improve his fitness.
<br  /><br  /><em >“At Eastbourne I was training part time and it will be very different training full time but I am ready for the challenge as I think my fitness is very good generally anyway and with full time training it can only improve. Signing for Dagenham this week has been a whirlwind of a journey, I’ve had to hand my notice in at work and the support from both sets of fans has been wonderful in wishing me luck in my new chapter.”</em><br  /><strong ><br />
Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br  /><div ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//romaininterview86292-3630088_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//romaininterview169292-3630089_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-16 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Signing,Team</Tags>
</News>