<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3630515-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/away-travel-guide-aldershot-town-3630515.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Away Travel Guide: Aldershot Town</headline>
  <page_title>Away Travel Guide: Aldershot Town</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Away Travel Guide: Aldershot Town</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Thinking of travelling to the Aldershot Recreation Ground for the Daggers’ fixture against Aldershot Town, below is all the information you need to get there by car, train or coach</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<strong >DIRECTIONS BY CAR:</strong><br  />
Leave the M3 at Junction 4 and take the A331 towards Farnborough/Aldershot. Continue towards Aldershot passing the North Camp turn off. At the next junction (Aldershot South) turn right at the roundabout towards Aldershot Town Centre (A323). Keep straight on this road and after going under a railway bridge, the ground is visible on your right. There is little parking available at the ground itself. But if using the directions above then if you pass the ground on your right and then turn right at the next roundabout there is a small pay and display car park immediately on your right, which costs £2 for four hours.
<br  /><br  /><strong >BY TRAIN:</strong><br  />
Get a train to Victoria Station (50 minutes from Dagenham East Station) and from here get the Southern Line to Clapham Junction which is a six minute journey. From Clapham Junction get the South West Trains service to Aldershot Railway Station which takes 50 minutes. Aldershot Railway Station is less than a ten minute walk away from the ground. Upon leaving the train station, go down the station approach and turn right into Windsor Way. Continue down Windsor Way passing the Holy Trinity Church on your left. The road bends to the left and leads into Victoria Road. Turn right along Victoria Road and at the bottom of the road you will see floodlights of the Recreation Ground in front of you.
<br  /><br  /><strong >SUPPORTERS COACH:</strong><br  />
The Dagenham &amp; Redbridge Supporters’ Club will be running a coach to this fixture at a price of £10 for members and £25 for non-members. The coach will depart Victoria Road at 4:15pm, if you are planning to take the coach to this fixture, please call Russell Elmes on the DRFC Travel Hotline using 07989901686.
<br  /><br  />
Ticket information for the game can be found <a href="http://www.daggers.co.uk/news/article/2016-17/tickets-aldershot-town-v-dagenham-and-redbridge-3612903.aspx" >here</a>.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-86292-3319433_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//awaytravelguide16-17-169292-3319434_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-17 10:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>