<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3630780-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-john-still-ahead-of-barrow-afc-3630780.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Barrow AFC</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Barrow AFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: John Still Ahead Of Barrow AFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to manager John Still ahead of Saturday's trip to Barrow AFC and got his thoughts on the two new signings the Daggers made this week</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After two defeats on the bounce John Still was delighted to get a win against Forest Green Rovers last weekend and complements the squad for continuing to bounce back after disappointing results.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Our spirit never goes down in the squad we always get back into training and go again, I think that having a group of players that are not the most experienced, they can get other things quite quickly. We had a couple of disappointing results, but we played well on Saturday and our form wasn’t great before that result but that is football and wherever you are bad results will happen</em>.”
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers have a brilliant record against the teams in the top four of the league although the club have dropped points against some of the teams that have been struggling, but manager John Still doesn’t want to dwell on previous results.
<br  /><br  /><em >“If you are successful in the league you have got to win most of your games and I think there is only one team who has won more games than us this season which is incredible and credit to the group of players that we have. I don’t dwell on any results in games that maybe we should have won as you can play teams on good days and bad days for us and teams that you are playing you can come up against on a good day for them.”</em><br  /><br  />
John Still signed a new two year contract with the club before the game on Saturday and the manager has explained his thoughts behind signing a new deal with the Daggers.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I think that up until around Christmas time there was a little bit of uncertainty at the club where there was a potential new owner in Glenn Tamplin which did not work out and now Glyn Hopkin has stepped in for the club. Now that has been sorted there has been a bit more stability at the club I was in a position where I could see where the club was, and I have been responsible for a number of changes in players in the last year.  When the club spoke to me about the future, as when I signed here again I said that this year could be my last year, that because of the stability at the club and the players that have come in and signed new contracts I thought that it was the right thing to do for the club. Through the talks that we had I like to think that we had found a foundation to build on and over the next two years this club will be fully stabilised and that whatever league the club is in it will be ready for the challenge that is needed.”</em><br  /><br  />
The Daggers announced two new signings this week in Elliot Romain and Mason Bloomfield and John Still is excited about what both players can bring to the Daggers while at the club. 
<br  /><br  /><em >“We have been watching Romain for a while and we have brought him in for the last stage of this season but also for next season as we were very excited when we had seen him play. There was a few of us who had watched him with me, Darren Currie, Terry Harris and our chief scout and we had been watching him over a long period so we thought now was the right time for us to push for something and thankfully we managed to get him. He is a young player that is very ambitious and is hard working which we feel will be a very good addition to the squad. Mason Bloomfield was another player that was brought to our attention and the person who told us about him was the same person who had told us about Dwight Gayle. I didn’t know that Bloomfield was here previously until we were in talks with the player but we have signed him on a contract and loaned him back to his club Aveley FC and we see him as one for the future.”</em><br  /><br  />
The Daggers have a long trip to Barrow on Saturday and John Still has told the players to carry on with the form from last weekend’s win over Forest Green Rovers.
<br  /><br  /><em >"My message to the players is that if you keep working hard and you are good players the bad form is temporary and you will come out of that. If you are generally good players and we have to have good players to be in the position that we are in, the form will come back with us working hard in training and making sure that you are unaffected by what has gone as you can’t change the past you can only make sure that you play well in future games. Our next game on Saturday is a long trip to Barrow and the players are in good spirits after last Saturday’s win so we need to keep that going now so that we can finish the season strongly."</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br  /><div ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//jstillmaidstone-86292-3601635_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//jstillmaidstone-169292-3601637_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-17 14:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>