<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3636583-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/welcome-our-new-commercial-manager-lauren-webster-3636583.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Welcome Our New Commercial Manager Lauren Webster</headline>
  <page_title>Welcome Our New Commercial Manager Lauren Webster</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Welcome Our New Commercial Manager Lauren Webster</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers are delighted to announce our new Commercial Manager Lauren Webster</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Dagenham &amp; Redbridge are pleased to announce the appointment of a new Commercial and Business Development Manager.
<br  /><br  />
Lauren Webster joins the Club after recently leaving her role as Commercial Manager at National League South Side Dartford FC. With an impressive background in the football industry working for a number of clubs including Notts County, Preston North End and Leeds United; Lauren has over 10 years’ experience of working within the football industry in a commercial and sales capacity. 
<br  /><br  />
We caught up with Lauren on her first day to get her thoughts on the new job role:
<br  />
"I am excited for the challenge here at Dagenham &amp; Redbridge. I think my knowledge of the football industry will help to further develop and build on the clubs commercial activity both on and off the field. It’s a great time to join and I look forward to being a part of taking The Daggers to the next level."
<br  /><br  />
Managing Director Steve Thompson said:
<br  />
"After losing our previous commercial manager Sean Joyce to the Football Association at the same time as getting relegated from the Football League the club needed to retrench. Now with the opportunities afforded the Club with the investment that the Consortium led by Glyn Hopkin have presented we quickly moved to appoint a new full time commercial manager.
<br  /><br  />
Lauren joins us with a wealth of experience at a number of League Clubs and most recently as a commercial Manager at Dartford Football Club, she is full of enthusiasm and excited by the challenge ahead. I’m sure she will be a great success with the Daggers."
<br  /><br  />
For any future commercial enquiries, please contact Lauren on 020 8592 1549 ext 33 or alternatively by email on <a href="mailto:%20commercial@daggers.co.uk" >commercial@daggers.co.uk</a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//laurenwebster86292-3637138_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//laurenwebster169292-3637139_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-21 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,League</Tags>
</News>