<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3636587-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/ladies-match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-7-0-waltham-forest-lfc-3636587.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Ladies Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 7 - 0 Waltham Forest LFC</headline>
  <page_title>Ladies Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 7 - 0 Waltham Forest LFC</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Ladies Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 7 - 0 Waltham Forest LFC</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham and Redbridge Ladies FC start their journey with dominant win against Waltham Forest LFC</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[A 7-0 victory against Waltham Forest Ladies FC saw Dagenham and Redbridge Ladies convincingly win their first game since being formed. It took the newly formed side 18 minutes to get the ball rolling and the goals scoring with Fran Pride being the first lady to score at Chigwell Construction Stadium, home of the Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
Dagenham began to create more and more chances in front of goal but were denied by the Waltham Forest keeper. Waltham Forest began to step up a gear and putting pressure on goalkeeper Jodie Sanderson but they were unable to find the target.
<br  />
 
<br  />
Lauren Beard became the second on the score sheet with a confident finish after a precise pass found her in space inside the box on 33 minutes. With confidence growing it then took the ladies just over ten minutes to fire five past the keeper with goals from Morgan Duffield, Hannah Humphreys and two from Lauren Beard to complete her hat-trick moments before half time putting the ladies 6-0 up.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The second half saw the Daggers continue to dominate the game which forced Waltham Forest to go to five at the back.
<br  /><br  />
After numerous waves of attack Lauren Beard got her fourth of the game and completed the score line to make it 7 – 0 to the Daggers after a well-placed shot on the edge of the area curled into the bottom corner past the Waltham Forest keeper.
<br  /><br  />
The last 15 minutes of the game saw Waltham Forest continue to defend well which saw Hannah Humphreys, Gracie Robinson, Daisy Cook and Briony Hagger all being denied goals with frantic defending from the away side.
<br  />
 
<br  />
The final whistle from the referee the saw Daggers Ladies claim a 7-0 in their first competitive fixture. 
<br  /><br  />
Confidence will be high going into their next fixture which will see the return of five additional first team players who were unavailable for Sunday’s match.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//ladiesmatchreport86292-3636585_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//ladiesmatchreport169292-3636586_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-20 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,Home,Ladies,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>