<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3636251-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/loan-update-21st-march-2017-3636251.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Loan Update 21st March 2017</headline>
  <page_title>Loan Update 21st March 2017</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Loan Update 21st March 2017</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Loan Update on Daggers loan players Hyde, White, Heard, Barnwell and Bloomfield</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Tyrique Hyde made his debut for Ware FC on Saturday in their Vanarama National League North game away to Norwich United, where the midfielder played the full 90 minutes as The Blues lost 2-1.
<br  /><br  />
Joe White started and played for 84 minutes for Wealdstone FC grabbing an equaliser from the penalty spot as The Stones drew 1-1 at home to Chelmsford City in the Vanarama National League South.
<br  /><br  />
Midfielder Scott Heard played the full 90 minutes and also got himself a goal as East Thurrock United defeated Oxford City 2-1 at home in the Vanarama National League South.
<br  /><br  />
Forward Shomari Barnwell made his debut for Hastings United on Saturday with the side winning 1-0 away to Corinthian-Casuals, where the striker played the full 90 minutes for the Isthmian League Division One South side.
<br  /><br  />
Mason Bloomfield who signed for the Daggers last week and returned on loan to Aveley FC got another goal for his side on Saturday as Aveley drew 2-2 away to Dereham Town in the Isthmian North Division.
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//loanupdate-86292-3490074_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//loanupdate-169292-3490075_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-21 09:30:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword>Loan Watch</userdefined_keyword>
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Team</Tags>
</News>