<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3637836-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-aldershot-town-3-1-dagenham-and-redbridge-3637836.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Aldershot Town 3 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Aldershot Town 3 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Aldershot Town 3 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>The Daggers suffer another defeat away, after Aldershot Town maintain their home form with a 3-1 victory.</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >John Still made just one change to his side that lost away to Barrow, Andre Boucaud was replaced by Frankie Raymond, due to international duty with Trinidad &amp; Tobago.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It was a tough opening 10 minutes for the Daggers after a number of chances came for the Shots. Idris Kanu headed just wide after he was found unmarked in the box.</div><div ><br /></div><div >It looked like the hosts had took the lead in the sixth minute after the ball fell on to the path of Rendell, but it was ruled offside.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Right on the tenth minute mark, Cheye Alexander curled a shot from the right hand side, but the ball ended up going past Elliot Justham's far post.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The goal eventually came for the hosts, 17 minutes into the game, as Donnellan turned a cross from Mensah into his own net.</div><div ><br /></div><div >38 minutes into the game saw the Shots double their lead, after a low cross from Arnold was tapped in at the far post by Mensah.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers came close to bringing one back, with three minutes left on the clock, as captain Scott Doe headed on to the side netting a Corey Whitely Corner.</div><div ><br /></div><div >John Still opted to make one change at half-time, Jordan Maguire-Drew was replaced by new signing Elliott Romain.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers then won a free kick in a dangerous area only one minute into the second-half, after Romain was pulled down, Frankie Raymond then forced Shots keeper Cole to save the low shot.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Ten minutes later saw another free kick being conceded in the exact same position, which ended up in a Daggers corner.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The corner resulted in the Daggers bringing a goal back in the 56th minute, a shot from Fejire Okenabirhie ended up being headed into the back of the net by Doe.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers made a double substitution in the 70th minute, Luke Howell and Paul Benson replaced Fejiri Okenabirhie and Oliver Hawkins.</div><div ><br /></div><div >83 minutes into the game and former Daggers player Matt McClure scored from the edge of the box and finding the bottom right of Justham’s goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Three minutes later saw Arnold shoot directly from a free kick just outside the box, forcing Justham to produce a brilliant save.</div><div ><br /></div><div >After a third consecutive defeat away from home the Daggers will play next at home on Saturday 25th March against York City.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Daggers: Justham, Widdowson, Robson, Doe, Raymond, Maguire-Drew (46’ Romain), Okenabihrie (70’ Howell), Hawkins (70’ Benson), Whitely, Donnellan, Sheppard</div><div ><br /></div><div >Unused subs: Cousins, Staunton</div><div ><br /></div><div >Aldershot: Cole, Arnold, Evans, Fenelon, Rendell, Mensah (71’ McClure), Alexander (78’ Straker), Gallagher, Kanu (85’ Giles), Benyu, Reynolds (C)</div><div ><br /></div><div >Unused subs: Buckley, Smith</div><div ><br /></div><div >Attendance: 2,113 (109 Daggers)</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-21 22:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>