<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3638707-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-craig-robson-post-aldershot-town-3638707.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Craig Robson Post Aldershot Town </headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Craig Robson Post Aldershot Town </page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Craig Robson Post Aldershot Town </URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to defender Craig Robson after Tuesday's disappointing 3-1 away defeat to Aldershot Town</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Tuesday evening saw the Daggers lose out on another crucial game to cement their place in the promotion battle, in a first half which was heavily dominated by the Shots left the Daggers trailing two goals behind heading into the break. The Daggers came out into the second half with an ascendancy and finding a way back into the game after a header from Scott Doe to lower the deficit to one, only to concede another goal in the 83rd minute from former Dagger Matt McClure.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Tuesday’s result was very disappointing we was poor in the first half there’s no excuses for how we played, it was probably the worst I have seen us play all year; no one had any spirit or bite about them. In the second half we did change the shape of the team ever so slightly which helped us going forward but again it wasn’t good enough to get us the win.”</em><br  /><br  />
The Daggers have now lost their past four out of five games, Robson believes that the Daggers need to make it count before it’s too late heading into the final eight games of the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“To be honest if we keep playing the way we are playing we won’t make the play offs, so we have really got to look at ourselves at the moment and take each game as it comes and make it count if we do want to be promoted this season.”</em><br  /><br  />
Next up for the Daggers is there game against York City on Saturday here at the Chigwell Construction Stadium after the recent performances over league leaders Lincoln City in the FA Trophy and coming from 3-1 behind to miraculously beating Southport on Tuesday, The Minstermen will be going into Saturday’s game looking to carry on their push to stay up this season and looking to avoid a double relegation.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Every game from now to the end of the season will be crucial, we are up against York on the weekend and they are fighting to stay in this league so it will no doubt be a difficult game we will have to go into the game and give 100% and winning will hopefully get us back on track going into the last 8 games of the season.”</em><br  /><br  />
Due to the Daggers lack of selection choices for the centre midfield spot after countless injuries to the likes of Luke Guttridge and Matt Robinson, Robson has had to fill in at the middle of the park, although Craig is happy to fill at any position required from the Manager for the benefit of the team.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I will play wherever the manager wants me to play, I’m just happy to do my job for the team and just try and win games.” 
<br /></em><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//robson86292-3638718_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//robson169292-3638719_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-22 14:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>