<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3640169-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-luke-howell-york-city-preview-3640169.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Luke Howell York City Preview</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Luke Howell York City Preview</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Luke Howell York City Preview</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to midfielder Luke Howell ahead of Saturday's home game against York City and got his thoughts on the disappointing defeat to Aldershot where he made his comeback from injury</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Luke Howell has suffered three injuries this season that has made his miss a large majority of the campaign but the midfielder is looking forward to having a part to play in the last eight games of the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Early on in the season I tore my cartilage in my right knee after returning from that injury I then done the exactly the same injury but to my left knee so it wasn’t the reoccurrence of the same knee it was just unfortunate I done it in my second knee. Four or five weeks ago I tore my thigh in training which is frustrating but I am back in training and now it’s just about getting back to match fitness now.”
<br /></em><br  /><em >“It has been tough picking up these injuries I’m not going to lie, I want to be playing football but there is nothing I can do about it really it has just been one of those seasons and they say bad things come in threes so hopefully that’s me done. When I came back from my second injury I’d had a lot of reserve games under my belt and I felt like I was in position I wanted to be at so the final injury was especially frustrating as it felt I had a good three or four months left of the season in me. I’m back now and we have some big games coming up so I just want to help out and give it my all.”</em><br  /><br  />
Howell was surprised at the first half performance against Aldershot on Tuesday and thinks that the performance wasn’t at the standard that the Daggers have set themselves this season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Tuesday’s game was very surprising for me the first half was hard to watch from the bench, the performance wasn’t acceptable. Aldershot was very dominant and we didn’t seem to show what we have proved to have and seen all season. We will be looking to put that right on Saturday for our home game against York and make up it up to the fans and the Club after Tuesday’s performance.”
<br /></em><br  />
The Daggers have suffered with numerous midfield injuries this season and Luke Howell believes that it has affected the team’s performances.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Boucaud hasn’t had an injury but he is a very good player and when he goes away on international duty we miss him. Matt Robinson was flying at the start of the season doing really well and then unfortunately he got injured, I have been injured for most of the season and Guttridge has been in and out of the team. It has been tough with all the injuries in midfield this season but we have had injuries across all positions, and the players that have had to play week in week out have suffered because of the injuries as we haven’t been able to rotate the team. So it has been hard on them and frustrating for the lads who have been injured but luckily we are getting back to a full squad now and Boucaud will be back with us next week.”</em><br  /><br  />
York City got relegated with the Daggers last season and they have struggled this year and find themselves in the relegation zone, but Howell is expecting a tough game with York City as The Minsterman are currently fighting for their lives.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Saturday will be a really tough game, they are scrapping for their lives and have had a bit of indifferent season and have changed manager so it has been hard on them. They are in form at the moment beating Lincoln in the FA Trophy over two legs so that’s impressive and they won again on Tuesday. We know that they are going to be physical and fighting for every ball so we know that we have to match that and then hopefully our quality will show for us.”</em><br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br  /><div ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//howell86292-3640181_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//howell169292-3640182_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-23 16:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>