<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3642221-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/match-report-dagenham-and-redbridge-1-0-york-city-3642221.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 York City</headline>
  <page_title>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 York City</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Match Report: Dagenham and Redbridge 1 - 0 York City</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Dagenham &amp; Redbridge left it late to record a vital 1-0 win at home to York City in the National League</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[Daggers made six changes for the clash, with Curtley Williams, Josh Staunton, Luke Guttridge, Luke Howell, Elliott Romain and Paul Benson coming in to the starting XI.
<br  /><br  />
There was also a start for skipper Scott Doe, who was making his 300th appearance for Daggers.
<br  /><br  />
In the seventh minute, Benson had a header saved following a good ball into the box from full-back Joe Widdowson.
<br  /><br  />
Two minutes later, Benson saw a header cleared off the line following a corner from Guttridge.
<br  /><br  />
York, though, created several chances themselves with Jon Parkin, Adriano Moke and Amari Morgan-Smith all going close in a first half which ended goalless.
<br  /><br  />
Corey Whitely missed a good chance for Daggers in the 58th minute, unable to get a clean connection on the ball after a great cross from Romain.
<br  /><br  />
In the 72nd minute, Romain was unable to head home his first goal for the club after a superb cross from Williams.
<br  /><br  />
At the other end seven minutes later, Elliot Justham was tested by a venoumous half-volley from Asa Hall.
<br  /><br  />
With seven minutes remaining, Daggers took the lead with a great, curled effort from the edge of the area by substitute Frankie Raymond.
<br  /><br  />
It proved to be the game’s only goal as Daggers returned to winning ways in front of their home fans.
<br  /><br  /><strong >Attendance:</strong> 1659 of which 109 were away
<br  /><br  /><strong >Line Ups:</strong><br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers:</strong> Justham, Widdowson, Doe (c), Robson, Howell, Romain, Guttridge (78' Raymond) , Whitely, Staunton, Benson, Williams
<br  /><br  /><strong >Daggers Unused Subs:</strong> Cousins, Maguire Drew, Robinson, Ling
<br  /><br  /><strong >York City:</strong> Loach, Whittle, Heslop (c), Morgan-Smith (78' Muggleton), Hall (87' Connolly), Oliver, Parkin, Newton, Moke (87' Fenwick), Parslow, Bencherif
<br  /><br  /><strong >York City Unused Subs:</strong> Rooney, Holmes
<br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-25 18:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>