<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3644872-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/academy-match-report-mk-dons-2-1-dagenham-and-redbridge-3644872.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Academy Match Report: MK Dons 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Academy Match Report: MK Dons 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Academy Match Report: MK Dons 2 - 1 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Delightful Daggers Dealt Bitter Dons Defeat</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >A second-half comeback from the MK Dons academy snatched victory away from the Dagenham &amp; Redbridge U18s despite a sensational display from Micah Hyde’s youngsters.</div><div ><br /></div><div >A young Daggers side, up against a physically mature and seasoned MK Dons line up, dominated possession and were in full control throughout, demonstrating good resilience and creativity in an encounter that saw the opposition struggle to match the hosts’ work rate and endeavor.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Having been on top for the opening ten minutes, the Daggers capped their early dominance with a goal courtesy of a James Turvey's close-range finish.</div><div > </div><div >After the break, the visitors equalised from a quick break following a broken-down Daggers attack.</div><div > </div><div >It took a moment of individual quality to turn things around for the Dons as the away number nine, scorer of their first, registered his brace from his own half to fire the Buckinghamshire into a second-half lead.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Further strikes from Jordy Mongoy and Michael Agboola could have earned the Daggers a point at bare minimum for their efforts, but both were denied, the former by an alert Dons stopper, the latter by the frame of the goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The result was undoubtedly harsh on the Daggers given the high standard of their performance.</div><div > </div><div >They were persistent, determined and focused during the ninety minutes in which their intensity and flamboyance both impressed and entertained.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The commitment of the Daggers defence and the control that the midfield had taken of the tie left the Dons starved of time on the ball, as well as the opportunity to carve out goal scoring chances, creating an abundance of their own at the other end. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The start made by the hosts set the tone for the rest of the game, taking the lead eight minutes in when the Turvey pounced on Jordy Mongoy's low cross and finished from close-range, before Mongoy almost doubling the lead a minute later with an effort from range that flew wide.</div><div ><br /></div><div >A header was also inches away with  from a delightful cross from the left as the Daggers went into the interval with the upper hand. </div><div ><br /></div><div >The hosts shone brightly in an encouraging second half that saw the Daggers move the ball around swiftly and continue to wreak havoc amongst a busy Dons backline and test the resolve of the opposing keeper, who tipped Jordy Mongoy’s curling free-kick over the bar before collecting the forward’s hooked effort with the Daggers man onside in front of a gaping goal.</div><div ><br /></div><div >The Daggers were continuously committing men forward as they gathered further momentum to aid their attacking presence.</div><div ><br /></div><div >Given the volume of chances created, the Daggers will undoubtedly have been ruing the chances missed as they were caught on the counter following lengthy spell inside the opposition box that failed to come to fruition, enabling the Dons number nine to slide in an angled strike to equalise.</div><div ><br /></div><div >But the spirits of the hosts were not dampened by the unanticipated leveler as they fought on for a potential winner which nearly arrived via a stunning eighteen-yard strike from U16 Michael Agboola, whose rising side-footed effort arrowed onto the Dons crossbar and back out to safety, before substitute Luke Hirst latched on to Jordy Mongoy’s centre but couldn’t apply sufficient power to the finish.</div><div ><br /></div><div >With the encounter drawing to a halt, both Jordy Mongoy and Luke Hirst fired efforts over from 25-yards in an attempt to earn the victory they deserved. </div><div ><br /></div><div >But the tie took a bitter twist for the hosts, who were forced to spectate helplessly as the Dons number nine claimed possession in his own half and fired directly in over the head of the daggers goalkeeper from fifty yards as the Dons snatched a late victory.</div><div ><br /></div><div >After the game, the Daggers Academy Headcoach Micah Hyde gave his thoughts on an encouraging performance from his side: </div><div ><br /></div><div >“From what I’ve seen today, the future of the academy is very bright. The U16s selected was very pleasing, given the arduous task undertaken to find the quality required, they bonded well with current scholars that was on the pitch, and the quality against a strong and mature MK Dons team, was outstanding,” said a happy Hyde.</div><div ><br /></div><div >“They showed good game understanding, dictating the game, if they continue to learn and develop as players, it's encouraging signs they will become better as they get to know each other,” continued the coach.</div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Line-up</strong></div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: Louie Chapman, Liam Gordon (c), Paul Symes, Jack Lee, Richard Taylor, James Turvey, Elliot Bonds, Jordy Mongoy, Michael Agboola, Blue Gallagher, David Agboola, Luke Hirst, Mekhi Hyde, Sam Salis, Deniz Alici </div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Goalscorers</strong></div><div >Dagenham &amp; Redbridge: James Turvey 8’</div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-86292-3316008_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//academymatchreport-169292-3316009_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-27 12:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Academy,Away Fixture,Club,Fans,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>