<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3645731-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-darren-currie-post-york-city-3645731.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Darren Currie Post York City</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Darren Currie Post York City</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Darren Currie Post York City</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to Daggers Assistant Manager Darren Currie and got his thoughts about Saturday's win over struggling York City</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[After losing the last four out five matches it was crucial for the Daggers to get back to winning ways going into the last eight games of the season. Darren was happy with the player’s performance, although it wasn’t a pretty a win Currie would take seven more wins like Saturday's to see out the season.
<br  /><br  /><em >“On the back of the last couple of games our performances have been disappointing and we did speak about that but one point we did touch upon before the game today was to be more resilient even when the game isn’t going our way, we had to change our play and be harder to beat and harder to breakdown which we was on Saturday we were very hard to play against, everyone put their body on the line as we expected and that was very pleasing. The one bit of quality that we did see in the game lead to a goal which was a nice little move leading up to Raymond’s skill and finish which won us the game and to be honest I would take another 7 of them.”</em><br  /><br  />
After a new look strike force starting on Saturday and Elliot Romain getting his first start for the Club, Darren was impressed with the strikerS performance in hand earning himself man of the match.
<br  /><br  /><em >“I thought Romain did really well on Saturday for his first start which was one thing we identified in his play he has got a lot of goals this season and is a very hard worker. I thought Benson was outstanding on Saturday, he lead the line brilliantly with Elliot although I can’t fault anyone. Curtley Williams has come back in and proved to us he has been a big miss this season he’s a good talker, organiser and a big strong defender. Not only Curtley but all the boys who came back on Saturday put in a real shift and we’re happy with all of them.”  </em>    
<br  /><br  />
Darren believes having the squad depth the Daggers currently have will be crucial going into the final seven games of the season if they are to earn promotion.
<br  /><br  /><em >“A big squad is what you want going into these last games you want all your players available. We have known all along that we have got a good blend between youth and experience and you want competition for places and with them all available now the choice has got to be made by the manager what team he picks and he’ll take it game by game and pick the eleven he believes in for each individual game but at some point we are going to need them all, so we need everyone focused and pulling in the same direction.” </em><br  /><br  />
Hawkins and Okenabirhie were both missing from Saturday’s squad, with a new look side on the pitch Darren told us that hopefully Hawkins will return to the squad for our next fixture against Eastleigh but he is still unsure about the seriousness of Okenabirhie’s knock that he picked up on Tuesday night against Aldershot.
<br  /><br  /><em >“Hawkins missed the last couple of training sessions before the York game due to a bug, so we knew on Thursday we would be without Hawkins. Okenabirhie did get a knock last Tuesday at the Aldershot game, how long that is going to be at the minute we are not quite sure as the physio wants to let the swelling go down just so he can check the seriousness of it. I do like to think we will have Hawkins back for next week but Fejiri I’m not so sure."
<br /><br /></em><strong >Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br  /><div ><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-86292-3529268_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//darrencurrienew-169292-3529271_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-27 16:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>