<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3646858-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/friendly-match-report-stevenage-fc-4-3-dagenahm-and-redbridge-3646858.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Friendly Match Report: Stevenage FC 4 - 3 Dagenham and Redbridge</headline>
  <page_title>Friendly Match Report: Stevenage FC 4 - 3 Dagenham and Redbridge</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Friendly Match Report: Stevenage FC 4 - 3 Dagenham and Redbridge</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>Daggers lose out narrowly to League Two side Stevenage</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[The Daggers arrived at the Bragbury End Training ground for their behind closed door friendly against League Two side Stevenage. With returning players such as Matt Robinson and Luke Pennell featuring in the squad, it was the perfect opportunity for the players to build up their match fitness before their return to first team football.   
<br  /><br  />
After a heavily contested first five minutes Stevenage opened the scoring in the sixth minute after a lofted pass into the Daggers box finding the Stevenage forward who used clever footwork to beat his man and slot the ball past Cousins.
<br  /><br  />
Six minutes later after a frustrating period where neither team could hold onto possession for very long the Daggers found their first chance at the Stevenage goal after a Luke Howells free kick was whipped into the opposition’s box which found a leaping Barnwell rising above the Boro defence only to put the ball the wrong side of the post.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers were eager to make the game level with several chances at The Boro goal, the closest chance coming in the 14th minute after a clearance from Matt Robinson landed at young striker Joe White's feet finding him in front of the keeper the forward only managed to the slice ball just past the post.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers replied a minute later after Scholar Jordi Mongoy headed the ball through to White who coolly slotted the ball in the bottom right.
<br  /><br  />
The current Wealdstone loanne scored his second of the match on the half hour mark striking the ball from the edge of the box beating the Boro 'keeper. 
<br  /><br  />
Stevenage started the second half with ascendancy scoring two goals in quick succession putting the Daggers behind going into the final third of the match.
<br  /><br  />
The Daggers continued to try and find a way back into the game after a cross from youngster Tyrique Hyde fell to Mongoy whose shot was denied by the Stevenage stopper.
<br  /><br  />
In the 76th minute the Daggers were gifted with another chance through a second dangerous cross from Hyde finding Barnwell's head only to be claimed by the keeper once again.
<br  /><br  />
With just over 10 minutes to go, the Daggers sub Glen Southam came to action rolling back the years with a spectacular volley 35 yards out equalling the game for the third time in the match.
<br  /><br  />
The final goal in the game which gave Stevenage the win came in the 86th minute with some quick play down the left hand side of the pitch which seemed to be an ongoing weakness for the Daggers throughout the match. The game finished 4-3 to the hosts, the Daggers were unlucky to suffer a defeat from the League Two side but it gave another chance for returning players to gain the valuable minutes they needed to return to first team action.
<br  /><br  />
Daggers Line up: Cousins, Ling, Symes, Pennell, Howells, Hyde, Brown, Robinson, Mongoy, Barnwell, White
<br  /><br  />
Fans can now access full highlights on the game <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JeSqCimHQS0&amp;feature=youtu.be" >here<span style="text-decoration: underline;">.</span></a><br  />]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//matchreport-86292-3299833_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//matchreport-169292-3299834_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-29 10:00:00 AM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>