<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3646252-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-scott-doe-on-the-win-over-struggling-york-city-3646252.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Scott Doe On The Win Over Struggling York City</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Scott Doe On The Win Over Struggling York City</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Scott Doe On The Win Over Struggling York City</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to captain and defender Scott Doe after our 1-0 home victory over struggling York City</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Captain Scott Doe is pleased to have got a win over York City after the disappointing result away to Aldershot Town on Tuesday.
<br /><br /><em>“The most important thing is that we got the win and a clean sheet which is important for us as a back four as we haven’t had one for a while. It was a big win as they have been one of the in-forms teams in the league recently, but it was important for us to prove ourselves after our performance on Tuesday.”</em><br /><br />
Scott made his 300th Daggers appearance on Saturday against York City and the defender is pleased to have made it to that milestone and hopes to make it to Wembley with the Daggers once again.
<br /><br /><em>“The play off final at Wembley is a game that sticks out for me and the good thing is that we could have the chance to do that again. It is special in the play-offs and it was an incredible day out at Wembley and I would do anything to get back there again. All I want to do is stay fit, try and be consistent and play as many games as I can, it has come round really quickly for me. I was twenty when I joined and most of the seasons that I have been here, I have managed to be able to play for the majority of the games which is good for me.”</em><br /><br />
The captain is relishing helping the younger players learn and develop this season, being one of the most experienced players in the team after learning from players, such as Mark Arber, when he first arrived with the club.
<br /><br /><em>“All of the young players have done well for us this year and on Saturday is was a bit different with older players like Paul Benson, Luke Guttridge and Luke Howell all starting, which meant that we had the more experience in the team. When I first joined the club I had players like Mark Arber, Jon Nurse and Peter Gain who all helped me to learn and now I am one of the most experienced players in the team who is helping some of the younger players to learn and develop.”</em><br /><br />
Scott Doe is pleased that the Daggers managed to keep a clean sheet for the first time in ten games against a York side who scored five against Southport on Tuesday.
<br /><br /><em>“Some people may have thought playing York City at home would be easy but we knew it wasn’t going to be. Playing teams like York can be harder than coming up against someone like Forest Green or Lincoln as you know that they are going to be battling for everything as they are fighting for their lives to stay up. They had just scored five goals against Southport on Tuesday and we stopped them from scoring. There are seven games left now and we have to dig deep in these games to get the wins.”</em><br /><br />
Frankie Raymond got the assist for Scott Doe’s winning goal against Forest Green and got the winner against York City on Saturday, Captain Scott Doe is pleased for Frankie that he is showing his worth for the team.
<br /><br /><em>“I couldn’t have been happier for Frankie. The manager will make changes to the team, as that is his job, and Frankie maybe was unlucky to be dropped as he was no worse than anyone else against Aldershot on Tuesday. He has done very well for us this season when he played left back and centre midfield, and he has shown his quality with an assist against Forest Green and a goal against York.”</em><br /></div><div ><br /></div><div ><strong>Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /><div><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//scottdoeworthing86292-3466307_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//scottdoeworthing169292-3466309_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-28 13:00:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news />
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>