<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<News xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <clubname>Dagenham-and-Redbridge</clubname>
  <clubwebsiteURL>http://www.daggers.co.uk</clubwebsiteURL>
  <articleID>tcm:292-3649885-16</articleID>
  <articleURL>/news/article/2016-17/interview-paul-benson-ahead-of-eastleigh-fc-fixture-3649885.aspx</articleURL>
  <headline>Interview: Paul Benson Ahead Of Eastleigh FC Fixture</headline>
  <page_title>Interview: Paul Benson Ahead Of Eastleigh FC Fixture</page_title>
  <URL_keywords>Interview: Paul Benson Ahead Of Eastleigh FC Fixture</URL_keywords>
  <short_description>We spoke to forward Paul Benson ahead of our fixture against Eastleigh FC and got his thoughts on the current season</short_description>
  <description><![CDATA[<div >Prior to the York City game the Daggers had only won one game out of their last five fixtures, although the performance wasn’t pretty Benson believes that at this stage in the season it is more important to grind for the points than to put on a performance.
<br /><br /><em>"After the two defeats against Barrow and Aldershot, the main focus was on getting the three points, the goal did take 80 minutes to take the lead with a stroke of brilliance from Frankie off the bench but I thought it was a solid team performance."
<br /><br />
"Having been in this position a number of times before throughout my career, you don’t want to say performances are secondary but it is all about getting points and as long as we can get as many points as we can from now to the end of the season we’ll see where we are at the end. We have now just go to focus on grinding out wins and getting three points, Saturday will be another test of how we can grind out another three points and sometimes it won’t be great for the supporters to watch but I think at this stage of the season we need to grind to get to where we want come the end of the season."</em><br /><br />
The Daggers will face both Eastleigh and League leaders Lincoln in the space of two days, Benson admits this will be a test for the players and that the team cannot underestimate any teams going into the last leg of the Season.
<br /><br /><em>"If you ask the manager he will tell you at this point in the season in this League every game will be tough, as we saw with York who are in the bottom three but if you look at the form table they are one of the top teams so it is hard to say a team won’t be tough especially at this point in the season.  Lincoln will be a tough game and Saturday against Eastleigh who have a very good squad, they haven’t lived up to the potential they should of probably lived up to this season but they will still be looking to give us a game and we will have to find a way to get a result."
<br /></em><br />
Paul Benson admits this year has been tough not getting as much game time as he would have liked, but with competition from top goal scorer Oliver Hawkins, Paul agrees with every decision the Manager has made to put the Daggers where they are so far this season. 
<br /><br /><em>"It has been tough spending the majority of this season on the bench but you are here to do a job, I came back here to do a job for Dagenham and Redbridge and if that job is more off the pitch than on it this season then that’s the job I’m here to do. I trust the manager to make the right decisions, if you look at the League table you’d probably say more often than not he has made the correct decisions. We have a player in Hawkins who has had a tremendous season he has been unbelievable for us this year, I just try to do as well as I can in every training session I have spoken to the manager and I have no problem with the position I have found myself in this season. I will just try and do the best I can for this Club, this is my Club I love it and will do anything I can to try and make this club successful."</em><br /><strong><br />
Daggers Player HD subscribers can watch the full interview <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong><br /><div><strong>Not a subscriber? Sign up today, full information <a href="http://www.player.daggers.co.uk/latest-news">here</a></strong></div></div>]]></description>
  <lead_image>/cms_images//mrpaulbenson86292-3649557_478x359.jpg</lead_image>
  <featured_image>/cms_images//mrpaulbenson169292-3649558_1600x900.jpg</featured_image>
  <gallery />
  <author />
  <quote />
  <quote_author />
  <quote_date />
  <news_video_url />
  <FinalUrl />
  <publish_date>2017-03-30 17:30:00 PM</publish_date>
  <news_type />
  <featured_news>Featured</featured_news>
  <excluding />
  <userdefined_keyword />
  <Tags>Away Fixture,Club,Fans,First Team,Home,League,Match,Team</Tags>
</News>